C'mon!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
Inari! Give me a hand.
I'll be right there.
This mist...
Sasuke! Sakura! They're coming!
I knew he was still alive.
Making an appearance so soon, eh...
Say, Kakashi Sensei.
This is his...Hidden Mist Jutsu, right?!
Sorry to have kept you waiting, Kakashi.
I see you've got those brats
with you as always.
He's still trembling. Poor thing.
I'm trembling with...excitement.
Do it, Sasuke.
I can see him!
Well, well. So you discerned
the Water Doppelganger Jutsu.
That brat's grown quite a bit.
This means a rival has emerged, Haku.
So it seems.
Damn it!
I'm totally late!
Well, well... It seems my prediction
was right on the money.
Prediction?
That little mask...
Oh!
I knew it... Heh!
So the Elite Shinobi of
the Hidden Mist thing
was a bald-faced lie!
No matter how you look at him,
he's gotta be a comrade of Zabuza.
Standing together with him and all...
How dare he show up like that
after what he did!
I hate brats who think they're so cool...
He's better than you, Kakashi Sensei.
Oh...really?
I'll do it.
Huh?
With his bad acting...
I hate brats who think they're so cool!
Sasuke, you are so cool!
That Sakura doesn't take stabs at Sasuke...
He's an impressive youth.
Hmm...
Even though those Water Clones
have only 1/10th the strength
of their original...
To think he went that well.
However, you made
the preemptive move.
Go!
Right!
What?!
Haku's Secret Jutsu:
Crystal Ice Mirrors
Are you Tazuna's daughter?
Sorry, but you're coming with us.
Mom!
Don't come out!
Get out of here, quick!
What's with you, brat?!
Shall we take him, too?
One hostage is fine.
Hostage...?!
Then...
Shall we kill him?
Wait!
If you lay a hand on that child...
I'll bite off my tongue
and kill myself!
You want a hostage, right?
Thank your mom, kid.
Oh, man...
It's not enough...
Knock it off.
You just tried out your sword earlier.
Forget it already and
let's take the woman.
Mom, I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry!
I'm weak, so I can't protect you...
I don't want to die...
I'm scared!
You crybaby...
So you're just gonna cry all day
like the lead in a tragedy?
An idiot like you can just
cry forever! You crybaby!
He's probably tired of crying.
So, he knows the true meaning of
the word strong.
Like your father.
For the things I truly hold
dear to myself...
I protect them until the end
with both these arms,
even if it looks like I might lose my life!
Inari...
Can I...
can I also become strong...?
Dad!
Looking at that beautiful skin
of yours makes me want to cut you.
Hey...walk faster.
Wait!
Inari!
What? It's just the kid from before.
Get...get away from my mom!
Man...This brat's hopeless.
Let's do it!
If you do that, I'll bite off
my tongue and...
Shut up. Go to sleep.
I...na...ri.
Well, well...
He can see that speed, eh...
Yes...
Sakura, surround Tazuna and
don't move away from me.
Let Sasuke handle him!
Okay.
I don't want to have to kill you...
I'd like for you to back down.
Nonsense...
I knew it...
But you won't be able to keep up
with my speed.
Also, I've already made
two preemptive moves.
Two preemptive moves?
The first one is the scattered water.
And the second one was
blocking one of your hands...
Therefore, you'll just be able
to defend my attack...
What?! With one hand he's...?!
A one-handed Sign?
I've never seen such a thing before...
A Thousand Needles of Death!
So he doesn't want to kill him...eh.
I wonder if that's how he really feels...
Sasuke!
Remember...that training...
Build up Chakra at one burst...
The Substitution Jutsu...?!
The woman... Hmm?
Sorry I was late.
Heroes usually appear
on the scene late, so...
Naruto...!
Inari, you did well!
Huh?
Thanks to you distracting them,
I was able to save your mom.
Naruto...how did you know that
those samurai were here?
In the forest, there was a boar that
had been cut-up with a sword.
Other than that,
there were trees with lots of cuts.
They headed in
the direction of your house...
so I got worried.
I see.
Well...
If it isn't the no-good Ninja
that Tazuna hired...
Let's do it...
Yeah...
Here they come!
Hah! Something like that won't work!
Fools.
Prepare yourself!
W-Wow...!
It's done!
Naruto, you're just like...a Ninja!
You fool.
I was a Ninja to start with!
Build up Chakra at one burst...
to the feet!
He vanished...
You're surprisingly stupid...
From here on...
you'll only defend my attack!
To think Haku would
lose in speed...
It seems that I'm faster than you...
I can't have you mocking our team,
calling them brats...
He may not look it,
but Sasuke is the number one rookie
of the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
And Sakura is our sharpest...
Hah! Serves you right!
And the other one is
the number one hyperactive,
knucklehead Ninja, Naruto Uzumaki.
You have a cold?
I'm okay.
Anyway...
Sorry about yesterday, Inari.
Huh?
Branding you a crybaby...
Forget I ever said that.
You're strong!
Dang it!
I...decided never
to cry again, but...
Now you'll laugh at me again
and call me a crybaby.
What're you saying...?!
It's okay...when you're happy.
It's okay to cry when you're happy!
Naruto...
Now then.
I can leave the rest to you, right?
Yeah...
Okay, I'm going to hop over
to the bridge for a bit.
Man, it's tough being a hero!
That's for sure!
Haku, do you know what this means?
At this rate, you'll be defeated
by your intended victim...
Yes...
What...?
It's unfortunate...
Is this...cold air...?
Hidden Jutsu!
Crystal Ice Mirrors!
What is it? What's that Jutsu?
Are these...mirrors?!
What...
in the world...?!
Damn it!
I'm your opponent, aren't I?
Since that Jutsu has appeared...
he's done for.
Now then...I'll start.
I shall show you...
my true speed!
Sasuke!
If you make a move,
I'll kill those two!!
I'm sorry, Tazuna!
I'm stepping away from here for a bit.
Sure. Go!
Sakura!
Sasuke!
Take this!
He caught it?!
What?!
Who is it?!
It's that idiot...that showoff...
The number one hyperactive,
knucklehead Ninja...
Naruto Uzumaki...
is finally here!
Naruto Uzumaki is finally here!
It'll be okay.
Now that the hero of the story
has appeared,
I'll smash those stupid
funny-looking mirrors in no time...
Huh? Why won't mirrors
made of ice break?
Why won't they melt?
What the heck is going on here?!
Next episode: "The Number One Hyperactive
Knucklehead Ninja Joins the Fight!"
As for me, will I be able
to kick butt once again?