Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
The End of Tears
By special...
By special, you meant that?!
I don't feel like I'm gonna lose.
Sasuke...you...
If they continue to be released
for a long period of time,
Curse Marks will progressively
eat your body.
When they have entirely eaten you...
you will lose yourself...forever.
This body...
It looks like there's no time to waste.
I don't have any feeling in my left arm...
That power you have...
seems to involve some risks too, huh?
Did you know...?
That this place...
is called the Final Valley.
I think this is the perfect stage,
don't you think...Naruto?
Oh yeah...
I said there'd be
no more talking, didn't I?
Well, in that case,
how about we bring it to a close...?
This battle.
All our battles up to now!
Next for Squad Seven. Naruto Uzumaki!
Sakura Haruno!
Yipeee!
With Naruto...?
And Sasuke Uchiha.
Yipeee!
With Sasuke...?
Try not to slow me down, loser.
You...!
But...but...but...you told us...
That's why they.....
Aren't we a three-man squad?
That's right! We three are one!
Hey!
Are you hurt? Scaredy Cat?
Hey...are you hurt? Scaredy Cat?
You are one of the ones I want to fight.
Sasuke!
I want...to fight you, too.
I don't want to see any more deaths
of my precious comrades.
Summoning Jutsu!
I...will protect Sakura!
What's so funny?
Nothing's funny, believe it! I'm happy!
When I think I can finally beat you here!
What did you say?!
Don't talk foolish, you failure!
I'm not going to be a failure forever!
Just bring it, now!
Put on your headband before that!
I'll wait.
I don't need such a thing...
Just do it!
You wouldn't even be able
to put one wound on my forehead!
You're wrong!
I'm saying this is a testament
to fighting on equal terms
as a Leaf Shinobi!
Naruto!
Sasuke!
I'll win no matter what!
Don't flatter yourself!
Stop it!
And from this time onward...
Chidori!
Rasengan!
-Rasengan!
-Chidori!
This Chakra...
This isn't good!
Naruto...
I...
It's started to rain!
Will it erase the scent?
No problem.
We're already close. This way.
Was I too late...?
Naruto!
Why did things come to this?!
This is Sasuke's...
I didn't make it in time...
please forgive me.
Naruto...
I know the kind of person you are...
You must have made a desperate effort.
Sasuke...
That's my boy...
With me, you're all
your father talks about...
You are my one and only brother.
I will continue to be for you...
a wall that you must find
a way to cross over.
Even if you were to hate me...
You are someone
who can obtain Mangekyo Sharingan
just like me...
However, on one condition.
Your closest friend...
The Final Valley...
To think that Sasuke and Naruto
would battle it out here...
How ironic...
Yeah...
When I look at the flow of this water,
it's as if I'm being confronted
by an eternal, never-ending battle...
Just like the fate of the two people
depicted in these statues here
who founded the Village Hidden
in the Leaves...
Naruto and Sasuke,
as long as you both live...
You have to kill...
your closest friend!
I'm not gonna...
abide by everything you say!
I will get my hands on power
doing it my own way!
I will surpass you doing it my own way!
Without fail!
The rain's...let up, hasn't it?
Yeah.
With that much rain,
I won't be able to pursue
the scent anymore.
Naruto is more important now
than pursuing Sasuke.
Yeah.
It's gotten interesting, hasn't it?
Yeah...
When I recalled the parts one by one,
I felt as though
I had understood everything
Faded words
which I kept so close to me
Speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
and this distant yearning for you
I live,
simply repeating this cycle
Held in my two hands
A droplet of time
Softly clutching forgotten memories
Lost words
I'll keep these thoughts...
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry, Sakura.
I made a once-in-a-lifetime promise
that I would bring Sasuke back.
But, I'm not finished yet!
I'll fulfill my promise, no matter what!
Since that was what I was always saying...
that I won't go back on my word.
That's my Way of Ninja!
Next episode:
"The Promise That Could Not Be Kept"