We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers don't care
what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road filled
with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes
and take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose, so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers don't care
what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn) We're
gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn) We're
gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
This man Jiraiya
does not fall victim
to any woman's allurement,
but rather his forte is
winning women's affections!
You were totally excited by a lame
tactic like a woman winking at you!
You shouldn't be the one to try acting
all suave and cool, you Pervy Sage!
Like I said,
don't call me that in front of people...
Be quiet...
More importantly
these people aren't normal, Pervy Sage!
Didja hear me, Pervy Sage?!
Like I said, don't call me "Pervy Sage"!
You are, after all, Master Jiraiya,
one of the legendary Sannin...
I didn't believe that I'd be
able to stop you so easily
despite the fact that you are
a huge womanizer.
What?!
You know the true identity of Pervy Sage?!
Well no, that's not
necessarily who I really am...
Seems like you released the Genjutsu
that we had put on that woman.
You shouldn't call yourself a man
for using such a cowardly tactic
like casting a Genjutsu on
the woman with your hypnotic eyes
to separate me and Naruto.
Separate us...
Why would they do that?
Your target is Naruto, after all.
You are
after the Nine-Tailed Fox in Naruto...
No wonder Kakashi knew that as well...
I see clearly now.
The information source was you.
To abduct Naruto
is the No.1 priority placed by
our organization, Akatsuki!
What's going on...?
I can't let you have Naruto...
I wonder about that.
This is perfect...
I'll get rid of you two right here!
Don't butt in...
The one that's going to kill him is ...
Me!
Hate Among the Uchihas:
The Last of the Clan
Sasuke...
Revenge, I see...
Right now, I have no interest in you...
Don't mess with me!
Sasuke!
Darn you!
Naruto! I told you not to butt in!
I told you before...
I've lived only for this very day...
for this very day!
Sasuke...
Not yet...
You can't even make a hand
sign together at this point...
This is...
my battle!
Fine.
Wha...?
You heard that didn't you?
This is their battle.
Let's not bother with it.
Fine then!
Wh-Why...?
Our power difference hasn't
changed at all since that time...
Why is that?
He doesn't show any mercy.
What have I... been doing all this time?
Whatever have I...
You are weak.
And you are weak...
because you don't have enough hate.
This place is...
Could it be?!
That's right.
This is our house.
Dad! Mom!
You are weak.
For the next 24 hours...
Stop it...
Relive that day.
Stop it!
Uncle! Auntie!
You're not even worth killing.
Foolish younger brother...
If you want to kill me,
begrudge me! Hate me!
And keep on surviving in
that unsightly manner...
Just continue fleeing and fleeing
and hang onto your life!
Hasn't changed at all...
Using Tsukiyomi: Nightmare Realm
on your own little brother.
Stop it already! You!
Wha...?!
Th-This...
Ninja Art: Toad Mouth Trap!
How unfortunate, Itachi, Kisame.
You guys are already inside my stomach!
I summoned the esophagus of the giant
toad of the Mt. Myomoku rock cave.
You guys are wanted criminals anyway.
I'll turn you guys into
fodder for the stone toad.
What?!
Wh-What is this?
Naruto, you stay still!
Don't worry, it's my Jutsu!
Come here, Kisame!
Oh!
Darn it!
It's useless!
There hasn't been one person who has
been able to escape from this!
A wall of flesh is charging at us!
The wall is faster.
At this rate...
Hey... Pervy Sage!
What's the matter?!
Huh!
They've gone!
I cannot believe that this wall
has been torn through...
Why must we retreat?
You would be...
We have no reason to rush to get
Naruto in the current condition.
Besides,
I have to rest my body
somewhere for a while.
Not just Tsukuyomi,
but he also made me use Amaterasu as well...
What is this fire?
-It's black...
-Don't get so close!
How did those guys manage to get out?
Not only that...
What are these black flames?
The stone toad who has the ability to
blow fire had its intestine's burned...
Huh...?
All right!
Sealing Jutsu: Fire Seal!
It'll be okay for now.
Now for Sasuke!
Sasuke!
Sasuke...
Dynamic...
-Guy?!
-Entry!
Well... Eh...
I'm sorry to have kicked you so directly.
I was in a rush and I forgot my mirror...
I used this headband instead,
but it was hard to see.
And I assumed this rough-hewn
face was the enemy...
I just let the flames of the burning
juvenescence take over me...
I'm sorry!
Is that ... supposed to be an apology?
I'm a simple-minded guy
just like how my face looks.
It doesn't really matter.
More importantly,
we have to get Sasuke to the Medical Team!
Yes!
He's broken his arm and ribs.
Not only that, he's lost consciousness
from some kind of mental blow
he received from the Visual Jutsu!
This boy also experienced that Jutsu...
Hey Pervy Sage!
Is Sasuke going to be all right?
Seems like he's received a significant
amount of mental damage.
I'm going to kill you!
Die!
-You jerk!
-You're in the way!
Darn...
Why?!
What did that guy do to Sasuke?!
Hey, Pervy Sage!
We've gotta change our plan!
I got scared earlier,
but this time
I'm going to chase those
black-capes and get them!
It's me that they want, right?!
Then, I'll be the one to make my way over!
Humph,
you're only going to be
killed if you go now.
They're at a totally
different level from you.
I just managed
to get you away from them...
Then, are we just going
to keep running away?!
Are we supposed to keep living in fear?!
Shut your mouth for a second!
You are weak.
I'm sorry, Guy.
I thought that I had spared
the boy's feeling, but...
I should have saved him much sooner.
Kakashi has also come
down with the same Jutsu...
We don't know when he will
regain consciousness.
Kakashi Sensei?!
When my students are hurt...
I always wish,
from the bottom of my heart...
If that person,
who is a medical specialist, were here...
That's why we're going to go find her now.
What? You mean, her?
Could it be...?
W-Wait...!
C-Could this money be...?!
Yup, that's right...
The one who uses the slug
and drives illness away,
and who is also one of the Sannin like me...
All right!
We're going to turn
around our luck with this!
Princess Tsunade
with the letter "Gamble" on her back!
A cycle of hardship, right?
Inside, we were crying, right?
But the one thing we won't give up
is the dream we've chosen, right?
It's a secondary role,
a role in the shadows
But in reaching for that dream,
let us stay centered, let us stay true
Over and over,
we hung on without giving up
Over and over, we kept coming back up
Over and over,
we believed and dreamed
Over and over, we've seen fools
Over and over,
we've stood in the shadows of others
Now, it's our turn...
Let us bask in our dreams
It's festival, festival,festival!
I'm going to spend like
there's no tomorrow!
Wait a minute, Naruto!
-I will keep your wallet for you.
-Huh?!
It's been said since ages past
that three forbidden factors:
money, alcohol, and women,
are believed to cause Ninja failures.
I am not like you, Pervy Sage!
All right!
I am going to enjoy the festival!
Next time: "A New Training Begins:
I Will Be Strong!"
Wait. What are we gonna
do about my training?