Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, "See you..."
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I'm not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
The Bewildering Forest
Hey kids, get out of here
if you don't wanna get hurt.
Better not think lightly of me!
I'm not gonna hand this guy over,
no matter what!
Ninja Dropouts...
It's not gonna end up with
you just getting hurt.
You're gonna get killed.
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Ninja Art: Blood Rain.
Todoroki!
Damn!
My Jutsu isn't Ninjutsu.
It's Killer Jutsu.
Sakura!
Lee, are you all right?
Yeah, just barely.
More importantly, where's Naruto?
Is everybody safe?
Yes. However, Commander Todoroki
is nowhere to be seen!
What was that?!
Naruto...
Die!
Damn! Let go, you jerk!
Naruto!
Damn!
Father! Mother!
Akio!
What a shame...
You're not getting back
with your comrades.
Todoroki! Gantetsu!
Are you all right?!
Y-Yeah... We're fine.
What are we going to do now?
We've gotten separated from
Sakura and Bushy Brows...
There isn't any question in my mind.
It's my mission to deliver
this guy to the capital.
But the ship's been destroyed, and...
Those guys are pursuing us!
What are you doing?!
If they're gonna steal this guy
away from us anyway,
it would be better to
take care of him right here!
What do you mean take care of him...?
Even if we delivered him the capital,
it's certain that
he'll be sentenced to death...
Therefore...
Rather than having them
take him away, it would be better to...!
It's not set in stone that
they'll be able to take him away!
Let's go!
Your mission is to guard this guy, right?
That's exactly what my mission is too!
If you so much as try anything,
your head's gonna roll!
Run!
We'll be fine...
now that we've come this far...
Looks like we've totally lost them.
We've gone pretty deep
into the forest, haven't we?
I can get our bearings from
the position of the moon.
It's too dangerous to go back
to the river.
We'll continue straight through
this forest to the capital.
Because it's my mission.
Are you sure it'll be okay?
What do you mean?
You said earlier you were going
to finish this guy off, right?
I was talking about
a worst-case scenario.
Got it...
Well then, let's get moving.
I wonder if Sakura is all right...
Naruto...
It's Naruto...
He's gonna be just fine.
Yeah...
So let's hurry up and link up with him!
Lee!
I detect something strange...
Where...?
Up above!
Lee!
Let's follow him!
The enemy might have captured Naruto!
What's the matter?
We're walking in the direction
of the moon, right...?
Then why is the moon following us?
That's strange...
What's going on...?
The Forest of Bewilderment...
Once you get lost you can
never find you way out again.
He talked...
You are in custody.
You're not allowed to talk!
Wait a second!
The Forest of Bewilderment...
You know something about this place?
What do you know? Tell us!
The Ninja Dropouts have
a hide-out in this forest.
What was that?!
So we were escorting you
through Ninja Dropout territory...?!
This forest is perfect for a hide-out.
The fog, the winds that
sweep through the forest,
the extreme magnetic fields...
They all make a person lose
their sense of direction.
A person finding himself in
this forest for the first time
will never find his way out.
I don't believe that...
There's no way we won't find
our way out...?
-You guys won't.
-Huh?
But for me, a member of
the Ninja Dropouts...
the outcome will be different.
I will...
I will guide you through this forest.
Yeah, that's right...
For you, a Ninja Dropout,
this forest is like your backyard, right?
Okay then, let's have you guide us!
Are you some kind of idiot?!
It's true...
The finesse that the Ninja Dropouts
showed earlier on
makes sense if you think
that this is their garden...
And I'll believe you when you say
you have a hide-out here.
Then even more so...
-Even more so, it's a no!
-Huh...?
Don't you get it?
This guy is gonna pretend to
be guiding us out of the forest
but will actually be taking us
to the hide-out.
Todoroki...
This is an emergency situation...
If we don't kill him, we'll be killed.
W-Wait a minute!
Nobody's gonna care...if this guy dies!
Todoroki!
What's that...?
I took all the money the Ninja Dropouts
had stolen up to now...
So I was tortured...
Those guys don't want to rescue me...
They just want to get that money
back from me.
Once they have the money back,
those guys will kill me too.
Do you really think I'll believe that?
Wait a second!
The Ninja Dropouts hide-out is
here in this forest, right...?
Which means it's like
a backyard to them too,
just like it is for Gantetsu...
Which means that...
Which means that what?
Well, since we've trespassed
into their garden
it's likely that the Ninja Dropouts
will come after us
whether Gantetsu's
betrayed them or not...
So I think our only option is to
pin our hopes on this guy...
Am I wrong?
Hey, are you sure
you know what you're doing?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Those guys won't figure out
this kind of circuitous route.
Can we really trust this guy...?
What?!
I'm used to it's venom. It's nothing.
Are you really gonna be all right?
Yeah...
Hey!
What's the matter?
No way!
You fell for it. You fell for it!
Here it comes!
Ninja Art: Crimson Mud!
Die!
You're the one who fell for it!
I combined the Shadow Clone Jutsu
and the Transformation Jutsu.
What was that?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Now it's my turn!
Rasengan!
I'm gonna strike you down!
Don't think it's gonna be that
easy to strike me down!
Like I'll let you get away!
Naruto!
That guy! Trying to get away, huh!
What are you doing?
Th-That sound is...
What?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Rasengan!
Thanks to you we made it...Gantetsu.
What's with you guys?
They want to fight, it seems.
I won't... I won't be fooled.
You...you...
We'll be safe if we just follow Gantetsu.
Todoroki!
Stop it, Todoroki!
You said you were going to deliver
Gantetsu to the capital, right?
This guy...
There's no way I'll forgive this guy!
What are you talking about?!
This guy...
This guy killed my family...
he killed my little brother!
Wh-What was that...?
Gantetsu...
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I'm told that
there is no bright future
I'll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
It's true that Gantetsu may be evil,
but how is taking revenge out
on him going to change things?!
Isn't our mission to take Gantetsu
to the capital?
And I... I don't think that
he's an evil person.
Anyway, you leave me
no choice if you won't listen.
I'll stop you with all my strength!
Next time: "Memory of Flames"