I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long way to go
on that road.
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky
with countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that...
What were you gazing at?
Follow My Lead!
The Great Survival Challenge!
I-I'll do my best!
Looks like it'll be interesting,
huh, Konohamaru?!
Here...Here...
Heck no, heck no!
No way in heck, believe it!
Why should I have to do
some babysitting mission like that?
I don't care what you say,
Old Lady Tsunade. I refuse!
The team organization has already
been announced to the students!
I don't care about that!
As for me, I want to train more,
get stronger and...
"I'll become Hokage someday,
believe it," huh?
A person like that...
would never betray the expectations
of his adorable juniors, would he?
Become a unit leader and
issue appropriate instructions...
Protect the lives of your men
and promptly carry out your mission...
I thought this mission I'm giving you guys...
is ideal practice for becoming Hokage.
Ideal practice for becoming...Hokage?
If you're going so far as to say that,
then it can't be helped...
It's too bad...
Whoa! Kidding, kidding,
kidding, just kidding!
Say so sooner if that's the case.
Practice for becoming Hokage...
Yeah-yeah...
That has a nice ring to it.
He fell for it.
Jeez, he's naïve...
Naruto...
Now then,
my adorable team members...are...
These guys...?
Oh! Why the heck are you
on that side?!
Man, I don't want to do such
a troublesome mission either.
Shikamaru will be
an assistant to us instructors.
I will now begin the explanation
of the outdoor training
to be conducted over
one night and two days.
This is the spot you all
will be setting out for...
Great Stone Face of Warudakumi
on the summit of Mount Takurami.
The team leader will not take routes
other than the ones indicated on the map...
in order to ensure the safety
of the Academy students.
Along the way, there will be obstacles such
as instructors disguised as enemy Ninja,
as well as trap and the like.
But you Academy students
should be able to safely evade them
if you act according to the instructions
of your team leaders.
You'll see
the Stone Face of Warudakumi
after you cover about
eighty kilometers.
The team that brings the secret document
hidden there back to the village...
will have completed the training
upon crossing the finish line.
There is only one secret document.
This will be a competition
with the other teams.
All right.
We'll finish first, no matter what!
You guys ready?!
– Yeah!
An important thing about survival is
acquiring food with your own resources...
This is called Beef Sashimi Grass
and it grows in this area...
You can eat it raw and
it becomes precious food
when the chips are down...
– Wow!
All right! All members acquire food!
– Yay!
This is it!
Let's eat...
That's a Blowfish Sashimi Grass.
It's a very similar poisonous grass.
See? The shape of the leaf
is a bit different, right...?
You two be careful as well, okay?
– Okay!
Listen up, an important thing in survival
is to acquire food by your own resources.
Something's not right!
Disappointing, isn't it...?
I've got an uneasy feeling...
Let's see...
The geography in this area
throws magnets out of kilter...
When you can't use a compass...
Huh?
You're wearing a watch, right?
Oh...yes!
Look for the bisecting angle,
which divides the 12:00 direction and the
current direction of the hour hand in two...
And then, when you line up that direction
with the sun as of now...
the approximate 12:00 direction is south.
Remember that!
– Okay!
Let's...see...
Huh? This way...?
Hey, Konohamaru... This way?
No doubt about it...
He's totally lost...
Right, right!
Yikes...This is bad, believe it.
A-All right! This way!
Come with me, believe it!
Will it be okay?
That was a more challenging route
than I thought, wasn't it, guys?
Challenging, my foot!
We're back at where we came from!
Man, we can't trust you,
Brother Naruto!
Then why don't you try?!
Give me that!
Oh... It's this way.
N-Not bad...
What's the matter, Konohamaru?!
What're you doing, Konohamaru?!
Give me that!
Sorry... Here.
Let me see...
Oh, it's that way!
What were you guys doing?!
Hey, we've come back again!
What...? How in the world can
we get out of here?!
All right... I'll do my best!
I don't feel good...
Hey!
Good grief...
Are you guys okay?
– Yes, Lee Sensei!
What did you say...just now?!
Lee Sensei...!
Ahh, that has such a lovely ring to it.
This is youth, this is extreme youth!
Now, run towards that setting sun!
– Yes, Lee Sensei!
Your sweat sparkling in
the setting sun is wonderful!
– Yes, Lee Sensei!
Finally made it, huh...?
Now, I guess I'll check out
Naruto's team in action.
Now then... Show me what
you've learned until now!
Go!
All right! Formation One, Konohamaru!
Sexy Jutsu!
Adults are a cinch with this Jutsu.
You idiot!
You wish, Brother Naruto!
Times are evolving!
New formation!
– Cheesecake Jutsu!
Fashion Model!
Movie Star!
Tanning Salon Receptionist!
– We're Cheesecakes!
I'd like to say, just what
I'd expect of my best pupils,
but you still don't have
enough "bust-waist-hip."
Jeez...This guy's such a pain...
as always.
Iruka Sensei!
What is it?
A report from the observatory...
Wow... It's warm...
Good thing we listened to you
and prepared it ahead of time.
We would've been soaked if
we were even a little slow
putting up the tent!
Reading ahead is important for
a Ninja...
In particular, if you don't acutely
sense the weatherr,
it could end up being fatal,
so be careful.
– Okay!
What're you doing, Moegi?
Pull it properly, believe it!
I've had it!
I don't want to do this!
Moegi! Stop saying selfish things
and hold it!
But...
What, really?!
It seems it's going to directly hit
the Leaf Village before dawn...
Jeez, why now...?!
The communication from
the observatory
was probably delayed due to the storm.
We have no choice, then...
The training is suspended.
Convey the order to all
the teams immediately!
– Yes, sir!
Why'd you put the tent away?!
Brother Naruto, what's the deal?
This path isn't on the map.
We fell behind the others more
than I thought.
We can't be resting
Then, this path...
Yeah... It's not on the map.
It's a shortcut route!
– What?!
Will this be okay?!
What're you doing?!
We'll be late if we don't hurry!
Don't talk nonsense!
We haven't learned that method
of climbing!
Right! Chakra control comes after
we've become senior students!
That makes no difference.
You can do anything if you get serious!
Come on! Let's go!
Damn it...!
Grab on!
Wh-What're you doing?!
Oh! Let go, Konohamaru!
If I let go, he'll blow away!
Let go of the bag, Udon!
I-I can't...!
It can't be helped...
No! I can't hold on any longer!
That was a close one!
I issued an evacuation advisory
to all the teams encamped
at the foot of the mountain.
I see... Now all that's left is
Naruto's team...
Iruka Sensei!
I found this on an unplanned route...
An unplanned route, you say?!
What do we do now?
We've lost our tent and our food...
There's no point in saying that!
What?! It's because you put your foot
on my backpack in the first place...
What're you talking about?!
If my foot hadn't gotten caught,
we would've blown away.
Now, now...
Stop fighting, believe it.
Why didn't you close the zipper, Udon?!
Sorry...
Now, now...
Don't say that, Konohamaru!
When you get right down to it,
it's your fault for entering a strange route,
Brother Naruto!
-Right, right!
-What?
We got behind because
you got caught in a trap
and were lost forever!
Hey, what did you say?!
You can't justify yourself, can you?!
We could've gotten through faster
if you guys hadn't gotten in the way!
It's because our leader's
not dependable!
What?!
Heh! How silly!
– What did you say?!
What?!
Ohh... I'm hungry...
Temporary ceasefire.
This is the spot.
That Naruto...
After all I told him about
following instructions!
Taking the direction of the wind
under consideration,
they're above here, I guess...
Okay, let's go, Shikamaru.
Right.
What's this?!
It's all stuff we need hot water for...
About the only thing we can eat
is the baumkuchen cake...
I'm hungry...
You're asking too much!
This is survival,
so it's common sense to have things ready
that can be eaten right away!
Right, right!
I won't share if you're going to complain!
I'm taking the big one.
The biggest one...is mine!
The big one... The big one...
Okay, eat up!
What...? But...
It's divided in three?
You're not having any here,
Brother Naruto?
Back in the day,
I also went without food once
when I screwed up during training.
We couldn't all pull together
and Kakashi Sensei got mad at us...
Cripes! Who cares about
three working as one?!
It's called teamwork.
I figured it out at that time.
The important thing for
a Ninja isn't rules or codes,
but teamwork acting for
the sake of comrades...
Here.
Sakura...
Brother Naruto...
Well as for me,
I don't like sweets, so!
– Oh...
You're one to talk
having bought it yourself!
Your stomach growled.
You have some too, Brother Naruto!
It's pretty slippery.
You okay, Shikamaru?
Yeah...
Damn it... How could that Naruto
take such a dangerous route?!
Jeez... He's always causing
some kind of trouble.
What a pain he is...
It seems they were here
until just a little while ago...
He really does cause...trouble.
The finish line is right
before our eyes!
That method of climbing isn't fair,
I tell you!
Right! I knew we shouldn't have
shared the food!
What is it, Udon?
What're you doing?
We'll leave you behind!
Something's...coming...
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
R-Run while you can!
G-Got it!
H-Hurry it up...
Brother Naruto!
– Brother Naruto!
Brother! Brother Naruto!
Hang in there!
What should we do, Konohamaru?!
We'll go help him...
But...it looks like
it'll crumble again!
Brother Naruto!
Let's go, Udon, Moegi!
Are you awake, Brother Naruto?!
That was close. So I made it into
a space between the rocks, huh...?
We're coming to help!
Idiot! Run, quick!
Konohamaru...
We can't do it...
Let's call for help...
Brother said it before!
The important thing for
a Ninja is teamwork!
Konohamaru, you...
No! If I move even a little,
the support rock will give way
and you guys will end up
getting entangled in this!
Brother Naruto! Have you forgotten
what you yourself said?
You can do anything...
...if you get serious!
You guys...
Konohamaru Gang!
Help Brother Naruto!
– Yeah!
Be careful!
Easy does it!
Yeah.
But hurry.
It moved...Time it right and
toss it away in one shot.
Got it!
One, two...!
Yes!
It's a big success!
We did it, we did it!
That was a close one...
– Naruto!
You guys okay?
Iruka Sensei! Shikamaru!
Naruto! Above you!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Run towards Shikamaru!
– Brother Naruto!
Naruto!
Rasengan!
Naruto...
Man, making us get all nervous...
Excellent, Brother Naruto...
Thank goodness!
Yeah!
So, what's the meaning of this?
So you see...
It was all Brother Naruto's orders!
We were opposed,
but he forced us to move ahead
saying the only way to finish first
was to take a dangerous shortcut!
I said many times we shouldn't
because it's dangerous!
But...
– Team leader Naruto forcibly went ahead!
What...? What?
It seems that's about the size of it...
You're prepared, right, Naruto?
Say...
Since when did your teamwork
get so good?
Naruto!
I've had it with lectures!
Hey, wait! Naruto!
Wait!
So many things happen
on this endless road, huh?
Although you're strong-willed,
your voice wavered on the phone today
What dreams did you
chase to get here?
Even I have times when
I just don't understand, baby
When you're sad,
I'll be close to you
Even on nights when we're apart,
Across the verdant wild
came the slender giant!
Equipped with two wakizashi,
a wandering bounty hunter!
The target is Gosunkugi,
the villainous thief!
A fierce battle of hunt and be hunted!
Then comes the voice to halt the action!
Hey, hey, hey!
That bastard thief is mine!
Enter Naruto Uzumaki!
Next time:
"The Bounty Hunter from the Wilderness"