Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only "the beginning,"
I wake up
and someday,
I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things
are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
Sasuke's movements have stopped!
There's still quite a bit of distance, though...
So Sasuke caught up to him, huh?
Okay!
Huh? This smell is...?!
W-What's wrong?!
Did something happen to Sasuke?!
I didn't notice until now.
You...
use the same shampoo as me.
This floral green fragrance...
No doubt!
H-Hey now...!
Well...my coat's shinier.
Don't be saying stupid things
at such an important time!
– I'm the same as a dog?
– Sorry, sorry...
Same as a dog... Same as a dog...
– Hey Sakura?
– Same as a dog...
Same as a dog...
Same as a dog... Same as a dog...
Hey Sakura...!
Wait!
Oh! Hey! Don't go ahead of me!
A Mistake from the Past:
A Face Revealed!
Dang it!
Sasuke Uchiha!
I won't let you get away now!
Jeez, this kid of all people...
at a time when Gaara is like this.
Man, this is bad.
Heh! That's fine.
Kankuro! Take Gaara and go quickly!
Leave him to me!
But Temari...!
No matter how you look at it,
you can't beat him alone!
Leave me be!
This is an important mission for
the Village Hidden in the Sand!
Make Gaara the first priority!
Besides, he's quite my type of a guy...
Go! Kankuro!
I don't think so!
I won't let you get away!
Eat this!
My opponent is that Uchiha kid...
This is not good. I only have
a bit of Chakra left.
I'll stand even less of a chance
if he uses his Sharingan here...
But I need to get him to use
a large amount of Chakra at any cost.
Shall I take care of her in
one hit with Chidori? Or...
In this situation, maybe I should...
As I thought... He's trying to save
some Chakra for Gaara.
Ninja Art: Wind Scythe Jutsu!
Don't underestimate me!
Ninja Art: Sand Storm!
Darn! I have to do something about
that bothersome fan...
Humph... I wonder how long
you'll last with such a way of fighting.
It can't be helped...
It looks like you've finally
gotten serious, eh?
Fire Style: Phoenix Flower Jutsu!
That's the stuff!
Aim with precision!
Fire Style: Fireball Jutsu!
Did I get her?
Wind Scythe Jutsu!
I've got you.
Oh no!
Now!
You're mine!
Good!
W-What?! Substitution?!
Oh no!
Sorry, but I don't have the time
to be dealing with you forever!
D-Dang it...
G-Gaara, at any cost...
What's that?!
What the heck is going on?
Who the heck is that youth?
Who on earth are you?!
Is it so sudden you can't tell?
It's me. Orochimaru.
It can't be... Have you completed
that Forbidden Jutsu?
I struggled for decades...
after leaving the village.
You're a truly frightening,
inhuman monster!
So, he did it, huh...?
The reason I couldn't select you
to be the Fourth Hokage...
is because of that distorted
consciousness.
I've finally been found out, eh...?
It's too bad.
Orochimaru...
What's the meaning of this?!
Here I'd set that
many booby traps...
so I was quite surprised.
But I see... So it was you.
Recently, there has been a steady stream
of people going missing from the village,
from Genin to Chunin,
and even Anbu Black Ops members.
There was also information that
you had been acting strange...
Master Orochimaru...
Why did a Shinobi of your rank
do such a thing?
Shall I kill you, too?
Orochimaru! Sure enough,
this was your doing...?
Say it! What were you doing here?!
Alas! I've been found out.
There's no point in acting cute...
It's for Jutsu development!
Orochi... You!
For that purpose, you did this
to fellow Shinobi...?!
As I thought, Forbidden Jutsu, eh...
What is it that you want?
I want everything!
Everything, you say?!
Get every Jutsu and understand
all of the truths of this world!
The one who first mixed
blue and yellow
named the new color made
in that way, green.
I just want to do the same thing.
If blue is Chakra, yellow is a Sign...
and green is a Jutsu.
In the same way that there
are no limits to the kinds of colors,
there are probably also tens
of thousands of Jutsu in this world...
But in order to get any
and all of the Jutsu...
as well as the truths,
a long time is necessary.
It's the one who takes those
long years to know everything,
who can suitably be called
the ultimate individual.
For me, the life span of
the body is too short.
Too fleeting.
Even if I were to be called the Hokage,
if I die, it all ends there.
Orochimaru... Could it be that
the Jutsu you're testing here is...
Right... It sure could be...
Immortality Jutsu!
Immortality Jutsu is a technique of
eternally pooling one's own
spirits into this earth...
In other words,
it's a Revival Jutsu where...
you find a new body, put your own spirit
into that body and take it over.
I assumed my old form until now,
so that you would feel nostalgic
about our reunion...
Aging is an empty thing, isn't it?
I feel that keenly when I look at you.
You'll die here...
and I'll get a younger,
more beautiful and stronger body...
The Leaf truly lets me have my fill of fun...
I get it...
You want Sasuke Uchiha, eh?!
Right... Exactly... Sasuke.
A Reviving Jutsu where
someone else's body is stolen
and the spirit is immortalized, huh?
How many faces and bodies
have you gone through?!
Two, I think...
I plan to take Sasuke over after
raising him a little more to my liking.
But after all, in order to make you regret
your very own life...
and curse destiny as you die...
...perhaps this face is better?
You monster!
Lord Hokage!
Don't lower your guard, Sensei!
You're always too soft...
What's been wrong with you?
This isn't like you!
I'm sorry...
Eyes...
Eyes with malice and ambition
concealed in them...
I had noticed that
you had such tendencies.
I had noticed,
but pretended not to know.
It was still during the war-torn era.
A genius who brimmed
over strongly with ability...
Nothing less than a phenomenon
that comes once in several decades.
So I wanted to think that
you would carry on
my own will and power.
That softness on my part...
created the conditions of that time
as well as now!
Are you going to...kill me?
Ninja Art: Summoning Jutsu!
I wonder if you can...
Sarutobi Sensei!
Kill him, Sarutobi!
Now's your only chance!
Sarutobi... You...
I couldn't kill him...
I'll bury you and correct
my old mistakes, now!
Here I go!
It's too late!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
No way!
Why the Shadow Clone Jutsu?!
To disperse the little Chakra
he has left...!
You've gotten old, after all...
To think you'd shorten your
own life span out of impatience...
D-Don't tell me, you...?!
Mi, I, Hitsuji, U, Inu, Ne, Tori, Uma, Mi...
This order of Signs...
I knew it, Sarutobi,
you are using that Jutsu!
So this is the Grim Reaper
the Fourth Hokage was talking about,
which only the one who has signed
a contract with this Jutsu can see, eh?!
Whatever you do now, it's too late...
I've won.
The Leaf Village will crumble!
The Village Hidden in the Leaves
is the home where I live.
The Hokage exists as the pillar
to protect that home!
The Hokage is the one who inherits
and is entrusted the will of the Leaf.
I won't go easily!
Genjutsu! Infinite Darkness Jutsu!
Stupid nonsense...
You're merely a temporal head
in the history of the organization
called the Leaf Village...
Even the face rock that is left
will eventually weather and decay.
Humph... Leaf Village is
not just an organization to me!
In the Leaf Village,
every year many Shinobi
are born and raised...
and live and fight...
and die to protect the village.
The people of this village...
even if they don't have blood ties...
To me, they are precious...
precious...
family!
Then I shall smash you, the pillar,
and destroy the Leaf home.
Humph! Even if you kill me,
that pillar will not break!
I am the man who carried on the Leaf Will
of the First and Second Hokages...
The Third Hokage!
No matter how much you target
this Village Hidden in the Leaves...
A new Hokage will carry on my will,
shall become a pillar and defend the Leaf!
Right, Fourth Hokage?
Orochimaru! Now I will perform
an ace Jutsu that even you don't know!
Behold! Sealing Jutsu!
Reaper Death Seal!
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Yes, breathe in the air
Lift your face to the sky and jump
If it rains, take a break
Go where the wind takes you
So many regrets
Don't let this scar be for naught
Let's go carve the badges in our chest
Yes, it's Show Time, life begins now.
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Transform sadness into the wind
and continue to forge on
Forge on strong
Every year in this village,
Shinobi are born, nurtured,
and fight for the sake of the village.
They live to protect the village and
things that are precious to them.
Even if they aren't related to me,
they are my precious family.
I won't let you have your way
with my family!
Next time: "Forbidden Secret Technique:
Reaper Death Seal!"