Press down hard on the gas
That's right, there's no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We're speeding through life,
squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you're not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we'll go far off into the distance.
There is no way that I alone can
lose in a place like this!
Guy Sensei...please allow it.
It is now...
A time to carry through and protect
one's own Way of the Ninja!
The Fifth Gate: A Splendid Ninja is Born
The color of his body changed...!
He's red...?!
What's up with him...?!
He's opened the third gate,
the Gate of Life...
He's going to make his move!
No, not yet!
What?!
And also,
the fourth gate,
the Gate of Pain...open!
What an incredible guy...
It's not as though effort alone
can make this happen...
That boy...
is he in fact a genius...?
He's fast!
Gaara!
Where are they?!
He's above!
But we can't find Lee!
Where?!
The sand isn't keeping up at all!
So it's the Sand Armor again...?
Then how's this?!
What...?!
This Sand Armor is...
being peeled away...!
You're a stubborn one.
Since it comes to this...
The muscles have torn...
Is that really Lee...?
When did he become like this...?
This is the end!
The Fifth Gate of Closing...open!
I can't defend myself...
Is this the movement of
a human being?!
Neji...
This technique is my ace in
the hole to take you down...
but I will specially show it to you!
Huh?!
The Sand Shield can't keep up!
Most of the armor has also
been peeled off...
He's done for!
W-Wow!
Hidden Lotus... In other words...
it's a high-speed continuous
Taijutsu that can't even be touched!
The answer to take Neji down is
that high speed combination...
There is no way that
the sand can keep up!
This technique will be the last!
Hidden Lotus!
I can't see anything, it's too fast...
That's impossible...
The gourd has turned to sand...?
He's done it this time!
Gaara!
Lee...
Oh!
What's...that?
He protects himself...
using a gourd made of sand?!
That technique is...!
Sand Coffin!
No way!
He got hit by the Hidden Lotus
and is still able to bring
forth a technique...!
Sand Coffin!
I just can not lose in a place like this...
I want to...
my Way of the Ninja...
Oh no!
Die!
Why...?
Why...save him?
He's...
I'm all right!
I'm strong so...
The Chunin Exam...
Guy Sensei, please watch
me with a smile...
I'd like to prove that I could
become a respectable Ninja
even though I can't use Ninjutsu!
That would be the ultimate for me!
He is...
an important subordinate
whom I care for!
A subordinate...whom I care for...?
Those words are definitely
not understandable to Gaara...
I quit...
He quit...?
The moment Guy jumped in,
Lee lost.
The winner...
Gaa-!
– Wha...?
– Huh?
Wha...?!
That's impossible...
Having opened the fifth gate...
And his hand and feet are crushed...
There's no way he should
be able to stand...!
Lee...
It's all right.
It's over!
You're in no condition to stand...!
Lee...
Y-You...
You are...
Even after having
lost consciousness...
You still want to prove your
own Way of the Ninja...?
So he had already...
lost consciousness...
Lee...
You're already...
a respectable Ninja...!
The winner...
Gaara.
Lee!
Stop!
Even if you went down
what could you do?
Your words of encouragement
would only make him feel worse.
There's no way he could
have beaten Gaara...
He was faced with a tougher battle
than we thought...
That Naruto...
Bushy Brow lost
to a guy like this...!
Medics, please hurry.
Bushy Brow...
Lee...
You are the Jonin in charge of him,
aren't you?
Y-Yes.
Please come with me
for a minute.
Careful...
Don't shake him.
There is faint breathing...
but because of comminuted fractures
and muscle tears to his entire body,
recovery will likely to take
quite some time...
If that was all, it wouldn't be so bad, but...
The damage to the left arm
and leg which received the attack is severe...
It's too severe...
Oh...!
I don't want to say this,
but he won't be able to...
live as a Shinobi again.
T-That...
that can't be true...
I will take Bushy Brow down.
Believe it!
It is not you whom I want to fight,
it's Uchiha!
You...!
Naruto, I get where you're
coming from, believe me.
But all fighting must be done
officially in a match!
The failure beats the gifted genius
through sheer effort...
Wouldn't that make for
an exciting main battle?
Though, I am probably going
to be the one fighting Neji...
Lee...
I didn't want to think...that you'd lose.
I wanted to let you fulfill...
your Way of the Ninja!
Yay!
I finally mastered it!
Yahoo!
This technique...
after all, only Lee managed to master...
Okay, you became Genin
from today.
I want to hear what it is
you all are aiming for!
I-I'd like to prove that I can become
a respectable Ninja
even though I can't use
Ninjutsu or Genjutsu!
That would be the ultimate for me!
Please forgive me for not...
stopping it...!
Lee...
It's not true...it's not true.
After hearing that,
what should Bushy Brow do...?!
This guy...
He said the failure would take
down a genius with effort...!
Isn't there something that
can be done?!
Calm down, Naruto.
B-But...Kakashi Sensei!
He kept saying he wanted
to battle Sasuke and Neji!
Perhaps...that led to his ruin.
To fulfill that dream...
the boy even used a self-sacrificing
forbidden technique to try to win!
The result is what you see...
That boy...
Sasuke and Neji...
and you...
he sacrificed himself to
a promise he never spoke of.
He risked his life...
so that he might have
a chance to battle you guys...
Don't forget that...
I wonder if Lee...
will be all right...?
Lee...
You didn't realize it even at the end...
Heaven does not allow it.
One who tries to move ahead
while achieving victory
through a method like dying
upon each other's swords.
So it ended without incident...
Welcome back Gaara.
Guy...
Well...
I spoke self-importantly earlier but...
I've thought about it and
had I been in your position...
I probably...wouldn't have
been able to stop him.
Guy.
We're in the way of the
next tournament...let's go up.
All right...
Then, the tenth and final round is next,
both contestants come forward!
So it's finally my turn...
I'm gonna win and have
some barbecued beef!
In any case, I need to last until
the main tournament and battle Sasuke.
Or I will not have met your expectations,
Lord Orochimaru...
I can almost see through it...
The reason that you went to the trouble
of getting to Sasuke before us and...
putting a Curse Mark on him
without killing him...
In other words,
we were the guinea pigs to measure
Sasuke's abilities
during the examinations.
What you wanted isn't Sasuke's life,
but Sasuke himself...
I was also taken for a fool...
Now, let the tenth round begin.
Hey, can you hear it?
The clear,
blue sky goes on and on
The ocean
spans limitlessly
Please keep that smile
on your face forever
Or else I'll cry
You won't have to search around you
It's all ok now.
Everyone is inside
this hand
when you want to cry,
and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born, and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia, feel the telepathy
Hey, can you hear it?
Sakura!
Do you know where
Kakashi Sensei is?
Naruto...
I'm gonna have him watch
my training until the main tournament.
Kakashi Sensei is probably with Sasuke.
What's up with you, Sakura?
You seem a little down.
No, nothing...
It's just that I get this bad feeling...
Next episode: "A Shadow in Darkness:
Danger Approaches Sasuke"
I feel uneasy for some reason...