C'mon!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
It looks like you've got some time
to kill there all by yourself.
What happened to the blond boy
and that stuck-up boy?
They're in the middle of
the tree-climbing training.
You don't have to do that?
I'm exceptional, so Kakashi Sensei
told me to guard you.
Really?
What?!
You got a minute, Tazuna?
Huh? What's up, Giichi?
Uh, actually...
I gave it a lot of thought.
Building this bridge...
will you let me quit?
Why so suddenly? Not you too?!
Tazuna, I've had a bond
with you from the old days.
I'd like to cooperate,
but if we push it too far,
Gato will set his sights on us, too.
Also...if you get killed,
everything is lost!
Why don't you just
stop building the bridge?
Not a chance...
This is our bridge.
This is the bridge that
everyone in town has built
believing that it would generate
distribution and transportation
for this poor Land of Waves
that has few resources.
But if it goes so far as
to take our lives...
It's already afternoon...
Let's call it a day.
Tazuna!
Giichi...you don't have to
come back tomorrow.
The Land Where a Hero Once Lived
Damn it!
What the heck is up with this?
I won't lose to you!
Say, where are we going?
I was asked to get some ingredients
for dinner on the way home...
WILL DO ANY KIND OF WORK
Thief!
What's up with...this town...?
We're here...
Welcome...
There's hardly anything here...
You pervert!!
You're...wrong...
Man, I was really surprised earlier.
What's going on with this town?!
Again?
Hey, you...
What...?
Gimme some!
Oh... Here...
Yaaay!
Thank you.
This is how it's been ever
since Gato showed up.
Here, all the adults
have turned into cowards.
So that's why now
that bridge is necessary...
It's a symbol of bravery...
in order to restore their spirit,
so they don't keep running away...
For the people of this land...
who have set their minds
on remaining passive...
If we can just... complete that bridge...
this town will return to how it once was...
and everyone will come back.
Sasuke...Naruto...
Damn it! Damn it!
Are you telling me that
Sasuke's still climbing?!
Darn it... He's gradually catching up...
Darn it! No! No!
If I let myself get distracted by Sasuke,
my concentration will be disturbed!
Hey Sakura, can you give me some tips?
Huh?
Without telling Sasuke, okay, okay?
Listen. Chakra uses spiritual energy,
so you mustn't get too strained or frantic.
Relax and concentrate on the tree
so that you can constantly accumulate
a fixed amount of Chakra
in the bottom of your feet.
Concentrate! Concentrate!
Okay. I'm getting good vibes, I say!
Okay! This is it!
Hey...Naruto!
Jeez, what the heck's wrong with you?!
Don't interfere while
I'm trying to concentrate!
U...Uh...Well...
W-What is it?!
I'm not used to him speaking to me first...
Y-You asked Sakura to give
you some tips before...
What did she say to you...?
I'm not telling!
Man... This is really fun!
It's been a long time since we've had
a meal with this many people!
Seconds please!
Stop eating if you're going to vomit!
No, I'll eat.
I have to eat even if it means enduring.
I have to get strong
as quickly as possible, so...
Yes-yes!
But vomiting is different.
Excuse me, why is there
a torn picture hanging here?
Inari was looking at this
all through dinner.
This torn part looks like someone who was
in the picture was deliberately torn off.
It's my husband...
He's a man who was
once called a hero of this town...
Inari! Where are you going...?
Dad!
I'm always telling you not to
talk about that person in front of Inari...!
What're you saying happened with Inari?
It appears there's
some kind of good reason.
Inari had a father not related by blood...
It was like they were a real father
and son who got along really well...
Back then, Inari was a child
who laughed all the time...
However...
Inari has changed...
ever since that incident with his father.
The word bravery was eternally taken
from the people of this island
and from Inari...
With that day,
that incident, as the trigger.
That incident? What happened to Inari?
To explain the incident, I must first...
tell you about the man
who was called the hero of this land.
Hero...?
It was around three years ago...
when Inari met the man...
Potchi!! Potchi!!
Wrong! His name's Shooting Star...
As of today, he's my dog!
He's not Shooting Star!
He's my Potchi! Give him back!
Potchi's my friend!
Who's going to give him
to the likes of you?!
Shut up!
Potchi!!
That's cuz you wouldn't
hand him over quietly...
Now I couldn't care less about that dog!
Hey, let him go!
What have you done?!
Are you trying to kill Potchi?!
Heh! He's your special mutt, right?
Then save him, quick.
What's the matter...?
Is it okay with you if he dies?!
Of course I'm not okay with him dying!
He's my only friend!
– But...
– Look. He can't even dog paddle
– even though he's a dog!
– But...
I'm sorry, Potchi... I can't swim...
Hey! If you're his owner,
dive in after him!
This is bad, Akane.
What if he can't swim...?
S-Save me...!
Leave him be.
B-But...
Then why don't you go
save him if you like?
I-I don't want to die... Somebody save me...!
P-Potchi!
Potchi!
I'm gonna digress, but...
Potchi learned how to dog paddle then.
Potchi!
Shooting Star escaped. Get him!
Ohhh...I can't breathe... This...is it...
Are you awake, boy?
I gave those kids a good scolding.
Here, eat!
Is this God? Oh...
Did you...save me?
Just eat! Start with that.
I see. You were betrayed by your dog, too...
In my country, dogs are creatures
that have a keen sense of loyalty...
Well, you betrayed your dog's trust first,
so there's nothing you can do about that.
I was scared and couldn't move.
I wanted to save him...
But...I have no guts, so...
That's right.
Of course a kid your age would be scared.
But you know...boy.
Just remember this.
Huh?
If you're a man choose
a lifestyle you won't regret...
For things I truly hold dear to myself,
I'll protect them until the very end
with both these arms.
Even if it's tough, or sad,
I'll stick it out...
even if it looks like
I might lose my life!
His name was Kaiza and
he was a fisherman who'd come to this land
from another country in search of his dreams.
After that, Inari really took to Kaiza.
It may have been because Inari
had lost his real father
when he was too young
to remember anything.
But he was very attached to Kaiza.
They were like father and son...
It didn't take long for Kaiza to become...
a member of the family.
And he was a man this town needed.
We...we've got trouble, Kaiza!
The river dam has broken from this rain!
At this rate, District D will be consumed!
What?!
Dad!
Inari, go out back and get some rope!
Okay!
Its no good!
The only thing we can do is
to attach a rope and pull...
Don't talk nonsense!
How are we going to attach a rope?!
We'd die if we were to go
into such a furious current!
But if we drag our feet,
District D will be annihilated!
What should we do...?
I'll do it.
Kaiza!
Don't be foolish!
Even you wouldn't be able to!
Dad!
Don't worry...
Your dad's unmatched.
Your dad loves the town
you're from, so...
For things I truly hold dear to myself...
Even if I lose my life...
I'll protect them to the end...
with both these arms!
Dad, hang in there!
He did it! The rope...the rope's attached!
Okay, everybody pull!
Yeah!
From then on...the people of this land
called Kaiza a hero.
And he became a father
that Inari could be proud of.
It was around that time when Gato
set his sights on this land.
And then, one night...
I heard...
That you're going to protect
this town with those arms...
I dare you to!
Listen up!
This man resisted through force,
the policies of the Gato corporation
and disturbed the order of this nation.
Therefore, he will now be executed!
I just hope that such trivial matters
will never occur again.
Dad!
Stop, Inari...
Do it...
Dad...
Dad!
Didn't you tell me...?
That you'd...protect...
me and the people of this land...
with both your arms...?
Dad, you liar...
Ever since then, Inari has changed...
as well as Tsunami... and the townspeople...
Hero, that's just stupid.
There's no such thing!
What're you doing, Naruto...?
You've had enough training for today.
You've built up too much Chakra.
You'll die if you move any more than that.
I'll prove it.
Prove what?
I'll prove that...
there are heroes...
in this world!
Huh? What do you want, lady?
As for me, I'm training right now.
Cuz we don't know when
Zabuza will strike next..
Getting strong for someone special
is something I understand very well.
So I'm going to get stronger and stronger.
I'll show Inari that there are heroes
in this world.
Next time:
"Battle on the Bridge! Zabuza Returns!"
As for me, I'm going to
kick butt once again!