I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long way to go
on that road.
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that...
What were you gazing at?
– Where...
– Where...am I?
Remembrance: The Lost Page
All right! I'm up for it today again,
believe it!
However... There haven't been
any flashy missions around here lately.
C'mon! It's unbelievable, right?!
Yeah well...
Lately, I'm dead tired from doing
nothing but training.
Sakura!
Naruto!
There's someone who got
too much time on his hands!
What's that?! Speak for yourself.
No matter how I look at it,
you are just helping the shop.
What happened to Shikamaru
and Choji?
On a mission with Asuma Sensei!
Oh, I wanted to go on a mission too!
While Ino was down with a cold,
everyone went on urgent missions.
And now I'm completely recovered!
What am I going to do with
all my fighting spirit?
Why don't you use that fighting spirit
in some training?
That's what you think!
In my family, if you don't have
a training partner,
then they make up some reason
for you to help out with the shop!
They must know that if you're alone
you'll skip training, eh?
H-Hey! Don't say something that
could hurt a person's reputation!
I do it properly by myself.
Naruto...
Stop it, Shino! Don't surprise me!
Naruto Uzumaki... Yamanaka Ino...
The Hokage is asking
for both of you.
What? Me too?
By the way, I've also been ordered to go,
along with you guys.
Ino... me and Shino?
Huh?
Demon of Ocean causing disturbance...?
Yes, literally a demon in the ocean.
It seems to be the cause of the disturbance
happening in the remote Land of Sea...
What's wrong...?
You'll go for me, won't you?
Of course.
Shizune...
Y-Yes!
Explain...
As you can see,
the Land of Sea is made up of
a group of islands of various sizes.
Recently in that area, their only means
of transportation, ships,
are being attacked and robbed
of money and valuables.
The people on the boat who
were victimized
unanimously claim that the damage
was done by the "Demon of the Ocean."
And exterminating this Demon
of the Ocean is the mission?
Well... more or less, yes.
But there's more.
The Land of Sea does not have
a hidden village of its own,
so they're prepared for contingencies
through military cooperation with
the neighboring country, the Land of Water,
and have been paying them
a retainer every month...
However, the other day,
one of their ships that collects funds
was attacked by
the Demon of the Ocean as well...
I see. To preserve their relationship
with Land of Water,
Land of Sea will do anything
to protect the next ship.
Yes... This mission is to guard
the ships collecting funds
and destroy the Demon of the Ocean...
I've got a few people to work under you,
so I'm counting on you.
Work under me...?
Enter!
The Chunin Exam's...
Th-That scary proctor!
Oh, you're bringing back memories..!
A-Anko Mitarashi Sensei?
Why are you here?
– Everyone!
– Yes!
I'm pronouncing your mission!
Shino Aburame!
Ino Yamanaka! Naruto Uzumaki!
The three of you will work under Anko
and accompany her on a mission!
What?! These members?
The team is pretty disjointed, isn't it?!
No use talking about it!
Listen... I've thought through
the matter and
I believe that this combination is
the most qualified for this mission...
All of you display your own capabilities
to the full extent and execute this mission!
– Yes!
She just gathered the available Genin...
Really, she is such a...
Still, something doesn't feel quite right...
Yeah, yeah, no complaints about
a mission that's settled!
Ouuch... I got it!
Okay, we'll depart right away!
Everyone prepare and assemble
at the front gate!
– Roger!
Oh, ouch!
Anko...
Be careful...
Yes...
Characteristics of
the Demon of the Ocean...
It's like a fish, like a person...
What is this?!
Huh, someone's eyes are playing tricks.
Something like that can't exist!
Not true, it's possible that Ex-Ninja
become pirates
and use Transformation and Genjutsu.
Well, whatever, if we don't gather
information, there will be no solution.
Right...
Mother Island is the biggest island
at the center of Land of Sea...
We'll go to a nearby fishing port
and cross over by boat!
– I understand!
Yeah! Let's depart for the Land of Sea!
This guy is always hyper...
I'm anxious about what's going to happen.
Here you are...
Um... Lady Tsunade...
It's about...Anko Mitarashi just now...
Did, uh...
Did something happen in the past?
Sort of...
Oh? This is...
Her record of missions from about
the age of ten is pretty sporadic.
Because Anko was under Orochimaru...
So the parts that are blacked out
are combined
with Orochimaru's movements...
and in the confidential file?
Part of them are...
Huh?
There are some parts
that aren't recorded...
That's the truth.
No record?! Even though
Anko herself was in the village?
That Orochimaru...
It seems he really didn't
want to be traced...
When he left the village...
He erased part of Anko's memories.
The wind is salty...
Coming this far, we can already
see over the Land of Sea.
Then, that must be the Mother Island?
What? What is this feeling?
Everyone... Sorry but...
Go ahead and take care
of the arrangements for the boat.
What? But, what would you do, Sensei?
I'll take care of some business
and join you... See you!
Oh! Sensei?!
C'mon, it can't be helped...
What are you doing, Shino?
We'll leave you behind!
Yeah...
The Curse Mark aches.
This presence... No question about it.
This way?
I can say their names
without a problem!
Um... That's Mother Island...
These are Taro Island and Jiro island.
And... That there's Demon Island!
Seems you prepared before you came...
I want to become a wiser, stronger
Shinobi like you, Master Orochimaru...
Oh...?
Here.
Sorry, but I can't give you anything
more than this.
What's up...Ino?
Hey, mister!
Aren't you bringing prices down
way too much?
That's high-quality fish, isn't it?
Oh dear...
I'm not price-cutting...
See... Because of that
"Demon of the Ocean" uproar,
customers are completely staying away...
This is the market price around here.
Really? That fish is rarely...
Oh!
What's with her appearance?
Is she injured or something?
No... That girl, she has her reasons.
Well...
She's a female diver from a small town
on the cape of Mother Island...
What?!
Why would a woman diver on
Mother Island transfer islands on purpose?
That's because, the island people
didn't want to do business with her...
That girl...
In the past, she was spirited away...
Spirited away...?
A person suddenly disappears...
is that it?
That's right! In the past,
a lot of island people disappeared
from being spirited away.
The story is that out of all those people
that girl was the only one
who suddenly returned one day.
Hey, hey!
It's a little village...
So everyone felt creepy.
They say that now, she lives alone
outside of the village...
I see... I feel sorry for her.
With her appearance...
And then you hear things, I too...
feel a little bit creepy...
That's true.
Hey, where's Naruto?
I don't know...
Hey! What are you guys doing?!
Oh no!
Hey, are you okay?
Yes...
You're uh... You're from a place called
Mother Island, aren't you?
Uh... Nothing...
Ninja...
Oh, I'll help!
That's okay...
Huh...? H-Hey... Wait.
What the...?
It's too bad but, the last boat from
the port has already left.
But the sun hasn't even set yet...
Around here, there's nobody who
will take you across in the early evening...
Sorry, but come back tomorrow.
No way...
Well, is there a way to get to
Mother Island besides the ferry?
Mmm, I can't really advise it, but...
If it's necessary,
I'll let you borrow my little boat.
Hey! I was looking all over for you guys!
C'mon! Where were you?!
Sorry, sorry...
You should at least say something
before you disappear.
You and Sensei are exactly alike,
suddenly going someplace.
Feels like there'll be
a bumpy road ahead.
What?! That's rude.
Placing me in the same category together
with that unreasonable sensei...!
Who's what?
S-Sorry.
This sensei... is dangerous, after all...
Good work procuring the boat!
S-Sensei... Where in the world
have you been all this time?
Oh, something like
gathering information...
Well, let's go!
The Shinobi of Leaf Village are here...
Land of Sea must have
pleaded with them
to investigate on
the "Demon of the Ocean."
Well then, we should give them
the best welcome.
It's getting dark...
We're almost to Mother Island.
All right, all right!
Full speed advance to Mother Island!
Although the sun has already set ...
Where does all your hyper-energy
come from?!
Times like this,
your state of mind is important!
Sakura sure has her share of trouble...
I feel sorry for her.
What the...!
I ran up against a rock or something!
Hang in there, Naruto!
Hey, all of you look forward, front!
Dodge it, quick!
You say that, but...
It's no good, the oar won't move!
I'll help!
You...!
Striking Shadow Snake!
Naruto! Leave it!
I understand!
To show themself so soon...
That was close...
The two of you be careful!
He's aiming at us from underwater!
Dammit!
Demon of the Ocean or whatever,
an underwater creature for
an underwater battle!
Summoning Jutsu!
I'm counting on you... Chief Toad!
What?!
Hey! Naruto!
What kind of place did you call me to?!
Why did you come out!
You stupid frog!
Oh! Hey, wait!
Summoning Jutsu.
Please come out, Chief Toad!
Hey, good evening!
It can't be!
I have been calling for Chief Toad!
Stupid! If you summoned
the old man to a place like this,
terrible things would happen.
Huh? Why?
We're freshwater creatures!
We don't go with saltwater!
I don't like salty things either.
You're no help at all!
Shino! Take care of Ino...
Okay!
All right!
Fire Style: Dragon Flame Jutsu!
Water Clone?!
You let your guard down!
You did too!
Take that!
There was one more?!
What the...? My body strength is...!
How is it?
My improved skill of Chakra Suction?
What's happening?!
Where did he go? Damn it!
My visibility is too bad...
Hey, pull yourself together, Naruto!
Big Brother, it itches.
Ah, I'm at my limit, too...
B-Big Brother!
This is not so good.
Naruto!
What happened?
You two are?!
I'll discharge all the Chakra
I absorbed at once...
Water Style: Furious Current Jutsu!
Shoot! I can't approach them
so easily with this.
Naruto...
I can't stand this!
The wind blows, Ah...
The pain,
The memories won't disappear
What should be brought along?
Assemble them into a piece.
There is no second chance, never
How foolish it is to throw away
Acting so innocently, Ah...
The images.
It probably will not end
Burn that love-filled heart,
Sail across a thousand dreams
Running freely
To take hold of the world in hand
The clouds scatter
The sun sets yet again
The solo parade begins to move.
Adventure, Lucky Day, Heart Beat, Rising,
Decisive, Encounter, Life, Mutual Love
To think the departure of
the collection ship
would be moved up
at the time like this.
It can't be helped.
We've got to find Naruto somehow
by tomorrow morning.
I hope we pick up some information about
the Demon of the Ocean along the way.
The search range is quite expansive, huh?
It'd be best to split up.
Then I'll go from the south,
you guys take the north.
– Roger!
Think about what happened yesterday.
Each of you, tackle this with care. Scatter!
Next time: "The Closed Door"