Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
Are you really happy
when you're always meeting
to someone's expectations?
Even if you change to
who you really wanna be
Will you always have a great smile?
Dreaming of only "the beginning,"
I wake up
and someday,
I'll live on my own.
Yes, precious things
are never in shape
You never know what it is
when you get it or lose it
Yeah, turn your sadness into kindness,
your uniqueness into strength
Even if you get lost,
let's start walking
One more time
Sasuke's Decision:
Pushed to the Edge!
There you are!
I'm here!
I'm returning them to you!
So it's a clone...
Bastard!
Sasuke...Uchiha...!
Why won't you come at me?!
Why...
do you flee?!
Ready?
Over here!
Wait!
Pass!
Here! Good one!
Good! Go! Go! Go!
Power shot!
What're we gonna do?
We don't know any wall-climbing
techniques or anything...
Y-You're...
This...
It's Gaara...
Gaara of Sand...
R-Run!
Wait!
Don't leave me alone!
Help me!
I don't...
want to be alone anymore!
Really...
No!
Gaara! Please calm down!
Yashamaru...
No escape!
I won't let you escape!
Sasuke Uchiha!
You've gotta be kidding!
What's with that outrageous strength...?
Are you afraid of me?
It's too overwhelming...
Sasuke Uchiha!
Are you afraid?
Are you afraid of my existence?!
Don't forget...
You are my prey.
Wait!
Why are you fixated
on me so much?
Those eyes that know true loneliness...
And eyes that know that
it is the world's greatest suffering...
I think I told you.
That you have the same eyes as me.
Eyes that lust for power,
overflowing with hatred
and murderous intent...
The same as me...
Eyes that burn to kill those
who drove you...
into a hell called loneliness!
Such are your eyes.
Okay. Just a minute.
So you're called Gaara...
I don't know what you know
about Sasuke, but...
It's not good for you to
speak as though
you perceive everything about Sasuke!
What is it that you want to say
to him before the final round,
by pursuing him so far?
A battle is where...
another's existence and one's own
existence are put on the line...
and each tries to kill the other!
Only the winner can actually feel
the value of his own existence.
In other words,
what you want to say is...
let's have a killing bout and
not a match?
Uchiha... You really should
be wanting it, too...
in the depths of your soul...
You want to confirm
the value of your existence.
Am I really, truly powerful?
Is my existence more powerful
than my opponent
who faces me with eyes
filled with intent to kill?
What's the matter?!
Sasuke Uchiha!
Are you afraid of me?!
Your hatred and intent to kill...
have they given way to fear?
Is that the extent of your existence?!
Fight me...and confirm it!
Your value! Your existence!
Experience it!
If you want an answer...
Come at me!
I was allowed to live...
Only...myself.
Expressly for what reason?!
No... I know the reason.
The reason that man left me alive
was so he wouldn't be tormented
by a sense of guilt for having killed
an entire clan...
Itachi chose me as the avenger...
in order to have me kill him!
Now, let me have some fun...
Sasuke Uchiha!
I'll finish it with one blow!
Hurry up and die,
release yourself from your misery.
You silly old fool...
I believe I told you...
that you would die too!
Bastard!
Let go, you old fool!
I will not let go!
I refuse to let go...
until I have pulled out your soul!
At this rate...
Gaara!
Looks like it worked...
I see! That's what it was!
That's not possible...
He countered Gaara's attack
in that condition?!
I just realized the reason...
why it's so fun!
This pain...
To take down an opponent
who wounded me...
and thoroughly destroy him...!
That will make me truly feel alive!
Gaara's never had a single wound,
but he got Gaara twice.
Is he...a freak?!
No...a true freak is...
After all, the only thing Gaara is
transforming is still just his right arm.
More, more!
What?!
What the heck is this guy?!
One after another...
Here goes!
He's even faster!
I can't dodge unless
I read ahead of his movements.
If I didn't have these eyes
I'd have died long ago.
I can no longer use Chidori...
Fire Style...
Fire Ball Jutsu!
So the Fire Style doesn't
work against sand...
Not only that,
this level of Jutsu won't...
Die!
Apparently...it needs to be Chidori!
Well! Your limit is two shots.
That's about it...
This is as many Chidori
you can shoot in one day
with your present Chakra.
After all, this Chidori is a technique
that can only be used
in conjunction with Sharingan
during actual battles.
But using Sharingan and
another Jutsu simultaneously means
exploding and using up the Chakra
in your body all at once.
Well! But you really are
one of the more impressive ones.
Even with my Chidori...
If I use the Lightning Blade
four times in a day,
I'd completely use up my Chakra.
What would happen if I tried
to use more than two shots?
The third shot won't be activated...
Remember this well!
If you try to force a Jutsu to activate...
not only will the Jutsu
not properly activate,
but your Chakra will deplete to zero...
And in the worst case, you'll die!
Even if you were to survive,
absolutely nothing good will come of it.
Especially in your case.
What's the matter?
Does the value of your existence
amount to only this much?
I'll be blunt...
You are...weak!
You're too optimistic.
And it's because your hatred
is weak!
The power of hatred is
the power of the intent to kill!
The power of the intent to kill
is the power of revenge!
Your hatred is weaker than mine!
Shut up...
Do you understand
the meaning of this?!
Shut up!
That means that you...
You are weaker than me!
Itachi chose me to be the avenger...
to have me kill him!
I am an avenger!
The Curse Mark again...
Darn...! My body...
Sasuke!
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Yes, breathe in the air
Lift your face to the sky and jump
If it rains, take a break
Go where the wind takes you
So many regrets
Don't let this scar be for naught
Let's go carve the badges in our chest
Yes, it's Show Time, life begins now.
Everyone makes mistakes
It's nothing to be ashamed about
Don't let this scar be for naught
Walk with a smile
Transform sadness into the wind
and continue to forge on
Forge on strong
Hey Yashamaru,
what does pain feel like?
I don't know because
I've never been injured...
I was wondering what it's like.
Could it be that I'm hurt?
I'm not bleeding, but my chest's
felt weird for a long time.
It feels stifled and it hurts a lot!
Next time:
"Assassin of the Moonlit Night"