Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, "See you..."
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I'm not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
No way...
To think Old Man Hokage would
try to eliminate Yakumo.
No way could that ever happen!
But if by some remote chance,
Kurenai Sensei
accepted such a mission...
it would explain her strange behavior.
No, no way!
No way that could ever happen.
Are you okay, Kurenai Sensei...?
Yes. I feel quite a bit better now
thanks to your first-aid...
Who in the world is
Kurenai Sensei protecting?
It was the Third Hokage who
told her to take custody of Yakumo...
What in the world is her real mission...?
What's going on?!
Th-That's...
Th-The Village Hidden in the Leaves is...
No way...!
Genjutsu or Reality?
It's like the aftermath of
a large war that broke out.
Hinata!
Right...
Byakugan!
There's not a person in the village...
What is this...?
What's going on here?!
Kiba, Hinata...
Is there anything unusual in the area?
No enemy signs anywhere...
Akamaru doesn't sense
the scent of any outsiders, either.
What happened in the village
while we were away...?
First, let's take Yakumo and
Kurenai Sensei to the hospital.
We'll check out the village after that...
R-Right...!
Leaf Hospital
What's this...?
Anyway, let's get these two
to a hospital room...
I'm okay.
More importantly, take care of Yakumo.
Right...
You're out of danger now...
Oh, no...She's unconscious!
Her vital signs are weakening...
I wonder if there's any medicine left...
Naruto, help me look...
Oh, well, but...
Just hurry!
R-Right...
There's no scent of blood.
Everyone must have
evacuated somewhere.
Let's us check out the village.
Right...
Make sure you three
always act together...
Come back here in thirty minutes,
no matter what.
Right...
What is it?
Sure enough, you have to be the one
to give us orders, Kurenai Sensei!
What's been the matter with you?!
The pharmacy is that way.
Nothing. I was just concerned
about Kurenai Sensei...
So let's hurry and get the medicine!
I mean, Kurenai Sensei's going to...
eliminate...Yakumo...
Eliminate?
Th-Th-That couldn't be...
I was just kind of out of it.
Huh?
Huh...? What was that?!
What is it, Sakura?!
There's someone here other than us.
What?!
That's close!
I'll leave the two in
the hospital room to you, Sakura!
I'm going after him!
Got it!
Hold it! Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Huh?! My Jutsu won't activate?!
Wait! This isn't the time
to be fighting.
You guys are the ones who
attacked the mountain cottage, right?!
I am Unkai of the Kurama Clan...
Kurama?!
The same clan as Yakumo?!
Why would her clan attack her?!
Listen to me!
If you don't, everyone will die!
What's this smell of blood?!
Byakugan!
Close your Byakugan, Hinata!
Kiba, restrain Akamaru's
sense of smell!
–What?!
–What is it?!
It's because we're caught
in someone's Jutsu.
Say what?!
Yes. We're now inside
Yakumo's Genjutsu.
It may seem as if the Leaf Village
was in a war.
But this is merely
a part of her Genjutsu.
This whole Leaf Village is Genjutsu
and we've all been trapped in it?
That's totally impossible!
But if her latent powers have awakened,
it wouldn't be hard at all.
This whole village?!
This ground we're standing on,
this sky, everything is Genjutsu?!
There are occasions when
superior senses become a hindrance.
It's because no matter how superior
the sense of sight or smell might be,
ultimately it's the human brain that
processes and perceives the information!
There are times when
well-developed brains make errors
in the process of interpreting
complex electric signals.
However, insects act only
with sharp senses.
Unlike the information processed
with a human brain,
insects narrow this information down
to the very minimum.
Look. My insects
are still under control.
They will not be deceived.
There are occasions when
Yakumo's Genjutsu
summons thunderclouds
and produces fire.
And that is planted directly into
the human brain
as if it had occurred in reality.
And that causes the brain
to hurt one's own body.
Then, Grandma's house...
That's also Yakumo's power?!
It's not just that...
She can even kill people easily
if she were so inclined.
But these tremors...
Are you saying this is also Genjutsu?
You'll see any moment now...
A-A snake!
It's too huge!
Is that also Genjutsu?!
It's a terrifying image that
our cerebrums have created.
Physical influence is absolutely...
unthinkable!
No way!
Yakumo?! Kurenai Sensei?!
Huh?!
Really...? Yakumo can kill people
with Genjutsu..?
So is that why the Third Hokage
tried to eliminate her?
Yakumo, Yakumo?!
Kurenai Sensei, Kurenai Sensei...
Over here... Kurenai Sensei...
I still can't believe it.
To think Yakumo would do
something like that!
Once every several generations,
a child is born into our Kurama Clan
with physical idiosyncrasies.
That child is Yakumo...
Moreover, what's terrifying is her
using her powers unconsciously
without being able to control it.
It's getting kind of hot.
Don't!
What's happening
outside the door...?
Don't open it!
Wh-What's this...?
Why's there lava here...?
That's an illusion our brains have
created due to Yakumo's Genjutsu.
But even it's an illusion,
if we were to dive into the lava,
our brains would determine it to be lava
and our bodies would burn up.
That is Yakumo's power.
So is that why Old Man Hokage
and Kurenai Sensei
tried to eliminate Yakumo?
That's not it.
What they really
attempted to kill
was the monster
existing inside Yakumo.
A monster?
Before too long,
Yakumo's massive powers
created a terrifying monster.
If left alone, the monster that
continues to grow would
someday attempt to
become one with her
by absorbing
Yakumo's consciousness.
The Third Hokage and Kurenai
determined as such
and all there was to do in order
to save Yakumo was to seal her powers.
A monster in her body...
So that's what it was...
I can't just sit back like this!
Oh!
Oh. My entire fortune!
I told you. If you dive into the lava,
you're body will really burn up.
Then does that mean
we can't get out of here?!
No, there is one way.
What's that way?!
If you seal your five senses,
the Genjutsu cannot affect the body.
You must escape from this world
and attack Yakumo!
What?! Attack Yakumo?!
Ow-ow-ow!
What? This is...Satomi Hill?!
Old Man Unkai!
It seems you safely made it
out of Yakumo's Genjutsu...
What the heck happened...?!
At the point you brought Yakumo
out of the mountain cottage,
you were already
caught in her Genjutsu.
What?!
Guys! Get a hold of yourselves!
Kiba!
Shino!
Wh-Where are we...?
Sakura, examine
Old Man Unkai's wounds.
Unkai...?
What happened?!
These are awful burns!
We were able to get out of
Yakumo's Genjutsu
thanks to this old man!
Rather, I'd say
we were driven out...
Her only target was
Yuhi Kurenai, after all...
Where's Kurenai Sensei now?
Well, probably...
Yakumo...
Kurenai Sensei...
What do you think of my paintings...?
Aren't they wonderful?!
What did you do to everyone?
Don't worry...
I just drove out the intruders...
Eventually, I must have my revenge
on the Leaf Village...
But first, I have some business
with you, Sensei.
Why include the Leaf Village as well...?
I should be enough of a target
for your revenge...!
I won't let you say
you don't know!
How is it?
Awesome, huh?
I have complete control now of letting
you live or killing you, Sensei.
Tell me the truth...
It was the Third Hokage who ordered
my father and mother killed and
the Kurama Clan and me eliminated
from the Leaf Village, right?
No.
The Third Hokage did not order
such a mission...
Why do you lie?!
Please.
Tell me the truth!
You'll vanish if you don't,
Kurenai Sensei...
Such a sad child...
If killing me will eliminate your suffering,
then you should do it.
If your hate will vanish along
with your suffering!
Why do you cry?
I won't be deceived by tears like that!
1001, 1002, 1003, 1004, 1005!
Yeah, it feels good in
every kind of weather to sweat.
So the Kurama Clan are still here!
Might Guy will take you on!
W-Wait, Guy!
Huh?! G-Guy?
I see. So you guys were also
caught in the Kurama Genjutsu...
I'm sorry.
Well, you're alive and
that's all that matters.
Thank goodness,
thank goodness.
Oh, you guys are back!
Where are the village reinforcements?!
There's no time to explain!
What?!
Oh, hey! Wait, you guys!
What's up with them?!
Who's that man...?
And what about everyone?
Please, just help me out, Guy Sensei.
But, well...
Just hurry!
R-Right...
Byakugan!
Those jerks...
No, Yakumo!
Yakumo and Kurenai Sensei
are in the innermost room.
All right!
Hey, wait!
Kiba!
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I'm told that
there is no bright future
I'll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Everyone, what's the current situation?
Naruto hasn't come back
since he first went in.
The insects had also detected
something strange and emerged.
Can you use your Byakugan
to look inside?
There's some kind of powerful force
that's getting in the way.
So all we can do is watch here?
Does this mean that all
we can do is believe in him and wait?
Next time:
"The Supposed Sealed Ability"