We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road
filled with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes and
take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose,
so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
Okay! Let's go!
Huh?
"Let's go,"
with so much energy...
Don't act like a little kid!
Oh? You're in a bad mood.
Because! Because!
It's in the middle of my training!
There are three steps
in the training, right?!
I'm only done with the second step!
You can do the third step
even while walking.
What! Really?!
A balloon?
Here!
What's this...? An ordinary balloon?
The first step is "Spin."
The second step is "Power."
And finally, the third step is this.
An Impossible Choice:
The Pain Within Tsunade's Heart
Which one is "this"?!
Watch me, it looks as if
I am simply holding a balloon...
You say it "looks as if,"
but nothing is really happening.
Then, I will do the same thing
on my left hand.
Let's see what's really happening
inside the balloon.
Wow!
The Chakra is randomly spinning
and going faster and faster...
But still, it's perfectly round...
It's almost like...
Like a small typhoon, right?
What's happening in your left hand...
is happening inside that balloon
in your right hand, too?
Yeah! That's right.
Cool...
The balloon isn't moving at all
even if he's spinning that much Chakra...
There's more power than
that time the rubber ball popped,
and it's spinning a lot more too!
Listen, in this third step,
you've got to use 100% of
what you have learned...
and retain them.
In other words, while keeping
the "Spin" and the "Power" at their max,
imagine creating a single layer
within the balloon
and compressing the Chakra within it.
Got it!
So, this training is about keeping
the spin and power that I did
in the second step,
and conversely,
trying not to pop a delicate balloon!
Oh! That's the most perceptive
you've been so far!
Huh?
But, what's the point in going
to all the trouble?!
In short, it means this.
Watch! It's like this up until
the second step of the training.
Next, after you have mastered
the third step!
This is what happens!
If you can keep this small typhoon
the size of your palm,
the force won't disperse.
The spinning gets faster and faster
and the power gets
more and more compressed.
And the destructive power
will reach its max.
Well, so, that's that.
All right! I'll do this, too!
Okay, this feels right...
Now!
Retain it here!
Retain...
No cutting-corners!
You've got to put out 100% spin and power,
and retain them.
You gotta be kidding...
Unless I can perfectly control all my power,
it's impossible!
Now I can see it...
This third step...
It's on a totally different level
compared to the others.
I told you...
With an achievement difficulty of Rank A,
it's a super advanced Ninjutsu.
Well, I'm done explaining!
We'll continue as we go on walking.
Hey, hey!
We don't need to rush so much,
until I can properly...
We have already wasted enough time
waiting for your body to recover.
There's no guarantee that
Tsunade stays in this town much longer.
What?!
But, but...
It's not like an old acquaintance
is going to conveniently pop up
and start talking about
the good old times with her...
Come on, let's go!
All right...
Long time no see...Orochimaru.
I'd looked for you everywhere.
What do you want from me
after so long a time?
You aren't thinking of talking
about the old days...?
Actually, I need to ask you
for a little favor...
His heartbeat is fast...
From that complexion,
he must have a high fever.
He must have been fatigued
for quite some time...
And that arm...
Lady Tsunade.
You must have understood by now.
Go to someone else,
I don't treat anyone any more.
That won't do...
You must know how serious this wound is...
No one can treat this wound.
Except for one of the Legendary "Sannin"
who won her fame as
a medical specialist, Princess Tsunade...
You...
That arm...
it's not an ordinary wound.
A special Sealing Jutsu or something...?
What have you done?
Well, it just happened...
when I killed the Third Hokage.
You... Really?
Humph. Don't look so scary.
Anything that has a form
will one day decay...
Same goes for humans.
You must already know that too.
For you have let two of
your most beloved ones die...
Let two of the most beloved ones die?
I see... He thinks of terrible things.
That was a really terrible way to die...
You!
Poisoned...
She's fast!
Get out of my way!
Won't let you!
Calm down, Shizune!
This attendant...is an expert.
Orochimaru...
Your personality's been like this
for a long time.
And you know my personality
very well...
So stop fooling around with me.
I'll kill you, bastard!
She's powerful...
And so scary...
she definitely must be single.
Tsunade is impatient and short-tempered...
Hey Naruto,
there's no time to be falling.
If we don't hurry,
who knows where that shrew
will disappear again.
Hey you, Pervy Sage!
That's no way to speak to
a hard-working apprentice!
Shut up. Tsunade is the first priority now,
not you.
Well, what the heck!
To have this Pervy Sage come
all the way to meet her...
Who could this Kunoichi Tsunade be?
Hope she's still here...
We didn't come here to fight.
We just want to negotiate with you!
Negotiate?
Yes.
Don't make me laugh!
I've already told you once.
Get out of my sight!
We can't do that.
Get out of my sight.
You are the only one
who can treat Lord Orochimaru's arm.
Get out of my sight.
We're not asking you to do it for free.
Let's make a deal!
I'll count up to five.
Leave before I'm done.
Or else, I'll make you disappear myself.
Please calm down.
It won't be a bad deal for you...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
I'll resurrect the little brother
and man, both of whom you loved...
with the Forbidden Jutsu I've developed.
Since we haven't disappeared yet,
I'm guessing that the deal is made?
Yes. I do know this young lady...
Really?
Yeah.
To win back the money she lost here,
I think she said...
she was going over there.
Spin... Power...
Letting them out to their max
and retain it...
Hey, kid.
Hmm?
Wanna gamble a bit, too?
Over there? Where is that?
Hmm?
See, if the total number of the pips
on these dices
comes out as even numbers,
that's "Cho"
and if it's odd, that's "Han."
Shut up! I am training right now,
don't bug me!
What nonsense!
This is a gambling house.
Instead of that balloon,
let's play with these.
No way! I don't have any time
to be playing with those dice!
Ha, what a boring kid!
Shut up!
So...can you tell me where that is?
Well, you can't expect things to be free
in a gambling house, you know?
Okay...
Let's make a deal.
The information will be free if you win...
And if you lose,
I'll give it to you for 1000 ryo.
All right!
So choose, odd or even!
Okay! Here we go...
Well, so...
since I am exactly 50 years old.
I'll go for...even!
If it's odd, I win...
I'll open it now.
Oh no! 2 and 5, odd!
W-What the heck...?!
1000 ryo...
Nice, Naruto!
Looks like I won...
Darn! It didn't work again!
Retain...
Where shall I look next?
Geez, she's nowhere to be found!
Hm? Me?
Lotto?
Kids, grownups, everyone loves it.
Come and play with
this fun, fun Lotto.
There's one that you know
the result right away.
Which one do you want?
Really, you are so much cuter
being chubby!
I can't believe he won
with just one draw.
He's very talented in this...
though his talent in Jutsu
is still immature.
Well...anyhow...
Where could have Tsunade gone?
She couldn't have gone that far
in this short amount of time.
I guess we'll have to
search for her from a higher place.
If I remember it correctly,
this is a castle town.
If we go up to the castle...
Naruto! This way!
Don't you want to see those two...
Tsunade?
Nawaki...Dan...
If I treat your arms,
what do you intend to do with them?
Well, I don't like to lie...
So, I will tell you the truth.
Hey, hey! Where is the castle?
It's not there...?
In addition to getting what I want...
This time, I will completely destroy
the Leaf Village!
A cycle of hardship, right?
Inside, we were crying, right?
But the one thing we won't give up
is the dream we've chosen, right?
It's a secondary role,
a role in the shadows
But in reaching for that dream,
let us stay centered,
let us stay true
Over and over,
we hung on without giving up
we kept coming back up
Over and over,
we believed
and dreamed
Over and over,
we've seen fools
we've stood in the shadows of others
Now, it's our turn...
Let us bask in our dreams
Hey, enough already!
Who cares if she is one of the Sannin?!
Who cares if she is
the legendary Kunoichi?!
Who cares if she's
the medical specialist?!
There's no way I'll accept
this person as the new Hokage!
If she belittles the Third
and Fourth Hokages...
I don't care if she's the candidate
to be the Fifth Hokage!
I'll kick her butt!
Next time:
"Unforgivable! A Total Lack of Respect!"