Connecting old words
that have been used up
I just want to convey
my simple thoughts
That day's faint wind blows away
at the castle ruins of yesterday
I'll laugh with you
and live for the moment
Still that incident
will continue to trouble you, right?
That's why it must be good-bye
Leaving nothing behind,
let us share what is left
In time, we'll realize
that it was everything
And sadness will touch our cheeks,
creating a river of tears
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex
and melting away
Gentle Fist: 8 Trigrams 64 Palms!
Uh-oh!
8 Trigrams 2 Palms!
4 Palms!
8 Palms!
16 Palms!
32 Palms!
64 Palms!
What's going on?!
A golden body surface...?
It's the same material as the weapon
he spit out of his mouth earlier...
That was close.
I hear that if you're hit straight on
with Gentle Fist,
your Chakra Network gets damaged
and you become unable
to build up Chakra...
That was close.
Are you a monster?
It seems to come
not just from your mouth.
Gum Style Spider Thread...
is a metal that hardens
the instant it leaves my body.
Moreover, it doesn't let Chakra through.
And...
it can be secreted
not just from my mouth,
but also from the sweat glands
throughout my body.
Attacks on Chakra points won't work.
Now it makes sense...
The Spider Web Net won't work.
And there'll be no close-range combat
fighting ̀against a Gentle Fist opponent.
In other words,
I just have to attack the blind side
from long distance.
There'll be no sound...
It'll be in a flash.
The game's over.
The Kunai Knife is a fake!
What?!
8 Trigrams Palm...
Rotation!
Wha–?! What is that?!
Does he...have eyes behind him?!
And the defense just now...
He repelled physical attacks
with Chakra?!
360 Degrees of Vision:
The Byakugan's Blind Spot!
If we're not prepared for
"one person, one kill,"
then it's not going to work out...
That's what you said earlier.
Hurry up and go!
I'll catch up with you all!
We have to be prepared for
"one person, one kill."
Naruto...
You've got better eyes than me.
Neji...
Catch up with us, no matter what!
Can he see me?!
What the heck is he?!
I know you're there.
Come out.
Those eyes...
It seems they can do more
than just see through the Chakra flow...
So I see there was
an extraordinary Visual Jutsu user.
A long range battle
is unfavorable...
I must bring this to
close combat by all means.
Very well.
I'll acknowledge that this game has
a somewhat high level of difficulty!
I too shall go for it seriously...
It's like he's a totally different person
from before...
His Chakra activity is overwhelming.
And those markings...
His move earlier...
He dodged an attack aimed
from behind
and was able to see me hiding
in the shadows.
In other words,
he has a combined wide range
of sight and X-ray vision.
And what's more, that Jutsu...
If so...
Summoning Jutsu!
Your ability...
I'll find a way to impeccably assault it.
If he defends
against physical attacks
with a large emission
of Chakra and its Rotation...
all I need to do then is to stop
that Chakra Rotation!
Scatter!
Rotation!
It's starting to stop.
Here!
Die!
He released the Chakra just in time
and repelled the Kunai Knife!
To think he'd stop my Chakra Rotation
by binding it with Chakra threads...
These things...
I just have to cut them for now.
If the Rotation won't do,
then I just have to dodge
each and every one.
This guy uses
close-range Taijutsu-style combat .
There will be no problem
if I fight him from afar.
In that way...
I'll have a good long look at your ability.
8 Trigrams, 64 Palms!
What a number!
Hm?! His stance changed?!
8 Trigrams.
128 Palms!
He's fast!
The number of strikes has doubled...!
If I get nailed by that straight on,
it'll be the end for me.
If that's the case on his end,
then it'll be a battle of numbers
on this end, too!
The number's too great!
I won't have enough time!
The Rotation's no good,
just as I thought...
It seems he has 360-degree vision.
And it seems he deals
with enemy attacks
by combining his X-ray vision ability
for seeing through things
and his telescopic vision ability
for long-distance sight.
Furthermore, although
he's got 360-degree vision,
that vision has a formidable extent...
If I were to determine the range
from his reaction before...
he almost unfailingly detected
the Kunai Knives
that entered the approximately
150-foot circumference around him.
But for some reason,
there are Kunai Knives
he can't evade completely.
If so...
8 Trigrams, Sixty...
I see...
This time, there'll be even more.
This time, two will hit...
I've found a way to impeccably
assault your ability!
It seems that defense technique
was something to compensate
for this weak point!
In other words...
Your Visual Jutsu isn't perfect!
Why even bother?!
I've won the game!
Come on. Are you going to
keep at it for naught?
The fate of the small fry character in an
easy game is to be destroyed right away!
You can't beat me!
– I-I'm not done yet.
– Lee...
You never give up do you?
No way you can beat him.
He's a genius unlike you.
Genius? What is genius anyway!
Even without any talent,
I'll surpass "genius" by working hard.
It's no use, Lee.
No matter how hard you work,
you cannot beat me.
It's already decided.
Lady Hinata...
You're the sheltered little baby
of the main branch.
A person can never change.
And then, this match...
Your destiny was decided at the point
when I became your opponent.
You don't know until you try!
This is the end...
Gentle Fist!
Small fry character one...
Destruction completed.
Well, for a crummy game,
I was entertained...
Heh... I missed the fatal spots, huh?
And he wouldn't easily die from
Kunai Knives from 150 feet away, eh?
I see...
He's still going to entertain me, huh?
This is thanks for that.
Seriously, that fat Jirobo
can't be helped,
but what's that clod Kidomaru
doing anyway...?
That lowlife!
He's got the habit of playing games.
Maybe he's found someone
to entertain him?
When that idiot plays too much,
he becomes hyper
and easily gets into that state...
But still...
Once he gets to the second state...
it's instant death for the opponent.
Maximum destructive power...
with 100% accuracy!
Die!
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
Would you think it was
a bother if I approached you?
Despite my doubts,
I worked up my courage
My clumsy attempts with words
You listened without turning away
No wonder I get carried away by you
But you don't feel anything for me, do you?
I feel so sad
But... For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
He doesn't carry out wasteful attacks.
And he accurately reads
information from the results.
No mistake, this guy's the strongest
of all I've fought up until now!
I probably won't be able
to evade the next attack.
I've had enough.
I can't dodge it anyway.
Since the secret of my eyes
has been discovered, I won't run or hide!
Next episode: "Losing is Not an Option!"