Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
♪ Natsuhiboshi, why are you so red?
Because I had a sad dream last night.
My eyes are red, from the tears I shed ♪
Swollen as I cried...
Hey!
Neji! Naruto!
What happened to those guys?
It seems they were attacked
by the Shinobi in question...
So he appeared again?
He took...he took Sumaru away.
What? He took Sumaru?!
Yeah!
Anyway, helping the guys who are
down comes first!
We'll split up and carry them!
Got it...
Roger!
Mizura...
Naruto!
They were attacked by
the Shinobi in the mask!
There are no external injuries...
They're just unconscious.
Umm... What about the others?
Lee and Tenten are carrying them
here now.
I see...
Then Sumaru as well...?
Oh... Uh...
He was taken away by
the masked Shinobi.
I'm sorry...
He escaped into the Valley of Death...
We couldn't go after him.
The Valley of Death?!
Did he inhale the gas from
the Valley of Death?
No... I put him into a state of
suspended animation beforehand,
so there was no effect on his body.
I understand using Sumaru
to lure that person...
But to use a child from our same village...
Is it enough to make you feel ill at ease?
We're comrades who have
already dirtied our hands...
What're you doing talking nice now?!
We'll make those Hidden Leaf kids
believe that
Sumaru's kidnapping was
the work of that person...
After we've taken back the star,
we can leave the clean-up to them...
Hidden Jutsu:
The Price of the Ninja Art: Kujaku
Mizura isn't feeling well and
is taking a break from his training...
Byakugan!
What's this...?!
Mizura!
You okay?
You still need to rest...
I must not rest at a time like this...
I understand how you feel...
But you shouldn't push yourself too hard!
I'm fine... I can walk by myself...
Mizura! See, didn't I tell you?!
I'm okay by myself!
Mother... Father!
Mother! Father!
Do not cry... Sumaru...
Your parents protected the star
and protected the village admirably.
Sumaru... Look up at the sky and watch.
There is a treasure you can see only
in the Village Hidden in the Stars.
If you were born as a Shinobi,
for the sake of protecting this village,
for the sake of protecting the star,
become strong!
Like your father and your mother... Okay?
Lord...Hoshikage...
Yeah, this looks good!
Naruto...
Huh?
At this rate, Mizura will die!
I felt a Chakra disturbance
and looked into it.
Despite him lying quietly,
his Chakra was being activated
to the utmost limit.
If that keeps up, he'll be killed
by his own Chakra.
That could never be...!
There's no mistake...
But...!
It's because of the star training.
The star has the power
to activate Chakra.
However, many Shinobi are unable
to control the amplification,
their bodies break down
and it leads to death.
In the middle of this training,
Mizura also...
The Third Hoshikage terminated
training utilizing the star
due to the large amount of casualties.
Then why again?
Lord Akahoshi,
the current leader of the village,
decided to resume the training
half a year ago.
Something so dangerous!
We'll make him stop right now!
Those born and raised in this village
do not fear the star training!
Why would you...?
If they can complete the training
by themselves
and make every effort possible for
the village as a Hidden Star Shinobi...
Even if the body were to be destroyed,
they would be satisfied.
That's just...
Go!
Notice my Chakra... Natsuhi!
Hotarubi... Please protect the star,
protect Sumaru...
Akahoshi's Chakra...
Please use this until you get better...
I'm sure you will!
Thanks, Naruto...
But I won't...
It seems his condition has stabilized...
Everyone seems okay for the time being.
It still doesn't sit right with me...
Mizura and Hokuto, they're all thinking
earnestly of the village.
Especially that Sumaru guy.
He thinks of the village
more than anyone.
What do you mean...?
If it were for the sake
of protecting the village
and the special comrades around me...
I would've gotten impatient,
wanting to get strong quickly as well.
Yeah... That's right...
Yes...
Well, this isn't the time to
be saying stuff like that.
The unforgivable one is that star thief!
But, there wouldn't be any suffering
from training if they didn't use the star.
I think so, too.
If they have the star, everyone would train
for the sake of the village.
But if they do train,
then their bodies get...
Geez, I don't know what to do!
Our mission is to protect the star.
Our first priority is to get back the star.
We shouldn't be meddling in
the matters that follow!
That's right...
Okay.
Got it!
Lee and Tenten, you guys search
around the village chief once more!
What? Again?
Why did the flying Shinobi escape
to the dangerous Valley of Death?
Even though he got the star,
why did he go so far as
to take Sumaru away?
Come to think of it... Why is that?
The quality of Chakra of
the one who took the star
and the one who took Sumaru away
were completely different.
What?!
Say what?!
That's right...
There are two masked Shinobi!
What does that mean?
In my opinion, there's more to
this mission than meets the eye.
As usual, impressive Ninja Art: Kujaku,
Lady Natsuhi.
Where is he...? Where's Sumaru?!
Before that, I'll have you return
the star to me...
I'll trade it for Sumaru!
The star first!
I refuse!
Then I'll take it back by force
if I have to!
What's so funny?!
Akahoshi...
You're no competition to me.
Even after you left the village,
a few of us who were interested
continued training in secret!
You think you have completed
the star training
by training on your own?
Verify with your own eyes whether
or not I'm no competition!
Ninja Art: Kujaku!
Beast!
Such a folly... I have no choice.
Ninja Art: Kujaku... Beast!
Wha...?!
To think she'd be this tough...
Yotaka! Shisou!
– Go!
– Yes, sir!
What're you thinking, Akahoshi?!
I'll have you play along with me
a little while longer...Lady Natsuhi.
Huh? What is it?
A flow of massive Chakra...
Is it him?!
No mistake!
Oh?! Who is it?!
Our helper from the Leaf...
The Shinobi who seized the star
has appeared!
Lord Akahoshi is now delaying
that person...
Please fight with us!
All right! Let's hurry!
The enemy's power is mighty
and Lord Akahoshi alone cannot...
It's all he can do to delay the enemy.
Right. Leave it to us!
It seems nobody's here.
It seems they've gone out...
There's a faint presence
inside the residence.
Now's our chance. Let's infiltrate!
Right!
Ninja Art: Phantom Jutsu!
What?! Lee?
Since when could you use Ninjutsu...?
Tenten! It's okay. There's nobody in here!
Hey, that's not Ninjutsu!
Kind of...
Suspicious, eh?
Yikes!
Uh...uh, oh...
Well... I guess I can do it later.
It seems to be a medical room...
Somebody's being laid down in a bed.
I wonder who it is?
That's...!
Sumaru!
Why did you make Sumaru and
the others do that star training?
You should've been told by
the Third Hoshikage
about how dangerous that training is!
You yourself...are the answer to that!
What?!
That Chakra is wonderful!
It would make for great fighting strength
if we had one hundred, no,
even ten Shinobi like you!
The likes of the Five Great Hidden Villages
would be no match for us
even if they all ganged up on us!
It's still not too late.
Let's make this village into
an invincible Hidden Star Village!
It hurts... It hurts...
My body feels like it is on fire!
Help me...
I must train... Star training...
– That's enough... That's enough.
– For the sake of Hidden Star Village...
There's no need to do
such painful training!
That sorrow must not be repeated...
If you're saying you're going to
continue this any further...!
W-Wait! If I die, Sumaru will also die!
You can't do it! Natsuhi!
Sumaru, who is more important
than your life, is in my hands!
There he is!
He's moving in on Akahoshi!
All right!
I won't let him get away this time.
Wait! He's not an opponent
you can take on from the front.
I've got a plan.
A plan...?
I'll stop his Chakra,
so I leave the rest to you!
Indeed, the situation will get worse
if we're too slow.
Got it! Be careful, Naruto!
All right! Let's go!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
– Let's go!
You again?!
It's more than I imagined.
It's impossible from the front, after all.
What?!
Where's the real body?!
Oh, no!
I get it.
When controlling massive Chakra,
less attention is paid to the area around
the main body in spite of everything...
Good thinking, Naruto!
He... He did it...
A woman...?!
The Hidden Leaf Kid has done it...
I can find the star if I take the time...
But now's my only chance
to defeat Natsuhi!
As long as she interferes, I won't be able
to carry out my ambitions!
Ninja Art: Kujaku!
Beast!
Naruto! Look out!
Shoot!
Naruto!
Something the matter, Mizura...?
No... It's nothing...
Naruto...
Mother...
Yesterday's Call Sign,
was all from my cell phone.
In a strange park,
I play the Fuzz Guitar without enthusiasm.
Yellow Moon.
Even now, counting to three,
I open my eyes
Shadow Moon I am still dreaming.
Look at my eyes, look at my eyes,
as we face one another's back
Look at my eyes, when can we meet?
EveryDay EveryNight
With every word I can think of
Right away, my messy feelings as is,
A magical chord change, in a restless city
A daily JAZZ Guitar played
in a soft minor key
Everybody, I just realized
something important!
What is it all of the sudden?
Sumaru was being captured
by Akahoshi!
Which means that the culprit who attacked
everyone was Akahoshi!
And?
Believe it or not!
One of the masked Shinobi is Akahoshi.
Neji said that long time ago, remember?
Excellent, Neji.
You are a sharp one!
Can we move on?
Next time:
"Hoshikage: The Buried Truth"