Press down hard on the gas
That's right, there's no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We're speeding through life,
squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you're not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we'll go far off into the distance.
Tenten vs. Temari
The fifth battle...
Tenten, Temari...come forward!
Seeing that made me all fired up, too!
Now...The second one from
the Land of Sand, huh...
Do your best!
– Tenten!
– It looks like it's going to be interesting.
Begin!
Killer Kunoichi and a Shaky Shikamaru
Go for it, Tenten!
Believe in your own strength, Tenten!
We're behind you, Tenten!
Knock her with all your strength!
That's good!
Cheer her on more, more,
more with passion, Lee!
Yeah!
These guys are noisy!
That spacing is just what I'd expect
from Tenten,
not too close, not too far.
Attacks or defense,
she can respond to either one.
What happened?
Please begin.
Are you planning to wait out and
see how I make my move?
Let me just tell you,
once I start my attack
you'll be over in a second.
You're trying to be cool and
see what I do first...
A hundred years too early!
It doesn't matter to me, come first.
You said it...
Well, I won't hold back.
They missed? That's impossible!
What happened?
Is that a warm-up?
Or are you scared and your aim is off?
I thought I would enjoy it
a little bit more,
but evidently it's not promising.
No way!
I can't believe Tenten's attack missed!
It's unbelievable indeed.
Tenten's weapons...
always hits the mark
ten out of ten times.
There no reason for them to miss.
That's right...
She didn't miss.
She was made to miss.
As always, she's being disagreeable.
How foolish...
How disgraceful!
Huh?
Sand wins again.
We don't know that yet.
We know.
How?
How do we know?
Explain it so I understand!
Stupid... As if I'd do
such a bothersome thing.
Shikamaru said it so,
surely that's how it is.
These guys are hard to understand.
Calm down...
Don't let her get to you...
One.
Two.
Three...
If it's gonna get dodged,
I just have to make
it impossible to!
So she's measuring the spacing,
next one is going to be the big attack.
I get it...
So, that fan is the secret.
If so...
How about...this?!
No way!
My flying weapons!
Is there a secret mechanism
in the fan...?
This is... the first star.
There are two more.
When the third star appears,
you will lose.
Tenten!
Don't be taken in by
your opponent, be calm!
Be calm!
I know...
Lee, I really intended to use
this in the main battle,
not the preliminary round...
but it looks like I can't do it that way.
She's already going to use it?
Pulling out two scrolls?
What does she intend to do?
Hah! No matter what you do,
it won't work.
Rising Twin Dragons!
Even if you increase the amount,
it's still the same!
Second star!
I'm not done yet!
Did I do it?
Third star.
She disappeared!
Where is she?
I'm over here!
Darn...!
Ninja Art!
Wind Scythe Jutsu!
Tenten!
Chakra is enfolded in that wind.
Huh?!
Tenten fought well...
But she won't be able to escape from
that twister.
T-That's awful.
Tenten...!
How boring...really.
To think she completely intercepted
Tenten's weapon attacks.
This is ridiculous!
What's going on with her...?
It's just like Shikamaru said,
it's the Sand's win.
That's why I said it.
There's no reason for us to lose here.
The Land of Sand is to be feared...
Temari wins the fifth battle.
Oh no!
Nice catch.
What are you doing?!
Is that something you do to
an opponent who fought to the utmost?!
You're annoying!
Take that trash away already!
Stop! Lee!
Leaf Hurricane!
What?!
You're just like you look...
You're dull too.
What did you say?!
Stop! Lee!
Guy Sensei!
Temari.
Come up quick, you've been
declared the winner.
Don't keep company with that awful-looking
guy and his chaperone forever.
What...?!
That's enough, Lee.
Gentlemen of Sand...
I wonder if I may give you
a word of warning.
This kid is strong.
You should prepare yourselves.
Picking a fight with the Sand...
I absolutely wouldn't want to
do it with those guys.
T-They're all awesome guys...
Don't lose to those guys!
Naruto!
S-Sakura.
Sakura... Are you okay already?
Never mind that,
you should worry about yourself!
Huh? Me? I don't have
an injury or anything.
That's not what I mean.
If you lose here, it's a point of dishonor.
You'd be ashamed to face Sasuke!
Y- Yeah.
And...
Thanks for earlier...
No!
Sakura!
You did your hardest
to get here!
You'll disgrace women if
you lose to that Sasuke-obsessed girl!
If it weren't for your stupid cheering
at that time...
I would have been soundly
beaten by Ino.
Yeah, that's right.
Y-You!
Okay, hurry hurry!
Me next!
Next!
Next is my turn!
Shikamaru Nara vs. Tsuchi Kin
Darn!
It's me.
Shikamaru, don't lose!
– Show us that you're a real man!
– All right, all right.
Get her with the 16 combo, go!
– Win Shikamaru!
– Ino's become super energetic.
You go for it!
That guy manipulates shadows.
Be careful of the shadows...
I won't be beaten by
a stupid technique like that.
Shikamaru!
Bash that one around!
And while you're at it...
Man, what a pain.
Furthermore, my opponent is a woman...
It's hard to get to it.
If that's what you think,
I'll end this quickly.
Go, go! Shikamaru!
Well, you could say that
I know these guys' raw power
from that incident from the second test...
I don't know anything about this one's Jutsu.
On top of that, she's seen my Jutsu...
– The sixth battle.
– That being said, for me...
Shikamaru versus Kin!
Begin!
I can only do this.
One trick pony, huh...?
Shut up!
Ninja Art, Shadow Possession Jutsu!
That Jutsu!
It's nothing if I just pay attention
to the movement of your shadow!
Bells...?
Heh, that's a classic.
Next, you'll throw Senbons with bells
and Senbons without bells
at the same time, right?
I'll respond to the sound of the bells,
intending to dodge them.
But I won't notice the quiet Senbons,
and, ouch.
Is that right?
You're a chatty guy!
So in order to not get caught
by the shadow Senbons...
I'm alert to the trick
and look closely...
What?!
Behind?!
String?
Darn it!
Too late!
Shikamaru!
He took that pretty bad.
It wasn't tat bad, look closely.
Huh?
F-For the moment I dodged a fatal hit.
Now it's my turn!
That's not going to happen.
W-What's this?
That happens to anyone
who hears my bell.
The sound vibration of
this special bell
reaches the brain directly
from the ear drum.
And then it will make you hallucinate.
It's useless!
You can't avoid the sound of
my bell by doing...
that...that...that...that...that...
Shoot! Which one?
Which is the real one?
You can't do anything, can you?
Your shadow, which was your faint hope,
doesn't even know where to stretch to...
Well... I'll cook you slowly.
Taking me lightly...!
This time it's five,
next time seven...
I'll continue until you become
a hedgehog.
Y-You're lying, you brat!
Huh?!
You'd end it soon...
That's what you said
in the beginning, isn't it?
I see, you can't endure the pain
and want to be eased.
Well, I'll finish it here.
It's your death warrant.
W-What?!
M-My body...
At last, Shadow Possession Jutsu
is a success.
W-What are you saying?
No way!
Your shadow isn't anywhere...
You don't realize it yet?
I-It can't be...
It's just that, you fool!
A thread at this height
can't have a shadow.
I can stretch and shrink
my own shadow.
The shadow is gradually getting thicker.
This wasn't the shadow of the thread...
That's right. I stretched my shadow
and made it narrow,
so it looked like the shadow of
a thread and stuck it on you.
But... How do you win with that?
I'm just gonna move
the same way as you.
Annoying.
Be quiet and watch.
Stupid!
If you continue like this and attack...
You, too,
will be wounded!
I know that.
No way! You're...!
We're gonna throw shuriken
at each other.
How far will we go...?
Fool, stop it!
You're only talk...
And that one's a goner.
If you're a shinobi,
you have to grasp the situation
and the layout when you battle.
Even though we made
the same movements...
the distance of the walls behind
each of us was different.
I just used the shuriken and
called attention away
from the wall behind us.
Winner! Shikamaru Nara.
Good job Shikamaru!
Cool!
Me next... Me next... Me next...!
That guy's dull and plain,
but that was kinda cool.
Shoot!
I'm the only one left.
And the next match.
The people left are one Sound ninja,
me, Hinata, Naruto, Choji, Neji and Lee.
And that Sand guy...
Just please spare me from that guy.
This year's rookie looks quite challenging...
Naruto Uzumaki vs. Kiba Inuzuka
It's here, it's here, it's here!
What we've been waiting for!
It's finally my turn!
Yeah! Lucky us!
If it's this guy
we'll absolutely win, Akamaru!
Yahoo!
– If I'm not next, Sakura will despise me...
– I'm gonna do it!
– and call me Bushy Brow.
– I'm gonna go for it!
– If I'm not next. Sakura will...
– Just watch me! Yay!
This Lee kid, he's just like
Guy was in the past...
Do your best, Naruto.
Leave it to me.
Well Naruto, show us...
how much you've grown.
I'm going to do it!
Hey, can you hear it?
The clear, blue sky
goes on and on
The ocean
spans limitlessly
Please keep
that smile on your face forever
Or else I'll cry
You won't have to search around you
It's all ok now.
Everyone is inside
this hand
when you want to cry,
and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born, and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia, feel the telepathy
Hey, can you hear it?
Darn that Kiba!
I hold back a little bit and
he rides my brain.
Yap, yap, yap, yap,
it's annoying! Believe it!
Just quit talking tough, and use your dog
or whatever, and come at me!
I don't know what kind of
training you've done,
but I'm the man who's going
to become Hokage.
You're the one who's going
to get his butt kicked.
Next time: "Akamaru Unleashed!
Who's Top Dog Now?"
Don't take me lightly!