I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long way to go
on that road.
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky
with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond
that...
What were you gazing at?
It's been a while since
I've eaten Ichiraku ramen!
Lately I've been away
from home on missions.
The bowl of ramen after
a mission...
it spreads to every muscle of the body
and becomes energy for tomorrow.
If you eat ramen
it drives fatigue away.
Ramen!
Temporarily closed...?
No, it can't be...
I endured all the tough missions,
looking forward to Ichiraku ramen...
I can smell ramen!
What?
You're right!
Without a doubt...
Ramen is being made in there!
Ramen!
Mix it! Stretch it! Boil it up!
Burn Copper Pot Burn!
This smell...
It's the smell of a soup
that's never been on
the Ichiraku menu before.
Then... It's temporarily closed
to develop a new menu?
Who's there?!
A large helping of miso char siu ramen!
With an egg please.
I see...
You were looking forward to
my ramen that much.
Sorry about that.
It's okay to develop a new menu,
but I wish you'd do it
after the shop is closed.
Since you came all this way.
Give this a taste.
Could this be...
Ichiraku's new menu?!
Let's eat!
Wait a minute!
There are rules when you're eating
a new ramen for the first time...
Rule #1!
Before you do anything,
you must first have
a sip to taste the soup.
– Delicious!
Next, you have to coat the noodles
in soup and eat.
Huh? It seems like something
is missing...
Let's get to the point.
The noodles are outdone
by the soup!
This well-seasoned, rich soup
greatly surpasses
any of Ichiraku's previous soups!
But! The noodles are
the same as always!
The balance is very bad.
I cannot give it a passing score!
That's what I thought...
Oh... Don't get so depressed...
Ayame, water! Water please!
Huh? Where's Ayame?
With ramen like this...
I'll never be able to get Ayame
back from the Ryonin.
Teuchi!
He's just overtired.
I had him drink an energy drink,
so after a little rest he'll recover.
But... I think he should take a break
from the shop for a while.
He's been using his arms
too much...
Look how swollen this is.
Come to think of it,
before he fell,
he said something about Ryonin
or whatever
did something to Ayame, I think...
Ayame is his daughter, right?
What's Ryonin?
I don't know...
Ryonin...
He's referring to the Ninja Chef.
Ninja Chef?
Do you know about them, Choji?
I've heard rumors about them...
One of the problems Shinobi's confront
on missions is the problem of meals!
Normally Food Pills were brought
with them,
but the main role of those
are to supply nutrients.
They have no taste.
If they could eat delicious food
while on missions,
would the success rate
of missions rise?
Based on that theory,
was born...
The Ninja Chef... Ryonin!
But what those Ninja Chef
have to do with Ayame?
They snatched her away...
What?! What are you talking about?!
Give us the details!
It was two weeks ago...
Ichiraku Ramen
Welcome!
The large serving,
here's your order!
A good job as always, Teuchi!
Hakkaku!
His name is Hakkaku,
long ago we trained at
the same ramen shop...
He told me he is a Ninja Chef,
a Ryonin, these days.
Actually... I have a favor to ask you.
What is it? If it's something I can do,
I'll cooperate.
The phantom recipe that
I heard you developed...
Please turn it over to me!
Ph-Phantom recipe?
What are you talking about?
To a chef, a recipe is
more precious than life!
I understand why
you want to hide it!
But... please! Give it to me!
I really had no clue.
But Hakkaku didn't believe me...
Ayame. Let's get to work
opening the shop...
What the... What's this tray?
Ayame!
I have your daughter.
If you want her back,
hand over the "phantom recipe!"
Damn that Hakkaku!
Why didn't you contact
the Hokage right away!
The Hokage could...
If I did that, I don't know what
would happen to Ayame.
And he also wrote this
in the letter...
That if I can serve them
something impressive,
he'll give up on the phantom recipe
and return my daughter safe.
But, you've got a way to win?
I don't know.
But a chef's challenged me
to a cooking match.
I have no choice but to do it.
So that's why you're developing
new ramen.
I was able to make the soup
exactly how I wanted to.
But...I just can't get the firm noodles
that go with the soup...
I can't get Ayame back like this!
The cooking match is tomorrow...
What am I going to do?
I can't imagine an Ichiraku
without Ayame.
Okay! Teuchi! We'll help you.
We'll make the best ramen...
And get Ayame back...
From the Ryonin!
You guys...
I'll teach you the basics
of making noodles.
Quickly mix the ingredients evenly.
If there are discrepancies,
there will be variations in
the taste of the noodles.
Next... Knead it.
If you don't put this properly
the noodles won't be firm.
Are you okay?
It's nothing. Don't worry about me.
And...stretch the noodles!
It's important for them to be
of a uniform thickness!
So there will be no differences
after boiling...
Try it.
It's easy to say it...
but to actually make the noodles
is not so easy.
It takes five years to become
an accomplished chef in his own right.
To do it by the match tomorrow
is completely...
When it comes down to it,
I'll have to give up this decrepit body
of mine to them.
Teuchi... You're not thinking about
when you lose, are you?
Th-That's...
Because if we are doing this,
we're doing it with the intention
of winning, believe it!
I absolutely don't forgive people
who hold a girl captive!
Cooking comes from the heart.
Technique and experience
aren't everything!
No problem...
We'll show them the real strength
of the Shinobi of Leaf Village!
Sorry to make you wait, Hakkaku!
The phantom recipe?
You can't tell by looking at me?
I see. How foolish...
Let me tell you,
ramen like the stuff I ate at
your shop the other day can't win.
Is Ayame okay?
Father!
Ayame!
The emotional reunion comes
after the match.
I have a favor to ask.
Let me have some helpers.
I don't think those kids are up
to the task, but...
Well... That's okay.
Well, let's start the cooking match!
Let's see if you can satisfy
all of us Ninja Chef!
There are so many of them...
We don't have time to stand around...
Let's begin!
The preparation for the soup
is done!
I'll prepare the ingredients
for the rest!
I'm leaving the noodles to you!
– Okay!
Listen. Our noodles determine
whether Ayame will return or not!
We cannot fail!
Seems like he's done a good job
with the soup...
The delicious aroma is
wafting over here.
Indeed, it's whetting my appetite.
The noodles are the problem!
Can those kids really make noodles that
will go with that soup?
First, mix the ingredients!
They're amateurs,
I thought so!
You can't make decent noodles
with that hand movement!
We practiced making noodles
all night!
But, we didn't make the noodles
we wanted to by morning...
Even so, we have to
make perfect noodles!
Hey hey. At least make us
something edible!
Quickly...
Uniformly...
Without discrepancies!
Next, knead it!
Hey, Sakura!
Look, it's Kakashi Sensei.
Don't play!
Sakura...
Oww! Sakura, you just can't control
your own crazy strength!
It's your fault for playing around
at a time like this!
This is...
the last of the ingredients.
No problem. This time, let us
show you we'll succeed!
Okay, I'm mixing.
Wait Choji! Leave this to me!
Naruto...
Hey, Sakura...
Huh?
We are Shinobi, right?
So then... Let's show them
the Ninja way to make noodles!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Rasengen! "Ichiraku" version!
Wh-What?! Mixing ingredients
with Chakra?!
No, that way he'll surely be able
to mix the ingredients uniformly!
And in micro units!
Sakura!
What?
Pervy Sage.
Naruto!
Cha!
Wh-What's this crazy strength...?!
If she does that,
the noodles will become super firm!
Okay, Sakura! Choji!
I, too...am a Shinobi of Leaf Village!
Partial Expansion Jutsu: Both Hands!
What?!
What outstanding noodles!
If those noodles are added to
Teuchi's soup, this match would...
W-We cannot lose!
It's for the future of the Ninja Chef!
Now they just have to be boiled, Teuchi!
Okay! Leave it to me!
Wait a minute!
When the ramen is done...
Who will you serve it to first?
Huh? Who...?
Th-That's right...
That's how it is!
That's how what is?
Among the chefs...
there's a cardinal rule
not to be forgotten.
The first guest to arrive is
the first guest served!
No matter how delicious
the food you make is...
if you break this cardinal rule,
you're disqualified as a chef!
True, if a guy who came later
were eating before me,
then it would seriously pisses me off.
There are 100 Ninja Chefs here...
They all showed up at about
the same time!
So you have to serve ramen
to 100 people at the same time!
You're four people...
Can you really serve at
the same time?
I said we're Ninja, didn't I?
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
What?!
Now! Lift them!
– Thanks for waiting. Here you go!
Th-The taste is the issue!
If you don't satisfy us, you lose!
Delicious!
– Delicious!
I've never had ramen this delicious.
So then...
We win!
– We did it!
The truth is...
We Ninja Chefs are at
the end of our rope...
End of your rope?
What do you mean by that?
We endeavored to make
delicious meals to eat during missions...
We thought to make delicious food,
to fill your stomach...
that can be eaten anywhere...
But we pursued taste too far.
It was too delicious, people were
compelled to overeat.
And as a result...
Ninja gained weight,
and it interfered with their missions.
And some people are now saying,
"we don't need
the Ninja Chefs anymore."
– Oh...
For us Ninja Chefs
to continue,
we had to get our hands on
the "phantom" recipe out there
in the cooking world!
Recipe?
If we use this recipe,
we can improve the performance
of Shinobi without causing a burden.
There's such recipe...?
I hear, it's called
"the scum recipe."
– The scum recipe?!
We've gathered information
from everywhere...
As a result,
we learned that the scum recipe
was at "Ichiraku" which Teuchi run.
– What?!
I-I don't know!
There's no reason something like that
should be at my shop!
There's someone who heard it!
I've got "the scum recipe"
at my shop, so...
Oh... Teuchi...?
Oh. I might have that.
Are you serious?!
I thought so!
To be precise...
It's the "scum removal recipe."
– Scum removal?
The trick to making delicious soup...
is how well you
remove the scum.
So I, too, studied a lot.
Eventually, I worked out a recipe
that can remove the scum effectively.
Usually it's called
"the scum recipe" for short...
I never thought that
this misunderstanding would arise.
That's a pretty big omission.
Geez. That's a stupid punch line...
We won the cooking match,
so keep your promise
and return Ayame!
That's right! Where is she?!
Father!
Aya...me?
Ayame...is that you?
Can't you tell by looking?
B-But Ayame is like...
The food they make is
so delicious, I overeat...
Did I gain that much weight?
Ayame!
Ichiraku's new menu?
The thing we made
at the cooking challenge?
No, a diet ramen
that's popular among girls.
Diet Ramen?
It's super popular!
Oh, come on in, Naruto.
You've regained
your former shape...
It's thanks to my father's
diet ramen!
Huh? Where's your father?
Well... While he was joining me
in eating the diet ramen...
Hey... Naruto.
That's a little too thin, believe it.
The wind blows, Ah...
The pain,
The memories won't disappear
What should be brought along?
Assemble them into a piece.
There is no second chance, never
How foolish it is to throw away
Acting so innocently, Ah...
The images.
It probably will not end
Burn that love-filled heart,
Sail across a thousand dreams
Running freely
To take hold of the world in hand
The clouds scatter
The sun sets yet again
The solo parade begins to move.
Adventure, Lucky Day, Heart Beat, Rising,
Decisive, Encounter, Life, Mutual Love
Does anyone have anything
to ask about this mission?
I've got a question!
Why should I have to go on
a mission with this group?
Okay, let's move on.
Everyone ready?
Hey, I've got a question, believe it!
As for the mission details,
we're to eliminate the Demon of the Ocean
in the Land of Oceans.
You guys are going to get
fired up for me
since you came to serve under me!
Just a minute.
Hey, listen to me!
Now, let's get going!
Stop complaining and
just come with me!
Listen to me, I say.
Listen! Listen! Listen!
Next time:
"Remembrance: The Lost Page"