Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
The Promise That Could Not Be Kept
Kakashi Sensei...
Where's Sasuke?
Kakashi!
How is Naruto Uzumaki's condition?
He's okay.
What about Sasuke? Where's Sasuke Uchiha?!
How are the other Genin?
Yes! By Lady Hokage's order,
the first and second medical corps
have been dispatched...
The wounded from all areas have
already been gathered.
They were convoyed after
administering emergency treatment.
How are their conditions?
Yes! Shikamaru Nara has minor injuries...
Kiba Inuzuka has serious injuries,
but it's not life-threatening.
Neji Hyuga and Choji Akimichi
are in serious condition...
At this point,
there's no telling what will happen.
Everyone...
The ingredients and
effects of the medicine
have been thoroughly researched.
Excellent...
Now bring the deer antler!
Yes, ma'am!
How is he...Big Sister?
No walks for him for quite a while...
The muscles of his limbs
have been severely damaged.
You're a vet, right, Big Sister?
Can't you somehow...?
It'll be okay.
It'll take time. But there's no threat
to his life, so rest easy.
Walks for you are out of the question
for quite a while, too!
Yeah, I know...
Intensive Care Unit 7
It'll soon be three hours...
Please take over.
All right!
Although we're making
this kid's hair into a conductor,
please don't mistake the cellular rate
of the deficient parts!
Right!
As for the Chakra control, handle it
as if we're threading a needle!
Understood!
Intensive Care Unit 6
There's no point in
you getting frustrated, right?
Missions come with sacrifice...
You took the mental training, right?
Training and actual battle
are different, you know...
I know what missions are about...
And I thought I knew what
the Shinobi world is like.
I became a platoon leader
for the first time on this mission.
With that, I understood...
I'm not cut out to be a Shinobi.
Surprisingly fragile...for a man.
This time...
The only thing I was able to do
as platoon leader...
was to believe in everyone.
I was naïve... I didn't have enough power...
It's all my fault!
Are you afraid of getting hurt?
Shikamaru...
Are you going to be argued down
by a girl and run away?
It's a drag...
I don't want to have arguments.
I'm not a woman.
Yeah... But you're not a man, either.
You're just a coward!
Even if you quit being Shinobi,
the missions will continue.
Someone has to do it.
Your comrades will just
be dispatched again...
under a different platoon leader.
And your comrades might die there.
But if at that time,
you were the platoon leader...
your comrades might be saved
from that happening to them.
If you reflect on this time,
make use of the experience and learn,
you might be able to carry out missions
with more perfection.
If you really think your comrades
are important to you,
before you think about running away...
think about becoming more exceptional
for the sake of your comrades!
That's what real comrades are, you coward!
Intensive Care Unit 6
He's okay, now!
The antidote has stopped
the death of cells
caused by the side effects of the Pills.
You were a big help this time, Shikaku!
The Nara Clan's secret medicinal
preparation manual was very useful.
It must've been tough to
make something like that...
It's the result of day-to-day study.
Thanks...
Lady Tsunade!
Neji Hyuga...
His safety line has been secured.
And, there's some information...
Kakashi Hatake and Naruto Uzumaki
have just now returned.
Although seriously injured,
it seems it's not life-threatening.
Two, huh?
Shikamaru...
It seems the mission is a failure.
But, everyone is alive!
That's the most important thing.
Next time for sure...
I'll carry out the mission perfectly!
Sasuke...You're the chosen one.
Whatever... Just give me "power."
Even though the form is different,
it's still Lord Orochimaru before your eyes.
If you don't want to die,
use more care in how you talk.
Wh-What? This quality of Chakra...
Yes... My future is inside this kid...
Hidden Leaf Hospital
I'm going to where Orochimaru is!
Please...bring back Sasuke!
I'll bring Sasuke back without fail!
I promise that on my life!
Oh...You were awake, huh?
Shikamaru!
I'm going on ahead to Choji!
What about you?
I'm going on ahead to... Naruto and Sasuke!
I see... So everyone's okay. That's good.
Then, Sasuke...
Yeah...he's gone.
Intensive Care Unit 6
Then, I still can't see him...?
Yeah... But Lady Tsunade said that
he should regain consciousness soon.
Thank goodness...
It's really a great help that
Lady Tsunade returned to the Leaf Village.
If she hadn't, right about now,
Choji would be...
The Lady Fifth...Hokage.
You've come to visit?
Information sure travels fast.
Sakura...
Naruto...
I heard you suffered
quite a serious injury...
But you look well, considering.
I'm sorry... Sakura...
Why do you apologize?
Being you, you probably
got reckless again, right?!
Jeez, you look like a mummy...
I'm sorry... I...
Hey... The weather's nice today.
So open the curtains.
Sakura! I...
I'll keep my promise, no matter what!
I promised on my life.
That's what I said, so I...!
It's okay already, Naruto...
-Sakura! He...
-I always...
said that, so... I...
I stick straight to what I say!
That's my Way of Ninja!
Naruto...
Thanks, Naruto...
I'll get right to healing this injury
and I've got to bring Sasuke back!
Wh-What was that?!
Per...Pervy Sage?!
Yo!
I've come today to tell you
something important.
From here on, as my official disciple,
I'll train you to become
a full-fledged Shinobi in three years.
Three years...?
I've received some credible information
from a certain source
concerning the "Akatsuki."
Akatsuki...
It seems that it will be
three or four years
before they come after you next.
I don't care about that!
Talking about stuff that's
so far down the road...
I don't have the time
to be doing slowpoke training!
What do you mean?
If I don't go after Sasuke immediately,
he might be killed by Orochimaru!
"Immortal" doesn't mean that
the flesh is being maintained as is.
Before his body decays,
a strong and new flesh will be made
into a vessel for his soul.
It seems you've learned
of the true purpose
for Orochimaru seeking Sasuke...
Huh?! Then that means you also knew...?
I was looking into
Orochimaru's Immortality Jutsu.
It seems with that Jutsu,
he can't reincarnate into
the next body for three years.
And unable to wait for Sasuke,
he just recently reincarnated...
It'll be okay for three years from now...
There is time.
That's not a lie, is it?!
Not a lie, is it?!
Nope...
However...
Forget about Sasuke...
Sasuke went to Orochimaru
on his own accord.
No matter what you do, he won't change.
I've seen many Shinobi, so I know...
Sasuke is the same kind as Orochimaru.
If you're thinking about bringing him back,
just forget it.
That's something an arrogant fool
would do!
He may be nothing to you
but he's my friend!
Would a friend hurt his comrade?!
Take a look at your current plight!
This is...!
Why? Why would you...?
We were called Sannin together...
Weren't we comrades since we were kids?!
In every regard,
you're a foolish guy, Jiraiya...
You lack thought in everything you do.
That's why you didn't notice
what I was doing.
Can't you rethink it, Orochimaru?
Absurd!
How can you be so stupid?!
No matter how much I wanted it...
in the end, there was no way
he would come back.
After the agony, all that's left was
my own powerlessness and regret.
I don't want you to go through
the same thing...
If you're going to go after Sasuke,
then there'll be no training.
I'll get Anbu Black Ops to watch you
and depending on the case,
prohibit you from leaving the village.
You're not just an ordinary kid...
You possess the Nine Tail Fox
that the Akatsuki is after!
This is serious.
I'll just have to do that...
if you're going to act on your own
without listening to what I say.
Eventually, you're going to have to deal
with guys more troublesome
than Orochimaru.
Give up on Sasuke.
Sooner or later this was going to happen.
Don't suffer anymore!
Forget and dismiss him.
It's not just Jutsu or power...
If you're a Shinobi, develop eyes that
can make the right judgment.
And if you're going to live
as a Shinobi, become wise.
If you remain a fool...
the reality is that it will be tough
living in this world.
Fine.
If that's what being wise is...
Then I'm fine being a fool for life!
Even if by myself,
I'll create even more awesome Jutsu
and save Sasuke no matter what!
And, and,
I'll even kick the Akatsuki's butt!
If someone like you were to do it alone...
the best you'd be able to come up with
would be some stupid erotic Jutsu, anyway.
It might somehow work out
if you are a big fool and
not an ordinary fool...
Be prepared once
you're out of the hospital,
you big fool.
See you then.
Roger!
-It's been seven years since...
-...all the members gathered like this.
Since Orochimaru left the organization.
That Orochimaru has gotten the Sharingan.
Itachi...Your little brother?
Don't get hasty. Yeah.
We'll kill Orochimaru eventually...
More importantly,
there are only three years left.
Can everyone accomplish
the work required of them?
Huh?
Yes, our goal is...
to get everything,
including the Nine Tail Fox in question!
When I recalled the parts one by one,
I felt as though
I had understood everything
Faded words
which I kept so close to me
Speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
and this distant yearning for you
I live,
simply repeating this cycle
Held in my two hands
A droplet of time
Softly clutching forgotten memories
Lost words
I'll keep these thoughts...
Sakura's been weird all along
ever since Sasuke left.
I can't put it well,
but she's gloomy or fretting or something.
On top of that she says,
"This time I'll do my best on my own."
What the heck does that mean?
It's bugging me, it's bugging me!
This isn't the time for me
to be relaxing in the hospital!
Next episode:
"Deep Cover?! A Super S-Rank Mission"