Press down hard on the gas
That's right, there's no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We're speeding through life,
squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you're not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we'll go far off into the distance.
Sakura Haruno vs. Ino Yamanaka
At this point in time,
I don't even plan to fight
over Sasuke with you.
Sakura!
Do you know who
you're lipping off to?!
Don't press your luck,
crybaby Sakura!
It seems like...
it seems like Sakura was out of line!
Ino's eyes show incredible anger.
She's scary.
Hmm.
That's not it...
Huh?
Sakura's not the kind of kid
to do things
like needlessly flaunt her
own power and hurt people.
She doesn't like having Ino
taking pity on her and pulling punches.
– This time for sure,
– with full strength,
– a fair...fight!
The Ultimate Battle: Cha!
Just a Clone Jutsu...?!
This isn't a Ninja Academy's
graduation exam!
You think you can beat me...
with a textbook ninja art?!
If I look carefully, I can find out,
which is the real one right away...
Chakra to my feet at a burst...Then...
repel off the ground!
Fast!
If you think I'm the crybaby Sakura
I was until recently,
you'll get your fingers burned!
Come like you mean it, Ino!
I appreciate you saying that...
I'll go like I mean it, as you wish!
Way to go Sakura!
Great! Really great!
With the fundamental movements
using Chakra,
she's topnotch among the rookies...
Huh?
Sakura is at her best.
That means...
Is she better than me?
Well! That's right.
Awww!
Sending Chakra all throughout
the body and
using the technique
with it at a right timing...
Those techniques alone
are better than Sasuke.
Well, from the start,
she was extremely good at...
controlling her Chakra, so...
Magnificent movements, Sakura!
However, her opponent is good too.
This evenly-matched battle
looks to take awhile!
Since when did this girl
get this strong?!
I can make it, too...!
You little...!
Whoa!
At this rate, it'll never end.
This is long...
They've been going at it
for ten minutes, at the least.
You shouldn't be evenly
matched with me!
What makes you think
I'm evenly matched with you...
who's only concerned with looks
and growing your hair frivolously?!
You!
You carry your mocking
of me too far!
Idiot.
She's going for the bait.
Who knows what Ino will do!
I don't like Ino when she's that way...!
You're simple-minded...
Uh-oh.
She's totally lost it!
I don't need this!
S-Scary...
I'll put an end to this right now!
I'll make you say that you lost!
Hey, don't tell me...
Could it be...?
As I recall, that Sign is...
I knew it...
She's planning to do
the Mind Transfer Jutsu!
Man...That idiot!
I understand your feelings of frustration,
but that's futile.
Humph!
I wonder!
Ninja Art, Mind Transfer Jutsu...
A Jutsu where the user can take
over the opponent's spirit
and wrest their body away
for a few minutes...
by discharging all of
their own spiritual energy
and striking the enemy with it.
But, there are major flaws
to this formidable Jutsu.
First,
the discharged spiritual energy
can only fly straight and at a slow speed.
Second, even in the case of failing
to hit the enemy and missing,
the user can't return to her
own body for several minutes.
I should add that during
that interval, the user's,
in other words, your main body
will turn into a doll that won't move at all!
In the first place, the Mind Transfer
Jutsu is used for spying
and is not a Jutsu for battle.
Ino, using that Jutsu here
would be equal to suicide...
It shouldn't be particularly
scary if she moves about...
And not only that,
if she dodges the Jutsu,
she can beat the heck out
of the non-moving opponent.
If that happens, Hayate will be forced
to put an end to the match...
So what?!
I won't know unless I try!
If you miss, it's over.
You know that, right?
In the first place,
it's a combination Jutsu to be used
after stopping the opponent's
movements during a battle
with my Shadow Possession Jutsu.
There's no way!
There is no way, it will hit...
Idiot! Stop!
Ninja Art, Mind Transfer Jutsu!
Which one...?
That was unfortunate...
Ino.
Has the fat lady sung...?
She went and did it...
Then, it's over, eh.
This is...?!
You fell for it, Sakura!
I finally caught you!
It can't be!
Yes, it can.
My Sign weaving earlier was just an act,
to drive you who was running
about into this contrivance.
So?
You can't move at all, can you?
It's special rope that's my hair
with Chakra poured in!
With this, it will be over when
I enter your body and say "give up!"
It wouldn't miss
a hundred percent of the time!
I see...
That idiot... Her losing it
was also an act?
Get out of there, Sakura!
I can't move...!
Then...
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
That was unfortunate...
She missed!
No!
Sakura...
Sakura!
W-What's with Ino?
Also... Sakura's acting kind of strange!
Believe it!
But...surely this is her chance!
Do it, Sakura!
It's no use.
To think, the Mind Transfer Jutsu there...
Sakura's had it.
Mind Transfer...?!
That means Sakura right now is...
Yes.
Sakura's spirit has been
completely taken over by Ino.
What?!
Ino is inside of Sakura's body now!
Well.
Ino's purpose is most likely...
With this, it's over.
Good bye, Sakura...
I...Sakura Haruno concede...
– this match...
– No!
Sakura!
Tsk!
He's annoying!
You did your hardest to get here!
You'll disgrace women if you lose
to that Sasuke-obsessed girl!
Like I said, those words
are useless...
What's...
this bad chill...?!
Naruto is annoying!
Anyway, that's right...
not to Ino I won't ...
Sakura?!
This can't be happening...
What's the matter?
Are you conceding?
I won't be conceding!
No Way!
Cha!
Which is it?
W-What's going on?!
Sakura...?!
No way!
I messed up my Jutsu...?
Ino...You'll have a terrible time of it
if you don't get out of me quick!
What's wrong, with Ino?
No... I won't hold on at this rate...
Release!
It can't be...
She shattered Ino's Jutsu!
She used too much energy
before the Jutsu...
So she didn't have enough Chakra...?!
To think she has two spirits...
What are you?!
Strength that ranks with beauty.
Girls can't survive if they're not tough!
If caught in that spell,
it's not that easy to cast out
the invader...
Ino's lack of Chakra...
There's also that...
But what was more effective
than that...
was the combative spirit towards
Ino she has inside her heart.
So that was awakened with Naruto's voice
as the trigger
and she cast Ino out...?
There's nothing to it.
Like Naruto...
Sakura's fighting spirit was
much stronger than others.
– This is...!
But, both of them should
have hardly any Chakra left.
– This is...
– the end!
Both parties are unable
to continue the match!
By double knockout,
no one gets through the
fourth battle of the preliminary!
– What?!
– Huh?!
Now then...
Good grief.
Hey, Ino!
Sakura!
A-A-Are you okay?!
Treatment's not necessary.
They'll probably wake up after awhile.
But, that was surprising...
Yeah...
Naruto and Sasuke aside...
to think even that Sakura who didn't
have what it took has grown this much...
A lot happened,
but I really feel like it
was a good thing...
sending her to this Chunin Exam.
Tenten vs. Temari
Seeing that made me all fired up, too!
Now...
The second one from the
Land of Sand, huh...
– This looks to be an interesting match.
– Do your best, Tenten!
It looks like you finally
woke up, eh...Sakura.
Huh?! Tenten, power of youth!
Go Go!
There is no limit to your youth!
Our match is already over.
Did I...lose?
I'm the one who wants to cry...
To think I tied with somebody like you...
Huh?
Here!
You also got a flower to bloom, didn't you?
A beautiful flower!
Ino...
However...
the next time we fight,
it won't end with you
getting knocked out!
Hm...?!
And... I won't hand over
Sasuke to you!
I return the same line to you!
– Humph!
The fifth battle...
Tenten, Temari...
come forward!
Hey, can you hear it?
The clear, blue sky
goes on and on
The ocean
spans limitlessly
Please keep
that smile on your face forever
Or else I'll cry
You won't have to search around you
It's all ok now.
Everyone is inside
this hand
when you want to cry,
and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born, and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia, feel the telepathy
Hey, can you hear it?
You know! You know!
I feel like women battles
are incredible, or...
Women are scary.
Huh?
Hey-hey! This isn't the time to be
withdrawing, Shikamaru.
You're kind of a plain, or a lousy,
or an unimpressive guy, aren't you?
If you don't really put your whole heart
into it, things will get hairy for you.
Next episode:
"Killer Kunoichi and a Shaky Shikamaru"
This is really, seriously bad!