I want to try and
gather the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long
way to go on that road.
I'll continue towards
the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky
with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond
that...
What were you gazing at?
What's this? Where does this water...?
What's the matter, Naruto?!
Get a hold of yourself, please!
Naruto!
They all look like they're having fun.
Naruto...
Hey, you jerk...
This is...that lake from before...
Naruto...
I see...
The person who was calling my name
earlier was you, right, Chishima?
Are you hurt?
I should be asking you that, Chishima.
You shouldn't be moving
with that injury.
I'm fine.
More importantly,
we need to find Lady Toki.
Oh yeah, that's right...
Where the hell did that Moso go?
I'm right here...
Moso...!
Lady Toki...!
Chishima, I'm sorry for having
deceived you for so long...
That's all right, I already had
a sense that maybe...
You guys know too many
of this land's secrets...
I'll have you guys embrace those secrets
as you plunge headfirst into hell...
Is that your real face?
My name is Hoki.
I'm a Wandering Ninja.
I'm not about to let you get in
the way of my taking this peaceful land,
which I have finally managed to snatch!
Water Style: Water Dragon Jutsu!
Chishima!
Please, hang in there!
Are you...all right?
I'm so relieved...
Chishima!
Lady Toki... I have fond memories...
of playing here at this lake...
with you and Lord Sagi.
In those days,
the Land of Bird was tranquil,
gentle and warm...
Use your strength, Lady Toki...
to restore the Land of Birds...
to the way it was in those days...
Chishima...
Hang in there!
Naruto, I beg you...
help Lady Toki...
help my friend...
Sure thing.
If a Leaf Ninja promises something,
he will complete it to the very end.
Promise me...
You must...
you must... protect Lady Toki...
You have feelings for her, don't you?
That ramen...was delicious...
I'll treat you to some again...
Thank you... Naruto...
Chishima!
Chishima...!
That guy was nothing more
than just another
convenient servant, after all.
Shut up!
He loved the Land of Birds
with all his might...
Chishima, who staked his life trying
to protect the country he loved...
I will not...forgive you,
no matter what!
You may say that
you won't forgive me,
but what exactly do
you think you can do?!
Water Style: Giant Vortex Jutsu!
Die!
How annoyingly persistent!
Gentle Fist!
That was careless,
Copy Ninja Kakashi Hatake...
The reputation of the Wandering Ninja
will be upgraded
if I take you, who possess
the Sharingan, down...
What...? A Substitution...
Sorry to disappoint you.
I don't need to use the Sharingan
on the likes of you...
This way!
Naruto!
If we follow this...
Yes, we should be able
to reach Naruto.
Unfortunately, I cannot allow you
to avenge the blood of the fallen.
The least I can do for you,
out of charity,
is send you to the same place
your father and brother are.
I don't care.
Why don't you just kill me
in one stroke?
You know when to give up, huh?
They're all dead.
I'm the only one left in this world.
Now that I am unable to take revenge,
I have no more reason to live.
You're a courageous girl,
aren't you?
All right, I'll grant your wish.
Resign yourself!
Wake up.
Save Toki... Save my little sister...
I entrusted the future of
the Land of Birds to my younger sister
and gave her the watch.
But Toki became obsessed
with her desire for revenge.
I, a dead soul, cannot change
my younger sister's heart
which is stalled in time.
I'm begging you,
please make my younger sister's time
begin to move again towards the future.
What was that just now?
Die!
What?
Hold it!
Naruto!
I met your elder brother in
a dream a little while ago.
Elder Brother?
It wasn't the wish of
your elder brother Sagi
that you avenge his death.
He wanted to leave the care
of this land in your hands.
But...
For Chishima's sake too...
you must make this
Land of Bird a great country...
That's why you must live, Toki...
Naruto...
It doesn't make any difference to me.
The two of you are going
to die here in any case.
Hey, Hoki, you want this Land, right?
What...
But a person with an impure heart,
with a heart bent on revenge,
cannot govern this land.
The reason this was such
a wonderful country was because
Chishima and Sagi and Toki's hearts
were all connected.
Even if you use dirty tricks
to gain status,
you will never be able to control
the hearts of the people...
Speak for yourself, squirt!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You Leaf Village greenhorn!
I'll send you down into hell first
to meet up with the others!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
– It ain't gonna be that easy!
– Then try to spot the real McCoy!
What...!
Let's go!
– Damn, which is the real one?
Naruto, hang in there...
I wouldn't have thought the real McCoy
would come straight out
when using Shadow Clones...
I was hoping you'd let me
have some fun...
So that was your caliber,
after all, huh.
Those without power should
hurry up and die!
Better not underestimate me!
The battle is not yet won!
You impertinent little...!
Now!
U-zu-ma-ki...
The real McCoy is... Over here!
Uzumaki Barrage!
I did it!
Chishima!
Chishima... Don't die, Chishima!
Don't...leave me...all alone!
Open your eyes...
Please!
Lady Toki...
Chishima...!
I'm so relieved!
Thank you, Naruto!
I was just carrying out my mission.
More importantly...
Make that guy pay dearly for
his crimes, okay.
Yes.
I'm sure that Sagi is happy
about this too.
You met...you met Elder Brother Sagi...
Yeah, in a dream.
But even if it was in a dream,
it doesn't change the fact that
he asked me to do something.
What did Elder Brother say to you?
Well, he said something about
starting up your time again.
My time?
He said he wanted you to forget
about things like revenge
and instead live for the future.
Elder Brother...
Hey!
Naruto...
Kakashi Sensei, Neji, Tenten!
Gimme a break...
I can't get paid my extra money
now that Moso,
the guy who signs the paycheck,
got nabbed...
Come on, resign yourself...
But...
It looks like the Wandering Ninja
are going to get a really stiff sentence.
Yeah... And Toki was finally able to
break the curse of seeking revenge...
Hey, it's gonna start!
Down on your knees!
Ohhh...wow...
I must apologize for having
deceived everyone
by using my brother's name fraudulently,
and claiming
the title of feudal lord.
In a case such as this,
it may well be proper to hand over
the title of feudal lord to someone else.
However, if you will forgive me,
I would like to ask you to
allow me to work
on behalf of Land of Birds
as your lord.
For my deceased father Owashi,
and brother Sagi...
And for my dear friend Chishima
who loves this country so dearly...
Lady Toki...
As long as there is breath in my body,
I would like to work positively
to rebuild this country.
She's doing an excellent job, isn't she?
Toki, awesome!
As you wish, Lady Toki...
It appears that
you all agree too, correct?
– Yes, sir!
Thank you...
To Komei...for accepting me
as your feudal lord...to everyone...
And to the young Ninja who taught me
what it is that I should really
stake my life on...
You're embarrassing me...
Land of Birds
Please take the best of care
along the road now.
Fare thee well.
Chishima, be nice to Toki, okay?
Thank you, Naruto.
Please come back to visit
again soon.
Sure, next time I'd love
to visit without a mission.
Goodbye.
Goodbye. Be well...
See you...
Toki...she was really kind
and gorgeous too, wasn't she?
I'm certain that the Land of Birds
will become a wonderful land again,
just like it was in the old days.
Yeah.
By the way, Naruto...
did you really meet Sagi's ghost?
You gotta be kidding.
There's no such things as ghosts...
that was all in a dream.
I'm not so sure it was just a dream.
Wh-What the heck are you
talking about?!
Do you remember that Cursed Warrior
we cornered the very first time?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, he was empty inside.
Th-This...?
The inside of it is empty.
Yeah, but that was just sort
of gimmick, right?
Some kind of string or piece
of wire or something...
No, I definitely saw it with my Byakugan.
Now that you mention it,
you said there was no sign of life,
right, Neji?
Yeah...I didn't feel a speck of life
from that Cursed Warrior.
In other words, there was
a ghost there.
So that was a real ghost, after all?!
Calm down, Naruto.
That's not true...
That's not true!
Tell me that's not true!
The wind blows, Ah...
The pain,
The memories won't disappear
What should be brought along?
Assemble them into a piece.
There is no second chance, never
How foolish it is to throw away
Acting so innocently, Ah...
The images.
It probably will not end
Burn that love-filled heart,
Sail across a thousand dreams
Running freely
To take hold of the world in hand
The clouds scatter
The sun sets yet again
The solo parade begins to move.
Adventure, Lucky Day, Heart Beat, Rising,
Decisive, Encounter, Life, Mutual Love
– Pork!
– Chicken!
– Beef!
– What, is this a guessing game?
– Bean sprouts!
– Spinach!
– Green onions!
– I got it! It's Stir-fried Beef & Vegetables!
– Egg!
– Nori!
Seaweed!
Umm...Stir-fried Beef, vegetable,
and seaweed in egg sauté?!
– Menma!
– Char-siu!
Naruto!
I got it, ramen! It's ramen, isn't it?!
Wrong answer!
Sakura, you're so slow to get it!
You should know
if we've said it this far.
Miso-tonkotsu ramen with char-siu
and eggs on top.
Isn't that right?!
Like heck I'd get it, Cha!
Next time:
"Mix It! Stretch it! Boil it up!
Burn Copper Pot! Burn!"