Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, "See you..."
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I'm not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
Stop that!
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Naruto Uzumaki has just arrived!
I'm not handing Gantetsu over
to you, no matter what!
That's...
It can't be...!
To Each His Own Path
You... You mean you ripped
through my net?!
I can cut through a weak flimsy net
like that with a single bite!
It's useless! You won't be able to
tear through my Mesh Cage!
I'm gonna have Gantetsu back!
I'm telling you, it's useless!
Damn it! I can't get this thing off!
Here, just die already!
–Naruto!
You're mine!
Too bad!
So it's you who's gonna die,
after all!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Go!
This is the end for you!
What's that?!
Shura, on the scene!
The kid! The kid inside that net
knows where the treasure is!
Good job, Monju!
Akio!
Akio...?!
–Akio! Bro!
Thank you.
Gantetsu...
I heard you say the name Akio,
just now...
Who in the world is that kid?
That kid... Akio...
He's your...
He's your little brother.
Th-That's a lie!
My younger brother...
My younger brother has...
In those flames...
Akio...
You...killed him...!
No!
Gantetsu hasn't killed anybody!
He rescued us! He rescued Akio!
Five years ago.
I had developed a distate for
the Ninja Dropout's way...
I found myself carrying Akio...
Akio!
Elder brother!
No! You'll inhale smoke!
Damn it!
I thought I could change a little
if I could only save that child.
But that's not what happened!
I just continued to create
victims like Akio.
So that's why I started planning
what's happening right now
in order to exterminate
the Ninja Dropouts.
So that's what happened...
–Gantetsu!
–Gantetsu, are you all right?
You're not hurt, are you?
I'm glad you're ok.
They are children from the houses
that the Ninja Dropouts attacked...
Using the money Gantetsu poached
from the gang,
Akio, the oldest, has been
taking care of them.
Gantetsu is just like
the central figure of a family.
I can't believe this...
You mean that...the kid who
was there just now was...
Akio!!
Where are you going...Gantetsu?!
To the Ninja Dropouts' hideout.
I'm gonna get...Akio back!
I will get Akio back! Your only job
is to guide me there!
Don't interfere!
Todoroki, I understand how you feel.
However, Gantetsu saved Akio
and all these other kids
from the Ninja Dropouts!
Besides, there's something
you should do before that!
Don't mess around with me!
Even so, this guy...Gantetsu...
is a member of the Ninja Dropouts.
The Ninja Dropouts killed my parents!
You're absolutely right.
My own crime will never
be washed away.
As soon as I get Akio back...
you can...do whatever you like to me!
I'm going, too!
Me, too!
Then, Sakura, please look
after the children!
Leave it to me!
Todoroki...
I've continued hating that guy
for five years...
What am I supposed to do now...?
Damn it!
In any case, we've got to take care
of your little brother right now!
I know that!
This time for sure...
I'll rescue Akio!
Where did you stash our treasure?!
Where's your hideout?!
Come on! Talk!
I'll never...tell you!
You little brat!
That's the Ninja Dropouts' hideout...
That residence belongs
to Shura, the leader.
I'm pretty sure that's where Akio will be.
Akio...
Oh! Hey! Todoroki! Wait!
Damn!
This ain't good! They'll detect us!
Leaf Hurricane!
Let me handle this situation!
I leave it to you, Bushy-Brows.
Akio!
This way.
I'm pretty sure that Akio is
being tortured in the basement...
That guy was once a Ninja.
There's no telling what
he'll try to do.
I'll go first.
Akio!
W-Wait!
Akio...!
Gantetsu...!
You jerk...!
Don't come over here!
Gantetsu!
Akio!
Hey! Gantetsu!
So only one animal got caught
in the net, huh...?
Shura!
He's one stubborn brat.
He never unsealed his lips.
I'll use another method to
get back the treasure.
After I've killed the lot of you!
Naruto, pursue Shura!
We'll be fine! Iron bars
like this are nothing!
Got it!
Todoroki, I'm leaving this
in your hands!
Farewell.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Todoroki, you take care of Akio!
Todoroki!
Blood Rain!
I won't forgive you...
no matter what!
Rasengan!
So that's what happened...
Gantetsu...
that's how you protected Akio...
Yet I... I...!
Gantetsu! Give me Akio!
Elder brother...
you came to rescue me, after all...
Hang in there, Akio!
My elder brother...
Todoroki, it's really you, isn't it?
This spells the end of the Ninja Dropout.
Yeah...
That's right.
But where is Naruto?
Hey!
Naruto Uzumaki! On the scene...!
Naruto! Lee!
Akio!
Akio's back!
It's Akio...!
Are you all right, Akio?!
Yeah...
Oh my gosh, you're hurt!
I'm fine. It's nothing!
Sakura, could you
take care of his wound?
Leave it to me.
Take care of him.
Apologies for the inconvenience...
Let's head to the capital.
I just cannot forgive you.
But it is true that you rescued Akio.
The Ninja Dropouts
have been annihilated.
Gantetsu got caught up
and died in the fighting
that ensued while being escorted.
Elder brother...
Todoroki...
Yeah! Great! That's great!
You're gonna stay here, right?
Huh?
You're gonna stay here with Gantetsu
and the other children, right?
I haven't been a good brother...
But you are an irreplaceable
elder brother for those children.
Elder brother...
What's this...?
This is the souvenir that
I didn't have a chance to
give you back then.
Elder brother... Thank you.
Let's go! Ninja!
Okay!
–Good bye!
–Take care, everyone!
–See you!
–Bye!
Hey... How are we gonna
get out of this forest...
without Gantetsu?!
We can't go back now!
We took this path earlier
on too, didn't we...?
I'm starving...
I can't go on.
Hey! Somebody rescue us!
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I'm told that
there is no bright future
I'll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Naruto, what on earth were you thinking?
What? I only brought an injured person
to the hospital.
But to bring an outsider
into the village...
But I'm sure he is not a bad guy at all.
I understand your feelings,
but he has amnesia.
There is a possibility that
he's an enemy spy.
Please, Grandma.
I'll make an exception,
just this one time.
But you will be his keeper, and will be
held accountable for all his actions.
That's all.
Next time: "Vanished Memories"