Hey boys,
listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
Plea from a Friend
That's Naruto?
What is this intimidating power?
And what was that
red Chakra earlier on?
Is this guy a monster?
What the heck are you?!
Your friend!
That's why I'm telling you
I'm not gonna let the likes
of Orochimaru get you!
I'm telling you that I'll stop you...
even if it means breaking
every bone in your arm and legs!
Fire Style:
Fire Ball Jutsu!
Come on! Wake up, already!
If you don't come to your senses,
I'll have to break your bones
so that you can't move
and I'll take you home that way, Sasuke!
Shut up...
What the heck do you,
who has neither parents nor brothers,
think you understand?
What makes you think that you,
who's been all alone from the start,
can understand anything about me?!
It's because I have the ties
that I feel this agony.
How could you possibly understand...
what it feels like to lose all that!
It's true that I can't understand...
how it feels to really
have parents or brothers...
However...
It's my treat today...
Eat your fill!
Yippee!
When I'm with Iruka Sensei,
I imagine...
-Dig in!
Ninja, first of all, need to
warm their inner man.
Hey! Hey! Don't get too carried away
and overeat!
If this is...
what it feels like to have a dad.
When I'm with you...
Idiot, idiot, idiot...
What was that, you loser?!
I'm not gonna lose to you,
no matter what!
Go ahead and say
whatever you want.
How about this?
Better not start feeling
too comfortable.
I wonder...if having a brother
feels something like that.
Why is it, Naruto...?
Why is it that you go to
this extent for me...?
For me it's a tie that
I've finally been able to have!
That's why I'm gonna stop you.
It's too late, Naruto...
It's already too late.
I can't go back anymore.
Come, Naruto!
In that case,
I just have to cut that tie.
Cut, huh?
Then why wear that headband now?
I'll acknowledge you...
You're strong.
And the reason for that is
you're someone who knows
the pain of solitude as I do.
And that pain makes people stronger.
And for that very reason,
by cutting that tie,
I will be able to obtain
even greater strength.
I will fight you now on equal terms.
However...
You won't even be able to
inflict a scratch on my forehead.
That's something that
won't change in the least.
It seems that whatever I say
won't have any effect anymore, huh?
Sasuke!
I'm done with talking...
From here on, it's only fighting.
Come!
I'm able to see...
I'm now able to see
this guy's movements...
which I wasn't able to see before.
I'm able to see them!
Sasuke's moving completely
different from a few moments ago.
But I couldn't care less!
In any case, I can't afford to lose!
Damn it!
It must be the influence of my body
getting used to the state of Curse Mark.
When he moves...
by the subtle movements in
the way he exerts his strength...
I can vividly see
an image of his next move.
With my level of "eyes,"
I don't need to use unnecessary Chakra
and can instead preserve it.
The Curse Mark takes
too much Chakra.
If I can see this much...
I can time my attacks to the images of
Naruto's movements as I foresee them.
This is no good...
He's totally reading my movements.
Damn it!
Oh, there you are.
There's no mistake it's this way, right?
Right.
We better hurry.
I have a bad premonition.
Sasuke!
Fire Style:
Dragon Flame Jutsu!
Sa-su-ke...
It's too late, Naruto.
It's too late now! Naruto!
You're weak, aren't you, kid?
You better be grateful to me...
and to the Fourth Hokage
who contained me within
the likes of you!
What's going on?
What was that just now?
Even if I'm able to read
Naruto's movements completely...
his Chakra makes
a separate move of its own.
It seems like the Chakra itself is moving
in accordance with its own will...
Even with my "eyes"
I'm unable to read it completely.
That red Chakra...
that's not an ordinary Chakra!
Your target is Naruto, after all.
To abduct Naruto
is the No.1 priority
placed by our organization, Akatsuki!
I see...
It appears that you have
some kind of special power.
Now I understand!
Fire Style:
Fire Ball Jutsu!
That Chakra is protecting him?!
Calm down.
I won't be caught as long as
I fight from distance.
Damn it... This is incredible!
All I can do is dodge...
Please let me get there in time.
Damn it, gimme a break...
If I get tainted by this power ...
I don't even know what
will happen to me in the end...
But, it can't be helped,
can it, Naruto?
It is certainly true
that you were special...
However...
I am even more special than you.
Sasuke!
When I recalled the parts one by one,
I felt as though
I had understood everything
Faded words
which I kept so close to me
Speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
and this distant yearning for you
I live,
simply repeating this cycle
Held in my two hands
A droplet of time
Softly clutching forgotten memories
Lost words
I'll keep these thoughts...
Damn! My body hurts!
And to make it worse,
I've completely lost feeling
in my left arm!
Apparently this power
isn't something that
I can just keep on using continuously!
But ...I can't give up!
My next blow is
going to be the end!
Next episode: "The End of Tears"