Press down hard on the gas
That's right, there's no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We're speeding through life,
squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you're not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we'll go far off into the distance.
...bring it to an end swiftly!
I won't let you do anything.
First move, a surefire victory!
Wow! That's amazing!
What's with his body?!
I dislocate every joint
and with Chakra, I can control
my softened body at will.
With Chakra...?
I can also squeeze until
your bones break.
I'll rapidly tighten as long
as you don't give up.
I don't know what kind of
ninja tool you'll use...
but if I keep doing this to your body,
it will make no difference.
I can break your neck right now.
So hurry up and give up.
No.
Do you want to die?!
Idiot. You're the one who's
going to die.
His neck is broken.
What?
How ridiculous...
Phew...
Idiot.
I went a little overboard and
ended up killing you.
W-What?
Okay, now it's my turn.
T-This is a Puppet!
T-That's the real body?
He's...a Puppet Master...
He's controlling the puppet with
Chakra from his hand!
G-Give up...!
If your bones get crushed,
you'll be able to bend even more, huh?
For once, I was close to stopping
the match in the middle.
The winner, by an inability
to continue the match by the opponent,
is Kankuro.
Two against one is hitting
below the belt!
Is that fair, Kakashi Sensei?!
It's not particularly hitting
below the belt.
It's a puppet, after all.
That's the Puppet Master Jutsu.
He's controlling the puppet with Chakra.
It's the same as using
a ninja tool... like shuriken.
They're all great Chakra users...
I thought I could make it
kind of far with Chakra.
Kunoichi Rumble:
The Rivals Get Serious!
Ino...!
You've got the jitters,
don't you, Sakura?
Wha...?!
Even Sasuke collapsed.
I mean, it felt like it was because
it was Sasuke that it ended at that.
What'll happen if you take part?
It might be best if you quit!
Something like that
won't work on me!
It's okay! I can tough it out
this time around, too.
Quit? Who?
I can hardly wait.
Cha! Bring it on!
Now then, to continue,
we will begin the fourth battle.
Man, man, nothing but
weirdoes all over the place!
Don't you say that!
-You've got a point.
-You, too, Sakura?!
This isn't the time to be laughing.
Sakura Haruno vs. Ino Yamanaka
I never thought...
I'd be fighting you, Sakura.
And what's more, so soon.
Ino was a standout
among the rookie Kunoichi.
With Sakura as her opponent,
will she go...no,
can she go with serious intent?
To think it would be those
two of all people.
Things have gotten gloomy.
I wonder if Ino'll be okay.
That's for sure.
What're you going to do, Ino?
Sakura! Good luck! Don't lose!
Begin!
Oh, no. I knew it.
Sakura's totally blowing Ino away!
Idiot.
Say what?!
If you're not an idiot,
you must be sleeping, aren't you?
Who...?!
Sure enough, they are Kunoichi.
So this is their level of
hand-to-hand combat?
What?!
-It's not because they're Kunoichi.
-Huh?
It's just that those two are lukewarm.
There's no man or woman in battle.
Lukewarm...?
There!
Kunoichi must learn
not only Ninjutsu...
but also a wide range of
knowledge and refinement as women.
If you don't blend into enemy territory
and conduct yourselves as a normal woman...
you'll have it rough on occasions
such as when you work as spies.
Today's class is flower arranging.
Now then, everyone.
Let's gather flowers we like.
Yes, ma'am!
Ino, wait up!
You're such a klutz.
I'm...not good at stuff like this.
What about you, Ino?
That's no good, considering
your name's Sakura.
Listen. There are tricks
to things like this.
You know, as for flower arranging,
after you've decided on a main flower,
you add other flowers to decorate.
All flowers can't be
asserting themselves.
For example...look.
You can see those cosmos
flowers over there, right...?
For example, if they were
the main flowers...
the thoroughwort flowers
you picked are throw-ins!
As contrasted with
spring cherry blossoms,
cosmos flowers have the
name of autumn cherry blossom
and are the prettiest flowers of the fall.
Also, they're flowers with
the original meaning of "harmony,"
so any autumn grass would
go perfectly with them.
So? Do I look as nice
as the cosmos flowers?
Say, say, am I cute?
Uh...yeah.
Say. What's with the pause?
You look like you're having
so much fun.
Billboard Brow!
You've recently reached
adolescence, haven't you?
Don't get too full of yourself!
Ami!
Sorry! You have such
a beautiful cylinder-shaped body
I mistook you for a vase
and put flowers in you.
Ino!
Shinobi flower aconite.
It has weak toxicity, but is poisonous,
so you'd best spit them out.
Sensei!
Only the root is poisonous, though.
Ino is great.
She knows everything,
is stylish, and is cute.
Even that shuriken skill.
Her Ninjutsu is great, too...
Compared to that, I...
Sakura?
If you're a cosmos flower...
then am I a thoroughwort?
What're you saying?!
What?
Let me see...
In a manner of speaking,
you are not a flower, but still a bud!
You're right.
At this point in time...
I don't even plan to fight
over Sasuke with you.
What did you say?
You and Sasuke don't go together,
and I'm totally stronger than you!
You are beneath my notice!
Sakura! Do you know who
you're lipping off to?!
Don't press your luck, crybaby Sakura!
169.0101:14:49:1101:14:50:24I feel like...
I feel like Sakura
was out of line!
Ino's eyes show incredible anger.
She's scary.
Hmm. That's not it...
Huh?
Sakura's not the kind of
kid to do things
like needlessly flaunt her
own power and hurt people.
She doesn't like having Ino
taking pity on her and pulling punches.
I'm a bud, huh...?
Say, Ino...
What?
Why...did you give this ribbon to me?
Actually...
I thought it'd be a waste for
you to wilt away as a bud.
There's no point if flowers don't bloom.
For all we know...
it just might...
become a flower
more beautiful than a cosmos.
Thank you...
Ino!
Okay Sakura.
Let's hurry and go pick flowers.
O-Okay.
What's wrong, Sakura?
I got some dirt in
my eye when I fell...
You're so clumsy.
Ino...
All along, I believed in the
words you gave me then.
I really thought that it would
be nice if it were so.
It would be nice if I could get
a beautiful flower to bloom...
I set my sights on you because
I wanted to be like you all along.
Thanks to that, I'm here now.
So, Ino, I want to fight you seriously.
If I can't surpass you at your
most serious, there's no point.
W-What's with Sakura?
Hmm.
Why are those two getting that heated?!
Alas, he doesn't even understand
the reason why he lashes out at Sasuke.
Well, a rival is a mysterious thing,
is the point.
Huh?
Oh, hi...
My rival from youth, Kakashi...
Oh, how hip and galling that
nonsensical reaction is.
I...
got on the same team as Sasuke.
Why are you telling me now...?
I won't lose to you anymore, Ino.
No matter what happens,
I won't lose to you either, Sakura!
The ribbon...
I'm giving back the ribbon.
I gave you that ribbon.
Besides, a headband is something
you put on your head, right?
From here on, I'm no longer
a girl who will run after you, Ino.
When I put this on my head,
it will be as a female Shinobi
who can't lose to you.
That's a good idea...
Me, too...
until that time.
I understand...Sakura.
– This time for sure...
– with full strength...
– a fair...fight!
Hey, can you hear it?
The clear, blue sky goes on and on
The ocean spans limitlessly
Please keep that smile on your face forever
Or else I'll cry
You won't have to search around you
It's all ok now.
Everyone is inside
this hand
when you want to cry,
and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born, and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia, feel the telepathy
Hey, can you hear it?
Since when did she get this strong?!
Sure enough, Ino's great.
But I won't lose.
I absolutely will not lose.
It can't be. She's evenly
matched with me now?!
I'm not who I used to be.
– The next hit is the decisive blow!
Next episode:
"The Ultimate Battle: Cha!"
I cannot concede this battle,
even if it's the last thing I do!