Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
Shikamaru! Ino! Choji!
Heh... Well...
It's a drag,
but it's Lady Tsunade's orders.
Old Lady Tsunade's...?
You're pursuing Mizuki, right?
Y-Yeah...!
And...who are these guys here?
Fujin and Raijin.
Fujin...and Raijin?
Yeah. They're a little weak upstairs,
but their brute strength...
is Herculean, surpassing even that
of the Legendary Sannin.
Are you serious?
Damn... It looks like he really means it.
Pretty amazing that they are able
to hold out
against the Shadow Possession Jutsu
only by using their strength...
It looks like this is gonna turn
into a troublesome situation again...
Leave this to us... You go pursue Mizuki!
We'll be fine!
Leave it to us!
Awright!
But be careful!
Those guys are crazy like monsters!
Yeah... I can see that.
Go, Naruto!
Thanks, guys!
We better hurry, Naruto!
Your opponents are this way!
You guys... Doing this kind of thing
to us brothers!
Don't even think we're gonna
let you leave here alive!
Well... I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Choji! Ino! Let's hurry and
take care of these guys!
– Okay!
A New Formation: Ino-Shika-Cho!
Wait, Mizuki!
Looks like I'm gonna
have a little fun, Iruka!
This way?
Mizuki! Where are you?
D-Damn!
This is Genjutsu...
Release!
After Genjutsu... Puppets come, huh?
His Jutsu are diverse.
And moreover, the timing of
his Jutsu are superb...
I was really close to being taken down...
I wouldn't have imagined that
he could have such full command
of the high level Jutsu...that Mizuki.
I guess I can praise you on catching that
the Puppet was real.
However... I wonder how long
you're gonna be able to continue
to engage in my game, Iruka!
Where's this...?!
This ain't good...
They're able to repel
Shadow Possession Jutsu
using only their strength...
Shikamaru, I'll go!
Choji!
Stop it! Their strength is unearthly!
I'll hold this guy down...
While I do that take care
of the other one!
Okay! All right, let's go, Ino!
Leave it to me!
Ninja Art: Mind Transfer Jutsu!
What's the matter, Elder Brother?
A success!
Oops...
All right!
Formation, Ino-Shika-Cho completed!
Elder Brother!
What's the matter, Elder Brother?!
Iruka Sensei...
I'll catch up with you in no time...
Please be safe!
How do you like my Jutsu, Iruka?
Pretty good for being self-taught,
wouldn't you say?
I can't understand...
You have the ability to use
such high-level Ninjutsu to this degree...
why would you waste it?!
As always, trying to impose
your morals on me, huh...?!
You're so lukewarm! You're so naïve!
Don't you start preaching me!
I won't acknowledge you, no matter what!
I consistently hardened my heart
and carried out my missions...
Despite that, those guys in the village...
No matter how strong I was!
No matter how many enemies
I took down in my missions!
Those guys didn't even attempt
to acknowledge me!
Saying we're comrades,
it's all about teamwork...
They were all bound by stupid rules!
His target's the Secret Manuscript.
Backup Mizuki!
Right!
Hey! Are you all right?!
I-I can't feel my leg...
What do you think, Mizuki?
It's no good.
It's unfortunate, but he can no longer...
I see...
All right! Let's withdraw!
Hurry!
Yeah...
It's unfortunate, but...
Guys who are of no use on the battleground
only become a ball and chain...
Even though it's just a minor injury,
you won't be able to move from this place...
If you're wanna blame someone,
I suggest you blame
your own helpless self!
I simply carried out
my mission faithfully.
And despite that, those guys
in the village...
Not one of them even attempted
to acknowledge me...
Why?! Why didn't anybody
acknowledge my strength?!
Why?! Iruka...!
When you and even that Nine-Tailed brat
are acknowledged, why only me...?
It's still not too late.
If you pay for your crimes
and start afresh,
the people in the village will certainly...
How cocky! Don't preach to me!
You're just the same as
those other guys in the village!
You disdain me, don't you?!
Mizuki...
Everything...
That's right... Everything began that day...
What are you gonna do,
getting nervous now?
Mizuki...
It finally takes place tomorrow,
doesn't it?
The Academy's teacher recruitment exam...
Yeah... It's weighing heavily on me.
I'm envious of you.
Your scores are better than mine.
You'll breeze right through
tomorrow's exam.
Not quite... Well, in any case,
let's both do our best!
Yeah!
Damn!
Lie low!
That was close, Iruka!
Yeah...
Mizuki... Thank you.
You really helped me out!
It's mutual... Come on, let's hurry!
Ninja Academy Exam Results
Number 7 - Iruka Umino
I-I did it... I did it!
Mizuki...
Exam Office
Now then, regarding Mizuki...
we will adopt a wait-and-see attitude.
Yes, it can't be helped.
I agree... The questions that were raised
at the time of that mission to
recover the Secret Manuscript...
Until those are completely cleared up...
It can't be helped, can it?
According to the autopsy report...
the cause of death to that corpse
was given as suffocation.
In Mizuki and the others' reports,
it stated that the leg injury
was not that serious...
I understand...
He's brilliant but it can't be helped.
I was just carrying out the mission
that I was assigned to do!
Can you understand how miserable
the life I've led has been since then?!
Huh? Iruka?!
You have no idea, do you?
I have undergone so many hardships,
and you, who has had it so easy...
Which one of us is the true Shinobi...
Let's clarify that once and for all,
shall we?!
Now then come! Iruka!
Mizuki... Where are you?!
You don't have any intention
of reforming yourself, do you?!
Don't make me say the same thing
over and over again!
Then I'll bring this to an end now...
It's very unfortunate, though!
What a tearjerker...
It makes me happy too, Iruka...
Elder Brother?!
What's the matter, Elder Brother?!
Hey... You came back, Elder Brother!
Uh, Elder Brother?
What did you guys do to...
to Elder Brother?!
I hijacked him! Idiot!
Wh-What the heck...?!
What?!
Elder Brother! Get up! Wake up!
These guys!
Owww...!
Are you okay, Ino?
I-I think I'm...
not okay! My gorgeous face is...!
Good grief... Gimme a break...
C-Choji!
Choji!
Are you okay?!
I-I'm fine...
Sorry... Feels like I fell asleep a little.
Hey, Elder Brother... You woke up.
Damn. Can't be helped...
Guess I have no choice but to use
that thing.
Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
Elder Brother...!
H-How dare you!
We're close. Mizuki may have
set a trap so be careful!
I know that!
It was so much fun to be behind bars...
The moldiness... The dampness...
The gloominess...
Pitch black year round!
But for that very reason that
I was able master techniques
that an ordinary Shinobi would
not be able to possess...
Even in this darkness...
I can get an intense sense of your energy...
What's the matter? Are you done already?
There's no time to be spaced out, Iruka.
I'm gonna take my time
and have fun with this...
Take my time, got it?
All right! Me too!
Wait! If you go in there right now
using Mind Transfer Jutsu,
my Jutsu will affect you too!
If you think you're the only one
who's learned a new Jutsu,
you're very wrong!
Ninja Art: Mind Destruction Jutsu!
Wh-What's the matter, Raijin?!
R-Raijin... What are you doing?!
Heh... Not bad...
"Ino collection,"
my new spring season Jutsu!
We're close!
That's it! That building!
All right! Just one last spurt!
How about it?
Have your eyes adjusted a little?
For guys like you who have lived
their lives in the light,
darkness is an inconvenience, isn't it?
Damn! Where are you?!
Hey, Iruka, weren't you saying that
you were going to bring this to an end?
I see! By end,
you must have been
talking about yourself, huh?!
Heh! Just a little bit!
Hang in there, Ino!
Leave it to me!
Damn...!
Damn! Unbelievable idiot strength!
Th-Those jerks...
I-I can't hold them any longer!
If we put a stop to the Jutsu right now,
everything will go to waste...
Think... Think about the next move...
Bear with it, Ino!
Leave it to me!
You're just gonna be sent flying again!
Ino, just be quiet and watch!
Even the big-boned guy can make
quite a showing once he decides to do it!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
Both Hands!
Choji...
I can't let just Ino get
all the good parts!
I'm the number one handsome
Big-Boned Ninja!
Good work, Choji! You're so cool!
Huh... That Choji...
New Formation! Ino-Shika-Cho completed!
It's strange...
Any hint of Mizuki in the air
has vanished...
It's too quiet...
That's not it...
Even deeper...
Footsteps? No... It's not ...
It's different from the sound
of footsteps...
Finer and smaller...
Continuous...
sound.
Paper Bombs?!
Wh-What is that...?!
Wh-What happened here?!
Iruka Sensei?!
Iruka Sensei!
Crappy news pass us by
And you become speechless
My voice is way too soft
So you don't answer
You're crying Crying alone
What can I do? I'm crying too
"Let my lonely scream ring out
through the night"
I'll thrash this confused era
with my speed
Yeah
And I'll thrash this confused night
with my speed
Yeah
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar
and my speed
Yeah
This sinking world and its evil bastards,
I'll kick their butt
Yeah
No way! What happened to Iruka Sensei?!
The scent ends here.
In any case,
we just have to search the perimeter.
Everything is in pieces. Damn it!
Please be safe, Iruka Sensei!
Hush! Be quiet, Naruto!
We have a company.
It seems someone is after us.
Next episode: "Orochimaru's Shadow!"