I want to try and gather
the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long way to go
on that road.
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that...
What were you gazing at?
Encounter! The Boy With a Star's Name
Shizune!
Is anything wrong?!
What is it...?
It's a protection commission
from the Village Hidden in the Stars.
Is there some kind
of problem with that?
You've never heard about it, Shizune?
The Village Hidden in the Stars
is small in terms of scale,
but they are very proud and
have often caused trouble...
So, will you accept?
I can't simply disregard it.
What...?
Since you-know-what
is in that village.
And it seems they'll form
a three-man team
with Neji as the squad leader.
But the Village Hidden in the Stars
is a Shinobi village, isn't it?
Then they should do
their own protecting
without asking others.
There are often instances
of a small village
with friendly relations
seeking cooperation.
In particular, that village is small
and it seems there aren't
that many Shinobi.
No kidding. But why's a place
like that being targeted?
Actually...!
It all happened 200 years ago.
A star fell in the village!
Those stars like in the sky,
not ninja stars or something?!
Right! It seems
there's a mysterious power in the star
that has an effect on Chakra!
That's a superstition!
In the first place, no way has
a star ever come falling down!
It's true!
It's actually been targeted
several times until now
by Shinobi of other lands.
By Shinobi of other lands?
Mysterious power, huh?
Indeed, it does seem that someone
like Orochimaru would target it...
All right, I guess I'll be participating
in this one too!
What?! But the three-man team's
already been determined.
I've got an ace up my sleeve...
Amaguriama Sweet Shop
Listen up. I'll take the lead from here.
There's danger before
entering the village.
Okay, got it!
Hi, guys!
I'll go on ahead and be waiting!
Naruto! Hold it!
That idiot!
Umm, what's Naruto doing
in a place like this?
Like I know.
Lady Tsunade, there was a report
that Naruto has joined up
with Neji's squad.
Yes. I added him to
the Village Hidden in the Stars mission.
Why...?!
Those four proved themselves
in the Katabami Gold Mine...
and things will quiet down
in the village here, too.
You'd change an already determined
three-man squad just for that reason?!
Lady Tsunade?!
Rare Roasted Chestnut Bean Jelly
with gold leaf candy from Amaguriama?
Could it be that was from Naruto...?
70.0101:06:50:2901:06:52:26Tea! Hurry!
Mizura!
You okay?!
I'm fine...
I told you not to push yourself!
But, I don't want to fall behind
everyone's training...
What're you doing
during your training?!
Mizura suddenly keeled
over in pain...
Take him to the medical treatment room.
Yes sir.
I'll go, too.
Hokuto by herself is
enough for an escort.
Sumaru, you have a mission.
All right! I'm here first!
Once I cross this valley,
I'll be in the Land of Bears.
The Village Hidden in the Stars
is close.
Wha...?!
You little...!
Ninja Art: Kujaku...
Protection!
This guy blocked Kunai knives
with Chakra!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Cut!
Damn it!
Incredible Chakra!
Wait!
This guy's an enemy...
He suddenly attacked!
You're Leaf Shinobi, right?
Are you from
the Village Hidden in the Stars?
I'm Sumaru.
I came to pick you guys up.
Then why did you do such a thing...?
Look at that.
Huh?
The border of the Land of Bears
is constantly filled with poison gas.
It's also serves as
a natural fortress
against invasion from other lands.
So this is the danger
you were talking about, huh?
Isn't that great, Naruto?
You owe Sumaru your life!
It's the beginning of
a beautiful friendship
between the Leaf
and the Hidden Star Village.
Give me a break.
Was it none of my concern?
I could have just watched
and not done anything...
I am Akahoshi
and I serve as the deputy Hoshikage
of the Village Hidden in the Stars.
Deputy...Hoshikage?
Due to the sudden passing
of the Third Hoshikage one year ago,
presently there is
no Hoshikage in this village...
But, I heard the only ones who can
refer to themselves as a Kage
are the leaders of
the Five Great Hidden Villages...
That doesn't make any difference!
We are not inferior to you guys!
Even if we're small now,
this village will someday rival
the Hidden Villages of
the Five Great Nations!
At that time,
I'll become the true Hoshikage!
Silence!
Go back to the training ground.
H-Hey, wait up!
Oh! Naruto!
Naruto!
Now of all times!
Don't worry about him.
Please continue your story.
Forgive me.
As you say, the Shinobi in our village
are not qualified
to refer to themselves as a Kage.
However, in this village,
there is the star
that all the Kage in the Five
Great Hidden Villages also envy.
We will use the power
of the star and someday,
this can become a village which can
claim the Sixth Kage title.
So that star is being targeted, right?
Yes. Our search team
obtained some information.
Where'd that guy go?
Hey!
I finally caught up.
Was your name Omaru?
Not Omaru, Sumaru.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
But Sumaru's sure
an interesting name.
It's another name for
the star cluster Pleiades or Spring Star.
Everyone in this village has
a name associated with stars.
After all, this is a village
where a star fell.
I see...
What're you trying to elicit from me?
What? Nothing in particular.
I hadn't thanked you for earlier, so.
I can tell even if you give me
the runaround...
The people from other lands
are all after the star.
If you have that power,
you can stand above all
of the Hidden Villages, so...
Is your awesome Chakra
also the power of the star?
If they had that star,
would everyone have
the same Chakra as you?
No! The more tremendous the power,
the more hard work is required
to control it!
I'll work hard, work hard, work hard!
I'll become the Hoshikage!
Yeah! I look forward to working
with you at that time!
Huh...?
I'm also going to become
the Hokage someday, believe it!
You're a strange guy.
Really?
Intruder!
Protect the star!
But they really are collapsed entirely
from the center towards the outside.
When a star explodes in mid-air,
it seems they collapse like this.
That's the training area
where the star is enshrined.
Hurry up and show me the star.
No. People from other lands
aren't allowed beyond this spot.
But the star is over there, right?
I can't protect it
if I can't get close to it!
It's not like we trust you guys.
Geez, you're such a suspicious guy!
Why can't you trust us
who came here on a mission?!
This is my personality, you see.
It can't be?! No way.
I'll chase him down!
You go to your friends
in the training area.
Hurry!
Right. Okay.
Hokuto!
Sumaru... I'm sorry.
We couldn't protect the star...
You little!
It's ridiculous to do something
like steal in someone else's village
in broad daylight, you little thief!
Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Now, I won't let you getaway!
Ninja Art: Kujaku...
This Chakra?!
Beast!
Uh, oh! Move away!
Fire the Everywhere Shuriken Jutsu
towards that monster!
It's futile!
This is my real target!
I found your weak point.
The main body doesn't move
while controlling the Chakra!
Let's go! Clone Body Slam!
There are more ways to
use my Chakra!
That one hit hard.
Synthesis!
Damn...
Naruto!
Wings!
You can fly?!
You let him get away.
I'm sorry. But...
It was my mistake for
leaving it to you.
But as for him,
he used the same Ninja Art as you.
What's the meaning of this?!
Only those who perform
the star training
can use that Ninja Art...
Then you're saying
he's someone from this village?
I don't know...
I'm the one who let him get away.
I'll get the star back, no matter what!
The wind blows, Ah...
The pain,
The memories won't disappear
What should be brought along?
Assemble them into a piece.
There is no second chance, never
How foolish it is to throw away
Acting so innocently, Ah...
The images.
It probably will not end
Burn that love-filled heart,
Sail across a thousand dreams
Running freely
To take hold of the world in hand
The clouds scatter
The sun sets yet again
The solo parade begins to move.
Adventure, Lucky Day, Heart Beat, Rising,
Decisive, Encounter, Life, Mutual Love
I'm kind of bothered by
the village leader's attitude.
That the opponent used
the Ninja Art: Kujaku means...
Yeah, the attacker is definitely
a Shinobi from this village.
But, that old man didn't say anything.
It looks like there's some kind
of secret.
We need to investigate him.
Let's all split up.
Roger!
I'll get that star back,
no matter what.
Next: "The Remembered Lullaby"