Connecting old words
that have been used up
I just want to convey
my simple thoughts
That day's faint wind blows away
at the castle ruins of yesterday
I'll laugh with you
and live for the moment
Still that incident
will continue to trouble you, right?
That's why it must be good-bye
Leaving nothing behind,
let us share what is left
In time, we'll realize
that it was everything
And sadness will touch our cheeks,
creating a river of tears
Trembling thoughts swept
into a vortex and melting away
Fire Style! Fire Ball Jutsu!
Wh-What is that Jutsu?!
Damn it!
Chidori: One Thousand Birds!
I'll win no matter what!
Don't flatter yourself!
Stop it!
Bitter Rivals and Broken Bonds
It's a tranquil village as always...
The security sucks.
Humph! We should just massacre everybody
in such a seedy village.
Calm down, Sakon.
We haven't come here to fight.
Shut up, you chicken.
If you're scared,
you should just go home
and go to bed already.
I'm telling you to calm down, Tayuya.
You understand what
our job is this time, right?
Let's go. We escort our special guest.
Stop it!
Damn.
I can't stop completely.
Kakashi Sensei?
Naruto... That thing you just did was...
What're you guys doing
up on top of the hospital?
You went a bit too far
for just a fight, you two.
That Jutsu earlier, no mistake.
It's the Rasengan.
What's going on?
How can Naruto use that Jutsu...?
Were you going to kill Naruto, Sasuke?
What're you doing giving yourself over
to a sense of superiority?
The size of the Chidori there
wasn't one to be aimed
at a comrade of the same village.
Why such infantile behavior...?
Sure enough, a reunion with Itachi...
Sasuke.
Damn it!
Naruto...
How far will you go...?
Kakashi Sensei...
Whatever happened to teamwork?
Was it you... who taught him that technique?
I think Naruto is still too young
to be handling that Jutsu.
He could've killed Sasuke
had something gone wrong...
Even if it's a means of resisting
the Akatsuki,
to think you would teach Naruto
that Jutsu...
Right back at you...
That Chidori was also considerably hairy.
But I didn't think he was the kind of kid
who'd fire that Jutsu at his comrade.
Or is it that there's something quite
complicated between him and that kid?
Well, all sorts.
All sorts?
Quite simply, it's a relationship
like the one between you
and Orochimaru in the past.
I see.
To him, Sasuke is a comrade
and a rival at the same time...
Well, someone he considers an equal.
Most likely, he couldn't take
Sasuke's cheap provocation.
He's been chasing him...
Chasing him since the Academy days.
Are you hurt...
Scaredy-Cat?
Sasuke!
I won't lose to you!
For him, it's neither you nor me now...
More than anyone...
he wants to be recognized by Sasuke.
On the other side of the coin...
Sasuke feels the speed of Naruto's growth
at close range and feels inferior.
To the extent that he thinks
he himself isn't growing at all.
Scaredy-Cat?
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto has gotten strong...
And Sasuke...
I'm going to kill a certain man,
no matter what.
Revenge, huh...?
I wonder if Itachi
is frustrating that kid.
So Sasuke doesn't want
to acknowledge Naruto.
If he acknowledges him,
he just might deny himself
up to this point...
Rivalry is a difficult thing.
It's not a very good trend...
Maybe I'll do some scolding.
Then I leave Naruto to you.
Well, I have a mission.
And there's the Chidori thing, too...
Sakura.
It's okay. Things can go back to the way
they were in the old days again.
Cheer up.
See ya.
Thanks, Kakashi Sensei.
Naruto...
Sakura.
Don't interfere with us!
You are weak.
Why are you weak?
It's because you don't have enough...
...hate.
What've I been doing...
up until now?
He got a nice look in those eyes.
Shall we go soon?
What do you think you're doing?
If I don't do this,
you'll run away, right?
You're not the type
to listen quietly to lectures.
As I recall,
that's Kakashi the Copy Ninja.
Sasuke... Forget about something
like revenge.
What?
Well, in this business
I've seen a stink of guys like you.
But the final days of those who speak
of revenge are never good.
They're tragic.
You'll only hurt yourself and
agonize more than now.
Even if you succeed in revenge,
all that will remain is emptiness.
Shut up!
What do you know?
Don't talk to me as if you know!
Well, calm down...
If you like,
shall I go and kill the person
most important to you?
You'll be able to realize just
how far off you are
on what you just said.
Well, I wouldn't mind if you'd do that.
Unfortunately, I don't even have
one person like that.
Everyone's already been killed.
I've lived longer than you have...
The times were not good.
I know all too well
the agony of losing something.
Well, both you and I
aren't the lucky ones...
That's for darned sure.
But we're not the worst, either.
You and I,
we both have already found
dear comrades, haven't we?
It's because I have lost
that I understand.
The Chidori is a power...
I gave to you because
you now have something important.
You should know that it's not a power
to be used on your comrade
or to use for revenge,
and I'm sure you know
what it should be used for.
Think hard about whether or not
what I'm saying is wrong.
It'll be tricky with a Shinobi
of that level hanging around.
So let's wait a bit.
Maybe jerks like you'd be no good.
But I could do it.
I wonder. "Two"
should be ample to rip him apart.
Don't be butting in all the time,
you clod.
Tayuya, women shouldn't
use words like that too...
Shut up, fatso.
– More, please!
Wanna head back?
Sure!
We both made it to the top of the tree.
Sakura.
I have a something to talk to you about.
I'll go out on a date with you,
so come along.
Damn it...
Damn it!
The Curse Mark left by Orochimaru
during the Chunin Exam...
Kakashi Sensei said it was okay now, but...
Master Orochimaru.
You didn't need to send out
all four members, did you?
It seems those kids are all interested
in Sasuke to whom I've taken a liking.
To see what extent his power is...
A contest of strength or whatever,
at this point Sasuke would be
no match for them.
That is precisely why...he will come to me
in search of power.
Who're you guys?
I'm Kidomaru, the East Gate
of the Sound Ninja Four.
I'm Sakon, the West Gate of the same.
I'm Jirobo, the South Gate of the same.
I'm Tayuya, the North Gate of the same.
I'm in a bad mood now...
If you wanna continue to fight her,
I won't go easy on you!
Once in a long while, once in a while
The remnants of a person broken by dreams
Look like a mountain
Clinging to the Divine, clinging to Buddha
The remnants of a person crying
Look like a mountain
Rendezvous with a happy dance circle
This is my victory pose, round and around
(round around)
Shake shake shake Let's look
With a bye-bye rhythm that never ends
Look like a mountain
A date, a date!
What do you want to eat, Sakura?
Anything's fine.
At any rate,
Kakashi Sensei's over the top.
I just wanted to fight Sasuke a little.
But if Kakashi Sensei hadn't stopped it,
right about now...
Of course, which of us was stronger
would be settled, believe it.
Listen, Naruto...
Next time: "An Invitation from the Sound"
I feel uneasy...