I want to try and
gather the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long
way to go on that road.
I'll continue towards
the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky
with
countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond
that...
What were you gazing at?
Too Late for Help
You guys did good
work. Komei has confessed.
It seems he plotted the Cursed Warrior...
to mislead the public and
to take the feudal lord position.
Is that what Komei said?
Yes. It turned out to be such a trifle.
The Cursed Warrior vanishing
was a soldier
disguising himself as the Warrior
using a strong nitrohydrochloric
acid to melt his own flesh.
It's empty again.
With this, the Cursed Warrior
incident is resolved.
Now the Land of Birds should return
to the beautiful and
quiet land it used to be.
Just a minute!
But the Cursed Warrior still isn't...!
Don't bother.
But...!
Now you are relieved of your duty.
Have a safe journey back to your village...
Why?!
You said the one we saw first
and the one last
night were different, right?
Perhaps there were multiple
people disguised as the Cursed Warrior,
not just one alone.
If there was a person inside disguised,
then how do
you explain the Warrior flying?!
As long as our mission
has been ordered complete,
there's no reason to
continue the mission in this land now.
Besides, Komei
confessed to the crime, right?
But, it's suspicious!
I can't go along with it if
I don't get the whole story!
This land has its own circumstances.
Getting too involved will cause trouble.
Then I'll just have to do it my way.
Hold it.
I'm the leader of this team.
So what?!
You look into the movements
of the Cursed Warrior once more.
Tenten and I will reinvestigate
this incident from a different angle.
What? But the mission's over...
You have a point with what you said.
Everything is moving along too swimmingly.
All right! Leave it to me.
Huh? Where are you going, Naruto?
Isn't it obvious? To
investigate the Cursed Warrior!
Oh, Chishima.
Um, Naruto just now...
It's nothing, it's nothing.
Did you have business with us?
Oh, yes.
You have all been so
helpful to me the whole time...
I feel so bad about that low payment...
Additional money?
We couldn't...
No, it's the specialty
of the Land of Birds,
chicken wing buns filled with bean jam.
Yakitori Tsurucho
Thanks!
Sure enough,
this area's fishy, believe it.
It's kind of
time-consuming searching alone...
Summoning Jutsu!
Ahh, long time no see.
Are you giving me a snack?
Why is it you guys?!
Dad's busy with stuff, so.
No, I can't have
Boss Gama appearing, either...
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
You guys have a better
sense of smell than humans, right?
You're calling us puppies?!
Geez! Toad authority
has sure hit rock bottom!
Gamatatsu, we're leaving!
Gamatatsu?
Hey, Gamatatsu!
A frog that pounces on a willow leaf?
What're you doing, you idiot?!
Big Brother Gamakichi...
I wonder what...this is?
Whoa, it's dark. It's night.
Good night.
Good morning.
What's this?
It's a kite painted black.
A kite?
Look up there!
That's a totally huge kite, believe it.
I wonder if there was a big
kite-flying festival or something.
It's rather plain for a festival kite...
What?! What does that mean?
Oh no!
Hey! Where are you going?!
I'm back.
I get it... If one were to fly
that in the cover of a dark night...
A Cursed Warrior
hanging onto the black kite
would look like he was flying...
With this, the mystery of
the flying warrior is solved, believe it!
Next...
Someone was here on that night...
What is it?
The Cursed Warrior came out from here.
It just looks like an old
temple that isn't used much at all.
You're right.
Let's go, Gamatatsu!
But Big Brother Gamakichi,
it's nice and cool here.
What're you talking about?!
In such a hot and humid temple...
Indeed, that's a nice damp wind.
See? Isn't it comfortable?
Draft from down below here...?
What's this?
Wow! I wonder if a giant worm made this.
Or a mole?
All right, let's check it out.
I wonder how we should
greet a mole if we were to meet one.
Like I care!
So Naruto is still
investigating the Cursed Warrior, huh?
I should probably inform Lord Moso.
There was some trouble caused,
but we have at last found a safe refuge.
After him!
Big Brother, where are we?
Huh?! This place is...
This is the residence
of the feudal lord, isn't it?
Really? Residence of the feudal lord?
No wonder it's an impressive building.
It was connected to this place?
What was that sound?
Oh! What a nice view.
Hey! What're you doing?!
Shh! Keep quiet! We'll be discovered.
Big Brother Gamakichi!
Uh, oh!
You blockhead!
Uh, umm... Good work with your duties!
As for me, I'm not anyone suspicious!
I was asked by the Superintendent Moso and
I'm investigating the incident...
It'll make sense if I tell you about it!
Lord Sagi! We have
captured a suspicious man.
What shall we do with him?
What...? Oh!
Oh. Sagi, bro!
Hey! We met at the lake, didn't we?
Explain to them about me!
I know no such person.
What?!
He's not worth sending
to the magistrate's office.
Lock him in the dungeon.
Yes, my lord!
Hey, that's harsh! Come on, Sagi!
Hey! Wait a minute! Come on, hey!
Come on. This is a misunderstanding!
I was just going after the Cursed Warrior!
Umm, everything will make
sense if you just ask Mr. Moso.
You okay?
Yo!
I can't be fighting
the soldiers of my employer's land.
Geez. You had to go
and get caught in that trap!
Well, it's cool. I can get
out of a place like this right away
if I just use both my hands.
Hey, untie this.
Right. Just a second.
Th-The Cursed Warrior...?!
Damn it!
If I could just use both
hands, this guy would be...!
Big Brother, are
we going to let things be?
If things go wrong, we'd be sliced in two.
I wouldn't want that.
Just a little more...
Just a little more...!
Sagi?!
What's going on here?
You're the other Cursed Warrior?
But, why?
They say people become
disembodied spirits and avenge themselves...
But that's a lie!
This watch has been handed
down from generation to generation
in the feudal lord family.
It was supposed to be
passed from father to son...
But now along with that death,
the watch has stopped ticking away.
It must have been very sad...
I am shamelessly living
on only for the sake of revenge!
I can go to hell if I can
just complete my revenge!
That's no good!
There is no way you could understand
how someone who has had
everything taken away from them feels!
Like I know about stuff like that!
But I, at least, know that living
for the sake of revenge is wrong!
You're a feudal lord, aren't you?
Is revenge the job of a feudal lord?
You know that's not it.
The true culprit Komei has been arrested.
You should just leave
the rest to Moso. Okay?
It is no concern of yours...
I must not let you live
now that you have learned everything!
As the thief who snuck into
the residence of the feudal lord...
your fate is a death sentence!
No way...!
This is creepy...
This is the tomb of the successive
generations of feudal lords, right?
Yeah.
That's the tomb of the Lord Owashi...
Byakugan!
What's this?
What is it, Neji? What are you seeing?!
There's something
poisonous in Owashi's body.
Was he assassinated...?!
We're surrounded.
An announcement to
the Ninja from the Leaf Village.
A message has just now been delivered
from the residence of the feudal lord!
Your comrade has
been arrested for infiltrating...
the residence of the feudal lord...
and his death
sentence has been determined!
Leave the Land of Birds at once!
If you don't, you will be
executed here for the same crime.
It doesn't matter! Draw your bows!
Neji, what should we do?
Let's go to
the residence of the feudal lord.
We're going to save Naruto!
You're...
Kakashi Sensei! Naruto's in trouble!
We have to go to the residence
of the feudal lord immediately
and save him...
We can't do that.
Your mission is over.
But!
Don't do anything other than the mission.
So many things happen
on this endless road, huh?
Although you're strong-willed,
your voice wavered on the phone today
What dreams
did you chase to get here?
Even I have times when
I just don't understand, baby
When you're sad,
I'll be close to you
Even on nights when
we're apart,
I'll be close to you
Are we really going
back to the village like this?
I told you. Our mission in
the Land of Birds is finished now.
But then, what'll happen to Naruto?
We can't interfere with
this land's internal affairs.
No way...
Sorry. The responsibility
rests on me, the leader.
Let it go... Sacrifice is
a part of Shinobi missions.
Next time: "The Death of Naruto."