Press down hard on the gas
That's right, there's no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We're speeding through life,
squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you're not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we'll go far off into the distance.
If there's an instance that we
become separated,
don't trust him if he looks
like your teammate.
Just like now there's a possibility
that an enemy will transform
to get close to us!
Yeah.
So what do we do?
We'll decide on a password.
Password?
I'll only say it once so listen closely.
You ask Ninja song, "Ninja Chance."
And the answer is this:
"It is a chance to sneak up where a large
number of enemies are making a scene.
"The quiet place has
no secret hideout.
"It is important for
a Shinobi to know the right time.
"The time when an enemy
is tired and drops his guard."
That's it.
H-Huge!
T-Tail!
You want our Earth Scroll, don't you?
Well, let's begin...
the battle for the Scrolls.
Life or death!
If this creature doesn't want
to spit me out ...
I'll make it to do so at any cost!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I can't move!
I wanted you to entertain me more.
It's too bad.
Move!
He wiped out the fear with pain.
As expected,
he's not the average prey.
Don't come near me!
Don't lower your guard,
not even for a moment...
A prey must always stay tense
and flee desperately
before a predator!
Sorry Sasuke.
Naruto!
The password... I forgot it!
Naruto's Counterattack:
Never Give In!
The password... I forgot it!
That's all right, Naruto!
Awesome!
Naruto!
I know you tried to be cool and
intended to rescue us, but...
Don't put your nose in this!
Escape!
This thing...
She's on a far different level!
Seems like you brought that
giant snake down brilliantly, Naruto.
No matter how you look,
she looks like a snake...
I get it, it was the handiwork
of this woman.
The situation has never gotten any better
with him showing up for the rescue.
But what should I do...?
Hey hey hey! Evidently you've been
bullying the weakling!
Now that I, Naruto Uzumaki is here,
I'm going to wipe the floor with you!
Darn it! If it continues like this,
all three of us are done for!
What should I do?
Sasuke...
It's no good.
This is the only way.
-Wait.
-Hmm?
-Huh?!
-Huh?
If it's the scroll you want,
I'll give it to you.
I'm asking you.
Just take this and go.
-Huh?!
-What?!
Hey, Sasuke!
What are you doing?
Why are you giving
our scroll to the enemy?
You, shut up!
What ...?!
I see...
You're sensible.
The only thing the "prey" can
hope for from the "predator" is
presenting other food and
pray you would be spared, isn't it?
-Take it.
-Wha...?!
You! Don't interfere with this!
Don't you understand this situation?!
What're you doing all of a sudden?!
As for me,
I don't remember the password...
So I got no way to make sure.
But you, you're an imposter
Sasuke, aren't you?
Naruto!
W-What are you trying to start?!
You loser!
I'm the real me!
Liar.
This, this stupid coward is...
absolutely...
not the Sasuke I know!
I don't know how strong she is but,
how can you be sure that she'll let us
go if we hand over the Scroll, huh?!
You're the one who choked and
doesn't understand this situation!
Naruto.
That's correct.
The Scroll.
I could just kill you
and seize it.
Don't mess with me!
Run, Naruto! Stop it!
Darn it!
I've lost confidence in you, Sasuke!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto!
There are three corpses.
This is some kind of Ninja Art,
isn't it...?
This is bad.
We have a problem,
from the get go.
I'll be darned.
Inform Anko,
the Proctor of the second test.
Yes, sir!
If you're going to have dumplings,
you've got to have sweet red bean soup.
Okay...
Once I've eaten this,
I should break through and
go wait at the tower for the kids.
With this program, the quick kids
should clear it soon.
The Leaf Village mark, perfect!
We have a problem, Ms. Anko!
Huh? What, so suddenly?
Corpses! Three of them!
Moreover, they're strange.
Anyway, please come!
Strange?
I checked their possessions
and identification,
Ninjas from Grass Village
registered in the Chunin Exam, but...
As you can see...
They have no faces.
Yes.
They're smooth and flat,
like they melted away.
Without a doubt...
This Jutsu is...
that man's...
Why is he at this test...?
Show me the ID photos of
these three Grass Village Ninjas.
It's on their applications.
Yes!
So this one's face was robbed.
Then, at that time it was already...
I'll return... the Kunai knife.
Thank you for your trouble.
We're in big trouble.
Huh?!
Communicate this to
Lord Hokage right away!
Make a call for action to
the Anbu Black Ops
to assemble more than two squads
to the Forest of Death!
Starting now,
I'm going to follow these guys! Got it?
Yes!
That guy...
That guy...has come to Leaf Village!
Cute.
You're such a cute prey.
Naruto!
Narutooo!
Well, polish him off.
Shove it!
This brat! Can't be...
Naruto... He's lost control...
But...that Naruto,
why is he so strong?!
Those eyes...
There's no mistake.
That's...Naruto?!
This just got interesting.
Next is...
Sasuke.
Now what's your move?!
Sasuke!
I have to hurry.
I get this...
bad feeling.
Hey. Are you hurt?
Scaredy cat?!
Naruto!
Hey!
Are you hurt...
Scaredy cat?
Sasuke!
This stupid coward is absolutely
not the Sasuke I know!
Huh?!
Darn it!
Let me go!
You stupid snake!
To think that the
nine-tailed brat lived...
When you get excited, a bit
of the nine-tail's power trickles out...
You've grown up interesting.
Look...
The Seal is appearing on
your skin like a tattoo.
Five-Pronged...Sealing!
Sasuke! Help Naruto!
Twelve years since the seal...
Naruto's Chakras and the nine-tail's
Chakras are beginning to act in synch...
But now... you're in the way.
He's gonna fall as it is!
Naruto!
What happened Sasuke?!
Sasuke...
Naruto's certainly different
from you, Sasuke.
He's a klutz and
kind of gets in the way.
But he's not in the least a coward!
Right?
Isn't that right?
You foolish little brother.
If you want to kill me,
resent me, hate me and...
continue to live your ugly life.
Flee.
Flee and hang on to your life.
No!
Just what I expect of the Uchiha clan...
his blood has begun to stir...
Sasuke!
I should take my time and
confirm his true power.
Hey, can you hear it?
The clear, blue sky
Goes on and on
The ocean
spans limitlessly
Please keep that smile
On your face forever
Or else I'll cry
You won't have to search around you
It's all ok now.
Everyone is inside
This hand
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
When you forget what happiness is
Just sing.
Light is born, and darkness was born
The two are one
Harmonia, feel the telepathy
Hey, can you hear it?
I'm an avenger.
To defeat my brother,
today I have to survive!
But how can a person who won't risk
his life in a situation like this
beat my brother?
Calm down, you should be able to see.
There should be some way
to intercept her movements.
Next episode: "The Sharingan Revived:
Dragon-Flame Jutsu!"