Rock away your existence,
Shouting that you are here...
A new journey begins now.
As we survived through
the changing seasons,
we gained knowledge and strength,
(just looks like a survival game)
But the forgotten memories,
of the feelings abandoned within
the flows of time,
have also been lost.
When sinking down,
we learned loneliness.
But now we've met each other,
we are no longer alone.
Unveil your feelings,
Those high emotions
Those tears will change your fate.
Pound your heartbeat
against the darkness,
We're sure to meet,
Under the same flag of pain
Reunion: The Remaining Time
What's going to happen?!
What's the deal?!
Sumaru's mom is being
pressed back!
My star training is
done my own way.
It shouldn't be a match
for one who has completed
proper star training like you.
But what's with that sorry state...?
I can't feel even a smidgeon
of the power from before.
Sure enough, you've also got
side-effects from the star training...
Even if this life should end...
I'll never forgive you!
Lord Akahoshi!
What?
You be a good boy!
It's a simple mission.
We'll be able to come back home
right away.
Right! Have a safe journey.
Mother!
Sumaru...!
Sumaru!
Oh, no!
Lord Akahoshi.
Why would you do such a thing?
Is it true then...?
Give it back...
Hold it!
Farewell.
Wh-What?
Then it was Lord Akahoshi
who knocked everyone out
and took Sumaru away?
A sensei who does something
like that
to students who believe in him
is unforgivable!
Why in the world...?
Why would you do such a thing?
It's all for the sake of the village...
It's for the sake of taking back
the star she stole!
Even if that were the case,
that doesn't make for a reason
to cause Sumaru pain!
That person is Sumaru's mom!
M-My...mother...
Exactly!
However, even if she is your mother,
she's now your enemy!
The person before you is
the woman who stole the star
and attempted to bring about
the doom to our village!
That's wrong!
Sumaru's mom just hid the star
in order to save everyone from
the pain of the training!
Foolishness! Being able to die
for the sake of the village
is a Shinobi's long-cherished dream!
Isn't that right, Sumaru?!
You're going to become the Hoshikage
and put to shame
the Five Great Hidden Villages
that treated us with contempt, right?
Yes... I want to become the Hoshikage
and put them to shame...
Show your foolish mother
your determination!
Yes... I can die if it's for
the sake of the village.
Sumaru!
Don't do anything stupid, Sumaru!
His Chakra is in synch with Akahoshi's.
Sumaru is being controlled!
What?!
Exactly... I have Sumaru's life
in the palm of my hand.
Lady Natsuhi.
I shall give you the ultimate choice!
Will you take the star?
Or...your son's life?
Wait!
What's the matter, Lady Natsuhi?
Have you realized
your own foolishness?
Lady...
You win, Akahoshi.
Sumaru!
You did it!
Excellent. How did you get it?
Simple, Lady Natsuhi returned it
with good grace.
Lady!
That's dirty!
Sumaru!
Sumaru...
Is that person...really...?
What're you doing?!
Multiple Shadow Clone Jutsu!
– You...! I won't forgive you!
Hidden Leaf Shinobi,
I'm your employer.
– That doesn't make any difference!
Wait, Naruto!
Neji!
Why, Neji? I can't stand this either.
No! From here on is an issue
for the Hidden Star.
It's none of our concern!
That being said, are we just going
to leave them be?
Anything further would be beyond
the scope of the mission...
The Leaf must not betray the client
of the accepted mission, right?
Damn it!
Oh well.
The star has returned.
I'll overlook everyone's actions today.
Those who wish to continue to live
for the sake of the village, come with me...
B-But...Sumaru is...
Forsake the son of the traitor.
Pull out!
Yes, my lord!
I'm sorry. I must not leave
Sumaru behind.
Rogue Ninja!
Hokuto! You'll regret this!
Well, do as you like!
That jerk...!
Hey, look...!
It's called Natsuboshi.
It's the other name for
the planet Mars, right?
It seems it's the same name
as Sumaru's mom...
Sumaru thinks that star
is protecting him.
I bet Lady Natsuhi was also
looking at that star.
I'm moved.
The hearts of parent and child
are connected!
Yeah...
How're the two doing?
They're resting comfortably now...
But Akahoshi attack
the mother took
when her body was weakened
from the effects of the star is a fatal one.
Her Chakra Network is in shreds
and it will mean certain death
if she uses that Jutsu
even one more time...
Say what?! But Old Lady Tsunade could...
Who knows...?
Damn it! That Akahoshi jerk
is unforgivable!
I'll kick his butt!
Naruto...! You still don't get it?
But he's a huge scoundrel.
That's right!
The Leaf would lose credibility
if we do something like betraying a client.
But we can't leave things be, right?
Well, I also understand what
Neji's saying.
We must ask the Lady Hokage
for instructions.
That's right. Anyway, let's take those two
to the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
Yeah... The Hidden Star matter
will come after that.
Sumaru.
Mother!
Mother.
You're probably angry,
aren't you, Sumaru...?
Of course, you would resent me...
who abandoned the village
and went so far as to entrust you
to someone else.
How often I attempted to take you
with me...
But I kept telling myself that
I couldn't make you happy since
I had become a Rogue Ninja...
with this body that could
give out at any time
due to the star training.
Stay away!
I often had the same dream.
A dream where I chase
after you two, crying.
Sumaru.
Mother!
I kept telling myself
that my mother was not
a cold-hearted person
who would leave me behind...
You had died.
Like that man, the Third Hoshikage said.
He said you had been killed by
a Ninja from some other land,
died and turned into a star...
He said you had turned
into the Natsuhiboshi...!
Sumaru...
Mother!
Even so...
Even so...I wanted you to
take me with you.
Sumaru...
I was lonesome... Mother...
Natsuboshi, why are you so red?
Because I had a sad dream last night
My eyes are red, from the tears I shed
Swollen as I cried...
Natsuhiboshi, why've you lost your way?
I'm searching for a child
who has gone afar
He can't be found. though I search all day
My sad dreams come once more
Hey! Sumaru! Wake up, Sumaru!
Where's the lady? Your mom.
Hey, where'd she go?
What?!
This is bad...
Mother!
Even if it costs my life,
I can't let that star be...
There mustn't be any more
sad mothers and children!
Can't let it happen.
If she gets reckless...
and ends up using that Jutsu again...
It became the village's power
and protected the village.
I didn't want to have to destroy it...
But star, you have caused
pain and suffering
to one too many of the children...
Forgive me...
Akahoshi...
Ninja Art: Kujaku
Beast!
Sumaru...
So your strength has given out?
How tragic.
Mother...
Hey, what's the matter?
It couldn't be! Lady Natsuhi is...
Mother died!
As of this moment,
I, Akahoshi, shall bear the name
of Fourth Hoshikage!
I shall announce the first mission
as Hoshikage.
The Rogue Ninja, Sumaru and Hokuto,
and the Hidden Leaf Shinobi
are enemies who demean us!
If you find them attempting
to enter the village,
bring them down immediately!
Yes, my lord!
I will...
I will get the one who killed
my mother!
Sumaru!
Yesterday's Call Sign,
was all from my cell phone.
In a strange park,
I play the Fuzz Guitar without enthusiasm.
Yellow Moon.
Even now, counting to three,
I open my eyes
Shadow Moon I am still dreaming.
Look at my eyes, look at my eyes,
as we face one another's back
Look at my eyes, when can we meet?
EveryDay EveryNight
With every word I can think of
Right away, my messy feelings as is,
A magical chord change, in a restless city
A daily JAZZ Guitar played
in a soft minor key
Damn that Akahoshi jerk!
I can't forgive him anymore.
He's diabolical.
Hey, you two!
I'll pound him with a good one.
Forget it. Don't stick your nose
into their internal affairs.
Then, I'll beat him into shape
with my Lotus.
That'd be the same as Naruto.
Then what're you saying we do?
Anyway, I'm going, so.
I'll go with you.
No.
Do you guys want to start
a war with the Hidden Star?
Next time: "The Star's Radiance."