I want to try and
gather the unrestrained winds
I'll run toward the horizon,
alongside the wave crests
I've made my decision,
even if there's a long
way to go on that road.
I'll continue towards
the future I've planned
Time rushes us
The heartbeat speeds up
When I woke in the middle of a dream
I kept searching for that same light
Under the shining star-lit sky
with countless constellations and shadows
There was something beyond that...
What were you gazing at?
Kakashi Sensei...
The mission in the Land of Birds is over...
That is enough.
But, then what about Naruto...?
As the leader,
I am responsible for all of this.
Sacrifice is
an unavoidable part of Shinobi missions...
Now...
Let's go back to our village!
Do you think they're really
going back to their village, Nagare?
Perhaps...
But I'm concerned about that masked
guy who joined up with them later...
Shall I follow him, Hokushin?
No, I'll do that. You give the report.
All right...
The Death of Naruto
How did things turn out...?
The two as well as the one
who joined up with them later...
seem to have crossed the border
and are heading for
the Village Hidden in Leaves.
I see.
And it seems Lord Sagi took care
of the one who infiltrated
the residence of the feudal lord.
Very nice indeed.
What're they doing
there for the past hour...?
P-Persimmon! Wh-What the...?
– Ouch...
– That hurts...
It couldn't be!
Substitution Jutsu!
Since when...?
They tricked me! Those Leaf Shinobi...
Lord Komei... Come out.
Land of Birds Tactician Komei.
You have abused the key
position in this land of tactician
and committed the crime of assassinating
the previous feudal lord
Lord Owashi and his child Lady Toki.
And you also ordered a subordinate
to run wild as the ghost
called the Cursed Warrior,
disturbed the public,
you undermined the government of the land,
endangered
Lord Sagi's position of feudal lord
and attempted to
attain the position himself,
an unforgivable crime of treason!
Therefore, you are
ordered to perform seppuku!
I see...
That explains it.
You ensnared me, didn't you, Moso?!
You're disgraceful, Komei! If
you're a warrior, kill yourself like one!
Assist him with the seppuku at once!
– Yes, my lord!
Is this it now...?
Wh-What?!
Hidden Mist Jutsu? No! This is...
It does not matter! Kill him!
Yes, my lord!
Begging your pardon, I shall assist!
Who are you?!
Wh-What is this? What's going on?!
– The Cursed Warrior!
– It's the Cursed Warrior...
That's the Cursed Warrior?!
Yes!
After him! Don't let him get away!
– Right!
You guys go after him as is...!
I've got something I want to look into,
so I'll be going on ahead!
– Roger!
I knew it!
You two were conspirators, right?!
Hold it!
You're the guys from the other night...
I've witnessed
the true identity of the ghost.
Who's there?
Hey-hey, Komei.
You're the one responsible for
controlling the Cursed Warrior, right?
I was also attempting to investigate
the true identity of
the Cursed Warrior that day...
I was almost sure
it couldn't be anyone but that person...
What a pain! I'll
expose the true identity here.
Don't bother...
Kakashi Sensei. Where were you until now?
I'll explain later. Go on ahead!
Hurry! You're going with them.
But...
Let's go, Tenten!
Wait, Neji!
Come on out...
You were following
me the whole time, right?
If that's your intention...
Summoning Jutsu!
What is it, Kakashi?
Smoke out the Ninja
hiding on the temple grounds...
Consider it done.
Hey! You there...
Hide-and-seek is over. Come on out now!
I can't fool a dog's
nose, as would be expected...
You finally grace me
with your presence, huh?
Why is there a hole...
in a place like this?
I have heard the feudal lord
built secret passages such as this
all over the land in order to look
in on the lives of the general public...
The feudal lord?!
Then that Cursed Warrior
has something to do
with the feudal lord...?
At the very least,
it seems he's not a ghost.
When the time comes,
I'm sure he will reveal
his true identity from his end.
Isn't it common sense for hired Ninja
to return quietly to
their village after completing a mission?
It's different in the case
of the premise of
the commissioned mission breaking down.
There were too many
suspicious points in this mission.
You're sticking your nose too
far into the business of another land.
Here you could've
returned safely to your land
if you hadn't
secretively sniffed around like a dog.
Excuse me for being a dog!
Universal Assimilation Jutsu!
Prepare yourself!
What?!
What is this guy?!
Has he introduced
properties of stone into his body?
Since you've learned of
part of this land's secrets,
I can't let you live!
He seems to be
a somewhat troublesome opponent.
Yeah. That's good enough, Pakkun.
I'll be okay by myself from here on.
I see... See you later!
Assimilation: Rock Tank.
I'll crush you!
A Shadow Clone...?!
This is as far as it goes...
It can't be...
A Paper Bomb?!
Now... That should be enough, right?
Yeah... We should be
okay having come this far.
Th-That voice...?!
N-Naruto...!
I knew it.
The true identity of
the Cursed Warrior wasn't Lord Sagi?
Your...
Your true identity is...
Lord Sagi?! It is you, Lord Sagi?
From the way he was standing still,
I thought for sure it was Lord Sagi.
There's a profound reason for this...
What're you doing, Tenten?!
Then tell me sooner!
It seems you also
knew it was Naruto, Neji.
Yeah... Ages ago.
Jeez, you two!
I was really worried!
There was a surveillance Shinobi
following us the whole time, right?
Neji, Tenten... Don't look back.
We're being followed!
We're going back to the Land of Birds.
Just do as I say... Got it?!
Y-Yes!
Understood...
But didn't we shake
the pursuer with Substitution?
Yes... Once...
However... when we chased the Cursed Warrior
from the execution grounds...
a different Shinobi followed us.
Jeez... Am I the only one who didn't know?
It was a waste to worry!
Then you, in the place of Lord Sagi...?
Yeah...
I see... So Lord Sagi is safe!
You okay, mister?!
I'm sorry... That Moso acted rashly,
forcing me to make a false confession.
Man, you've been beaten up good...
Well, we'll tell
you about the developments inside.
Sagi is waiting!
Assimilation: Rock Shower!
We're Wandering Shinobi...
We make do without having a village
by going around to every village,
stealing Jutsu and devising new Ninjutsu.
For example, a Jutsu like this one, too...
S-Say what?
Sharingan!
Assimilation: Sand Coffin!
He's using the same Jutsu as Gaara!
Assimilation: Sand Funeral!
Sagi!
How's Chishima doing...?
He's okay... There's no threat to his life.
He's resting and receiving treatment
in the treatment room of my residence.
That's good...
Did something happen to Chishima?
Who...? Who hurt him?!
Komei... I'm sorry for the misunderstanding!
My lord, I don't deserve
those magnanimous words!
Although he had suffered
injuries, Chishima came to tell me.
At that time...
I must not let you live as is
now that you have learned of everything!
As the thief who snuck into
the residence of the feudal lord,
your fate is the death sentence!
No way...!
L-Lord Sagi...
Chishima?!
Bro!
Shuriken wounds...?
Go to the residence doctor!
Lord Sagi... Please listen...
Lord Moso, no, Moso has betrayed you...
What?
Moso was the one
who killed your father,
Lord Owashi, and Lady Toki!
And Moso had his own Ninja
henchmen use the guardsmen shuriken
to falsely accuse Lord Komei...
I'm sure Lord Komei
learned of Moso's scheme and...
Hang in there, Chishima!
Lord Sagi, please...
Stop Lord Komei's execution.
We have to go save him quickly!
I must not stop the execution!
Wh-Why is that?!
I won't be able to have my revenge
if Moso realizes
that I have learned the truth...
Are you saying
it doesn't matter who is sacrificed
if it's for the sake of your revenge?!
Then what would you do?
Komei is being kept under
strict watch by powerful soldiers.
We would have no chance of winning
if theywe were to cause a rebellion there...
Then I'll go! I will save Komei on my own!
You don't have
a problem with that, do you?
Lord Sagi...
Do as you like...
And so I disguised
myself as the Cursed Warrior.
I played the part of Cursed Warrior
and attempted to look
for the assassination culprit...
But against my intentions...
Instead of finding the true culprit...
Komei... I was used
as a tool to incriminate you.
I thought the Cursed Warrior I encountered
in my bedroom
was you, Lord Sagi...
And so I headed for the abandoned temple
where the Cursed Warrior once vanished.
There I encountered
the Cursed Warrior, but...
That Cursed Warrior wasn't me.
Perhaps it was a fake that Moso devised.
That's it, believe it! All of
it was that old man Moso's trap!
That Moso!
Did he think to first dispose of me
and then eventually
attempt to rule the Land of Birds
by doing away with Lord Sagi?
That guy acting like a good guy!
I'll grab him up and kick his butt!
Naruto, was it? You did good work.
However...
I will take care of things from here on!
Well... But...
I will even the score by myself.
As long as the score isn't settled...
the clock inside my heart...
will remain stopped in the past!
So many things happen
on this endless road, huh?
Although you're strong-willed,
your voice wavered on the phone today
What dreams
did you chase to get here?
Even I have times when
I just don't understand, baby
When you're sad,
I'll be close to you
Even on nights when we're apart,
What do you mean you will
even the score on your own?!
What good can you do going by yourself?!
Even you did avenge
them, the dead won't come back!
Do you still insist on having revenge?!
Would that make you feel better?!
Would that really make
your father and sister happy?!
Next time: "When Time Stands Still"