Connecting old words
that have been used up
I just want to convey
my simple thoughts
That day's faint wind blows away
at the castle ruins of yesterday
I'll laugh with you
and live for the moment
Still that incident
will continue to trouble you, right?
That's why it must be good-bye
Leaving nothing behind,
let us share what is left
In time, we'll realize
that it was everything
And sadness will touch our cheeks,
creating a river of tears
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex
and melting away
I'll let you out of here.
And I'll grant you one wish, too.
You don't have to worry.
Your strong will is going to remain
as Residual Aura inside me.
It's not like you'll lose everything.
Now then, your flesh is mine.
With this, Lord Orochimaru's body
has once again
become unable to reanimate
for several years.
However there's a next time...
I-Indeed. My body no longer has value
as a vessel for Reanimation Jutsu.
It will now be difficult for me
who has lost everything...
to find my own calling.
I've finally understood that.
Even if it's not me...
I'll bring in the new "vessel,"
even if it costs me my life.
That's my repayment to
Lord Orochimaru.
That's the only redemption for me...
who was worthless.
Miscalculation: A New Enemy Appears!
They're fast.
Akamaru.
Come quick after you've set the bombs!
Oh no!
All right.
Great.
Akamaru, well done.
Messing with me.
Akamaru.
Don't you "arf" me, you mutt!
I'll waste you.
Hold on.
You!
Kiba! Akamaru!
Damn it.
What's happening?
You punks!
Where are Kiba and Akamaru?!
Another one's come.
We have no choice.
I'll take care of this, so you take
the coffin and go on ahead.
Shikamaru...
Get going already.
Wh-Why are you...?
I'm sorry, Naruto.
It's my miscalculation.
Kimimaro.
You were taking too long, Tayuya.
And what happened to
the other three?
Being none other than those
of the former "Sound Ninja Five."
Why are you...?
Your body... Your body's no longer...
I'm not moving with the flesh anymore.
It's mental power.
Man, you cheater of death...
I understand a little now,
that feeling...
of being information that has escaped
from the prison of the flesh.
The feeling of experiencing
a taste of Lord Orochimaru's dream.
Orochimaru...!
This vessel...is an important vessel
for the dream...
The flesh that Lord Orochimaru
truly desires.
But you guys were a bit too late.
Some dangerous guy
has appeared again.
That air about him is
nothing ordinary.
Anyway, we need
to sort out the situation.
If we were to carelessly
plunge in...
You jerk.
What're you babbling nonsense?
Naruto!
Give back Sasuke!
Hey, wait!
Tayuya.
The reason why I won't kill you now
is because you have a mission
you have to complete.
And my mission is to deliver
that to Lord Orochimaru.
Isn't it too late now?
Humph. I told you.
That's the body that Lord Orochimaru
truly desires.
The next vessel, huh?
That's right...
And this is the only thing that
I can do at present.
I leave those two pieces
of garbage to you.
Sasuke...
That punk!
Calm down, Naruto.
How can I calm down?
At this rate,
Sasuke will get far away again.
Naruto's right.
This is a mission to bring Sasuke back
to the Leaf Village.
We must choose what would be
the most rational means
to execute the mission.
Damned punks.
I'll finish this in a flash.
Naruto, listen up.
Please move according to the plan
that I'm going to tell you.
He's a classic close-range
combat-type fool
with Shadow Clone Jutsu
as his only saving grace.
And he's a middle-range
combat type
who binds his enemies with
a Jutsu using shadows...
and a sharp squad leader, huh?
Got it?
Yeah.
Come on already, you punks.
It's two versus one.
We've got the upper hand.
It's an opponent we can beat
if we team up.
Let's go, Naruto.
All right.
With garbage like you jerks,
it doesn't matter how many
of you are there.
Don't underestimate our teamwork.
Let's go!
Bring it.
Now...Naruto.
I'll blow you away.
Gotcha. The strategy is a success.
Farewell.
Blast.
You tricked me.
Teamwork, my foot. You little punks...
Blast.
You wouldn't fall for the same trick
over and over, huh..?
Small fry... You've got nerve.
Well, I guess I'll settle for just
having been able to let him get away.
Remember this.
It's not just Jutsu that are weapons.
I'm counting on you, Shikamaru.
Hang in there, Sasuke.
But that kid,
how wonderful it is that
he can move with that body, eh?
Kabuto, I don't know what kind
of order you gave him,
but it's a bit harsh.
Not at all.
It wasn't an order.
I don't like to force things.
He acted on his own.
For you whom he reveres.
Kabuto...You've really got
a hateful personality, don't you?
Lord Orochimaru.
To you,
Kimimaro was a perfect existence...
His thoughts were steeped in darkness
in the same way as yours.
And he sanctified you.
And he fanatically admired
and revered you.
Moreover, he was of the Shinobi clan
with the strongest and perfect bodies
being the legitimate bloodline
of their Kekkai Genkai...
until a short time ago.
Yes...
When I think about having lost him,
I still get a chill down my spine.
I think about it even now...
The man I truly wished for...
The body I wanted the most...Kimimaro.
And if only he hadn't been stricken
with disease,
the assassination of the Hokage
would've gone smoother.
Seal!
My arms...
Now...you can no longer use
either of your arms...
And since you can't use your arms,
you can't weave Sign...
You no longer possess Ninjutsu!
Your ambition of crushing
the Hidden Leaf...dies right here!
Orochimaru, you fool...
It's unfortunate that we can't leave
together but, my disciple...
Let's meet in the other world
one day...
Sasuke...
Sasuke's not here yet?
We wouldn't have needed to go
through such an experience.
In the world, very often things don't go
as we want them to.
It's only a matter of time,
Lord Orochimaru.
When Tayuya...comes back,
I'll kill her.
Hold it.
Hey...!
Now then, how shall I defeat you?
You...
Those eyes...
It seems he possesses
a peculiar Chakra.
What does Orochimaru want to do...?
Why's he after Sasuke?
Lord Orochimaru has already
obtained Immortality Jutsu...
A long time is necessary to get every Jutsu
and obtain everything in the world.
What does that have to do
with Sasuke?!
"Immortal" doesn't mean that
the flesh is being maintained as is...
Before his body decays,
a strong and new flesh will be made
into a vessel for his soul.
That's...
Are you saying that's Sasuke?!
Yes... That's right.
I won't let such a thing happen!
Idiot... What will come of sending
one shrimp punk in pursuit?
And looking at things
in terms of time,
up until now you probably sacrificed
one member each time
in order for the group
to move forward.
Is that guy called Sasuke
that important?
How many of your men do you intend
to sacrifice for the sake of just one person?
You incompetent punk.
Heh... Indeed...
For me, this is my first mission
as a platoon leader.
It's very disquieting having
comrades gradually whittled down,
and I didn't know if my own judgments
were correct or not.
As a squad leader with
the lives of the party in my hands...
respecting the lives in
the four-member party,
rather than the life of one person
taken by the enemy...
and deciding to abort a mission
that's too dangerous, would be by the book.
Then, why didn't you do that?
The world doesn't go
by the book very often...
Since not one person in my squad
would do something like
abandon a captured comrade
and give up fighting
for the sake of their own safety.
Me included.
Being the cloud-loving loafer myself,
I am not cut out to be a squad leader
who gives orders to comrades.
The only thing I can do for them...
is to have faith in them.
Listen. I'm not thinking anything
like they were sacrifices.
I'm not thinking anything
like they've died.
Don't mock my comrades.
I got you.
Summoning Jutsu!
This doesn't...look so good.
I'll play a melody of death for you.
Don't you mock us,
you damned punk.
I won't let you take Sasuke,
no matter what.
Interesting.
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
Would you think it was
a bother if I approached you?
Despite my doubts,
I worked up my courage
My clumsy attempts with words
You listened without turning away
No wonder I get carried away by you
But you don't feel anything for me, do you?
I feel so sad
But...
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
And you smiled
For the first time, I was able to speak
In my own words
For the first time, I spoke to you
Damn it! What'll I do?!
He's trouble enough yet,
but his Chakra has increased
several ten-fold!
It's no good. I can't use it here yet.
But if I stay like this, we'll...
I get it, Akamaru.
It's like you said.
I have no choice but to use it!
Next time: "Roar and Howl!
The Ultimate Tag-Team!"