Press down hard on the gas
That's right, there's no compromise
We'll slip through the night
At the final moment push hard
That's right, all the way to zero,
Until we wipe away the days
Gently open your heart
If you pull it close to you
It will reach you, without a doubt
It will come, closer
Now
We're speeding through
life, squeezing it for all of its worth
Our feet are tied
But we still keep going farther
Even if I take it back, and grasp it
If you're not the one
There will be no meaning
And so we'll go far off into the distance.
Umm, where's the room that Sasuke's in?
Mr. Sasuke is not allowed any visitors.
What?! Hey, hey! What's up with that?!
I'm sorry, those are the rules.
Why, Sis, tell me why?
Naruto, this is a hospital. Keep it down.
Say! Say! I've got a favor to ask!
You don't need to say it all.
Well, I thought it would come to this so...
I searched for
someone to watch your training.
Why?!
I want you to, Kakashi Sensei!
I have some matters to take care of.
I don't have time to
trouble myself with you.
Oh! Aha...!
You're going to train Sasuke, aren't you?!
Well... don't say that.
I found a sensei
who's more reliable than I am!
Well...who is it?
It's me!
Huh?!
Oh! You!
The Closet Perv!
Such insolence!
Ebisu Returns:
Naruto's Toughest Training Yet!
Ebisu Sensei is a Closet Perv?
Why's this guy my training teacher?!
In the first place, he's weaker than me!
What did you say?
But you see! But you see!
A long time ago,
with my Harem Jutsu, this guy...
Transform!
Master Ebisu! Master Ebisu!
B-By any chance...
Harem Jutsu?
U-Uh...it's nothing!
I'll treat you to and buy
you whatever you want later!
Just be quiet about that!
You better.
Wow, I didn't know you were acquainted.
Well, they're unsavory ties, but.
How could I ever forget that humiliation?
But why this guy?
I definitely don't want him to.
Same here.
If it weren't Kakashi's favor,
who'd teach you for the fun of it?
Then don't.
Now now, both of you...
Don't say that.
Naruto, Ebisu Sensei is a private tutor
who teaches the elite, a special Jonin!
He's truly better at teaching than I am.
Well, Naruto, of the three
kids in Squad Seven that I taught,
you're the worst at the basic skills.
Get taught with care this time around.
How the heck am I inferior
compared to Sakura and Sasuke?!
Naruto, it's fact
that you don't have the fundamentals down.
No matter what you do,
the basic skills are important.
If you really want to become strong,
just be quiet and listen to what I say.
Now then, Ebisu Sensei,
I'm leaving him with you.
Yes, yes.
Dang it.
It may appear to be harsh,
but you can become stronger a lot more.
Do your best.
Okay, then, let's go.
Still, I'm not convinced...
Huh?
You see!
Fundamentals might be important,
but I won't get strong being
taught by someone weaker than me!
So in other words,
you want to say that I'm weak?
Who else is here?!
I was certainly surprised having
that indecent Jutsu used on me that time.
But it's premature for
you to judge my ability on just that.
Even though you were totally knocked out.
Fine.
Then, why don't we put it to the test?
Hmm?
Naruto, run.
Huh?
If you can get to outrun
me, I'll back down quietly.
Back down...?
Yes. And of course,
I'll speak to Kakashi Sensei
about you receiving direct training.
What?! Really?!
This elite instructor
does not go back on his word.
However, this is
only if you can outrun me.
Then that makes it easy!
See ya!
This'll be a snap, a snap!
I'll lose that... Closet Perv in no time!
He already can't catch up!
I knew I was quite an exceptional Ninja...
Who is exceptional, you say?
Surely you're not thinking
you can outrun me with just that much.
W-What're you saying?!
The chase has still...
only just begun!
Though he's a Closet Perv,
he's the elite tutor after all, he's good.
Now then.
I knew you were Closet Perv.
What are you doing...?
Naruto?
I see. The idea isn't bad.
Then, how about this?!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Heh! Catch me...if you can!
Not bad...
However, you are not the only
one who uses the Shadow Clone Jutsu.
I won't let you get away!
Dang it!
Son...of...a...!
Now then, next.
Hold it!
I found you!
Wait!
I won't let you get away!
Get off!
There! No, actually, here! Here!
There! There!
Hold it!
Have you reached your limit?
You're freaking pesky!
Give it up already!
What are you snapping back at me for?
This is a chase,
so chasing is natural, right?
T-True enough...
Naruto, you have
understood my greatness by now, right?
It's about time
you surrendered and moved on to training...
The heck with that!
I'm going to bump you off,
and receive Kakashi Sensei's training!
Even if I have to knock you out!
It appears you still
have some spirit left.
To think he would come at me
head on, even though this is a chase.
Just what I would expect of you, Naruto.
As Kakashi said, he's
the number one unpredictability Ninja.
Don't take this badly! Eat this!
Clone Jutsu...?
The game is over, Naruto!
Dang it!
Miso-flavor barbecued pork
noodles and salt-flavor ramen noodles!
Here you go!
Naruto, having been
shown your movements and
having further analyzed
what Kakashi has told me...
it is clear
that you cannot control Chakra well.
Control...?
That's right.
Now then, comparing
you with Sasuke and Sakura ...
I shall explain your bad points in order.
As you know, in the case of
using Ninjutsu, Genjutsu and the like,
Ninjas build up
Chakra and activate the Jutsu.
I-I know that already!
Is that so?
Then, in the case of
comparing the three of you,
I shall explain
specifically how you are inferior.
That's kind of
an irritating way of saying it.
I'm treating you the ramen as promised,
so be quiet and listen!
First, let us say
that Sakura uses Clone Jutsu.
Clone Jutsu!
In her case, her build-up control as
well as her control of Chakra is perfect,
so she can make clones
without using wasteful energy.
Cha!
Next, in Sasuke's case,
he is somewhat poor at building up Chakra.
Clone Jutsu.
But, his control of Chakra is perfect,
so both he and
Sakura can make five clones.
But, he uses a bit more
wasteful Chakra than Sakura.
Oh! So Sasuke's nothing special.
In your case, there's no
time to be laughing at others.
Huh?
You are very poor at
building up Chakra and controlling it,
so you cannot make clones
with the same amount of Chakra.
In the case where
you strain to make clones despite that,
after consuming a much larger
amount of Chakra than Sakura and Sasuke...
Clone Jutsu!
...you can barely make one clone at best.
By the way, Sakura and Sasuke can become
ten with the same amount of Chakra.
Like this, the three of you are this
different even using the same Jutsu.
Well, this is a somewhat
exaggerated comparison of you three,
but you build up too much
Chakra, use too much physical strength,
and your Jutsu
activation is also unstable.
But, there've been times when
I was greater than Sakura and Sasuke...
That's only because you happen to have
the most outstanding stamina of the three!
Well, I am pretty sure
that your Chakra control
is getting difficult due to
the influence of the Nine-Tails...
which is the origin of your stamina.
Anyway, there is no
mistaking that you can become strong
if you carry out
the training we will be doing from now.
Huh?! Really?!
I guarantee it.
Now then, let's go.
Sir, your bill.
Oh, that's right. Wha...?!
Thank you very much!
We've come quite a long way...
But, this is a hot spring town, right?
It doesn't look like we've come
here to leisurely soak in a hot spring...
Hey! Naruto! That's the women's bath!
I simply will not allow indecent behavior!
Huh?
I'm not you...
It's not that I was
trying to peep. Believe it!
Thinking of something like that in
the first place makes you a Closet Perv!
What's with that look?
N-Nothing.
More importantly,
why've we come to a place like this?!
Will soaking in a hot
spring do anything for training?
No! The training will be
here in this hot spring area!
Okay, this is the place.
It's a bath, sure enough!
What are you saying?
I said this is
training, didn't I? Training!
We're going to train here?
What the heck are we going to do?
Walk on this hot water!
What?!
What is it?
Walk on hot water?
Can you really do that?
Of course!
I heard from Kakashi Sensei.
You already did tree-climbing
training without using your hands, right?
It's an application of that.
Hmm... What do you mean?
Besides, I don't really
remember stuff from long ago!
In tree climbing, all you do is accumulate
only the necessary amount of
Chakra in one necessary location
and maintain
that amount of Chakra all the while.
Trees are fixed objects,
so you only need to be attached to it.
In other words,
it's training for building
up a fixed amount of Chakra.
To float on the surface of water,
you have to discharge on a constant basis
an appropriate amount of
Chakra from your feet to the water
and balance that to the extent
that you can float your own body.
Huh?
This Chakra control is
more difficult than maintaining...
and is a control training for
discharge and usage of fixed amount
of Chakra for Jutsu and alike.
Hmm, I really don't get it!
Well, it would be better
to show you in your case.
First, you build up Chakra in your feet.
Then, while constantly
discharging a fixed amount...
you balance it with your body weight.
And... well, this is how it goes.
Oh! Okay! I'm going to try!
First, you build up Chakra in your feet.
Then! Discharge a fixed amount. Right?
Oh!
I knew it.
Hot-hot-hot-hot!
I forgot to mention it,
but this hot water is 60° C.
If you do nothing but fail...
you will become a boiled octopus!
Dang it!
I'll do it no matter what!
You're unusually
spirited today, honored grandson!
My principle of
guidance has finally gotten through!
This would ordinarily
be the time to go carry out
a surprise attack on Lord Hokage.
I've stopped doing that now!
That's right!
So you have finally understood.
That the shortcut to
becoming the Hokage is to do as I say...
There are no shortcuts!
Huh?
Brother Naruto said it...
If you're to become
Hokage, be prepared for that!
Oh!
I'm starting to get it!
To think he would get the hang
of the Chakra control this quickly...
I never thought, you would grow this much.
Indeed, there are no
shortcuts, in anything...
It appears I had the wrong idea about you...
You are a much smarter teacher than I am.
And, you were not just a Demon Fox...
You were a splendid
Hidden Leaf Village Ninja!
Oh! Hot!
Hm?! That is...!
Humph! I don't know
who you are or where you're from, but...
I will not allow indecency!
Man...
T-That is!
What?!
Don't make a ruckus.
Jeez, it won't do to be found out!
The Closet Perv lost?
W-What's with that Shameless Perv?!
One! First, Tyson jumps and slamdunks
Two! He kisses and hugs
everyone randomly and says "I LOVE YOU"
Three! Masala masters Yoga but hates curry
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter. Ole!
All over the world, the sky's
smiling, so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Oh yeah! Fight! Fight! Fight!
One! Bodimahattaya-san
devotes his time for digging black ships
Two! Peking Duck, Action Scene,
Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
Three! Popo loves to polish his Coteka
Four! Japanese
people, now lend me your hand!
All over the world, the sky's
smiling, so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Oh yeah! Fight! Fight! Fight!
All over the world, the sky's
smiling, so look up and smile too
Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
Oh yeah! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, you!
What're you doing, Shameless Perv?!
Here I was having my training watched,
and you did this to the Closet Perv!
And you're so
infernally quick at running away.
Could he be a super Ninja?
Next episode.
"Long Time No See: Jiraiya Returns!"
I'll chase him down and
make him train me without fail!