Hey boys, listen up!
Humans aren't such a big deal
Who needs tomorrow anyway,
so don't hide your fists
You're not old enough
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
Hey boys, you're the only ones
who can pull the trigger in your heart
All the kids said
We're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
awesome world right at this moment,
All the kids said
Don't forget every truth or lie
We're way too young to die
In this empty town lined with empty faces
All the kids took off
into this windless night
Because they want to change something
Funeral March for the Living
Wh-Why...
Why does such a good man have to...die?!
It's sad... It's so sad!
I remember now...
I forgot when,
but you showed it to me, didn't you?
With a twinkle in your eye,
you proudly said it was
a memento of your father.
That was the pipe box, wasn't it?
It was an amazing box.
No wonder you're so proud of it...
Even though I took it and smashed it,
you only laughed.
You were smiling when
we kicked you and tossed you.
It was a great smile.
Really...
Hold it in, Rokusuke! They'll all be gone.
If we let this moment go,
there will be no other chance
to get out of the village.
But Kanpachi is...!
It's for the village,
we have to do something and
make our way to that village!
Yeah...
Funerals are awesome, aren't they!
I wanna do that again.
One...two...
three people... got away again...
Looks like we can have another funeral.
This is...
The Village Hidden in the Leaves.
You are...?
Naruto Uzumaki! Right now,
I'm in the middle of training.
The Village Hidden in the Leaves...
H-Hey! I said hey!
Hang in there!
This is training too...!
I can't give up yet! Not yet!
The escort for the ruler of
the Land of Swamps, Lord Chichiyasu,
was completed without incident!
Well done.
That's Lady Tsunade's...!
Excellent dumplings are always
from the Leaf Village, aren't they?
That was my last one!
Mission Accomplished!
I came to pound the pirates
of the Gottani Channel
with the fist of love!
If they take this opportunity
to rehabilitate themselves,
it's worth while to shed a tear!
I'll have your team do it for me.
Yes?
Even though we're already busy,
that Naruto brought in more work.
After this, Guy has the S-rank mission.
The client picked him,
so he must depart today.
So, do it without Guy.
That's pretty straightforward...
I called Neji Hyuga, Tenten and Lee.
Ohh!
My pupils can undertake the fulfillment
of this mission without incident!
Wait...
Take Naruto Uzumaki, too.
Why can't it just be my pupils,
who are loved by all the world?
Please answer me, Lady Tsunade!
It just is.
Hidden Leaf Hospital
Those three people that Naruto saved
came all the way
from the Katabami Gold Mine
to request a mission.
Katabami Gold Mine is one of
the Land of Rivers' greatest mines,
but about half a year ago, hooligans
calling themselves the Kurosuki family
appeared on the pretext of guarding it,
and took control of the village...
killing villagers for
no particular reason.
How vile!
Your mission is this:
Once those three have
regained their strength,
escort them to Katabami Gold Mine
and eliminate the Kurosuki family.
It's a simple mission.
Well anyway, it must be a group
of punks who're after money.
Why did you call me for
such an easy mission?
Who do you think you are?
I'm busy searching for
Sasuke and training, and...!
You forced your way into missions
that you weren't called for.
It's not a Genin's place
to choose his missions!
Would you like to be sent back
to the Academy? Well?!
-Neji Hyuga!
-Yes!
You're the leader!
It will be good training for you
to try to tame the unstable.
I don't want to... but, I'll do it!
I'll go continue my training!
Hey Naruto!
Please excuse them. They have no manners...
Wait!
Those little brats...!
What the heck do they think missions are?!
-Umm, excuse me?
-What?!
The Kurosuki Family...
What did you say their boss' name was?
-Raiga!
-That's what I thought...
What?
Well, on a previous mission,
I heard a rumor about him.
A rumor...?
Pervy Sage hasn't returned...
I'm forced to go on a mission...
Oh, this is irritating...
-Sakura!
-Naruto?
What's going on? A bird?
Yesterday I found it injured
and treated it, but...
Sakura, that's amazing!
But poor thing.
It's separated from its friends.
Naruto!
Oh, sorry, did I intrude?
You intruded big time!
No, no!
Don't turn your back,
no need to grovel to youth.
Sakura, Hello!
-Hello!
-What did you come here for?
-Just to have a word.
-Huh? What the...?!
Oh, Sakura, goodbye!
-Hey! What was that?!
-She went wild, didn't she?
She should act her age.
Ichiraku
What?! The boss of the Kurosuki family
is one of the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist?
Yeah, it's exclusive information
from our respected teacher, Guy.
Who're the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist?
Naruto, you said that
you fought in the Land of
the Waves mission, didn't you?
At that time...
Oh, Zabuza! And?
And Guy Sensei and Kakashi Sensei
fought Kisame Hoshigaki.
I heard that
you met them there too, Naruto.
Oh! I know that guy!
Those two were once called
the Seven Ninja Swords Men of the Mist.
And at that time,
who was with Kisame Hoshigaki?
Oh!
The man called Itachi! And then?
You still don't understand?
If Raiga is one of the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist,
then he's probably tied to Itachi
who was with Kisame.
Oh! And?
Tell me, who's after Itachi?
I know! Sasuke!
That's right!
We can probably get
the clue to Sasuke's whereabouts
at Katabami Gold Mine!
But...
If that's what Guy Sensei said then...
Don't say anything rude!
It's information that's 100% reliable!
Starting now,
while guarding Rokusuke and the others,
we head toward Katabami Gold Mine
to fulfill our mission to
wipe out the Kurosuki family.
There's a shop I'm familiar
with close to the gold mine.
Let's make that the base.
What do you mean
a shop you're familiar with?
That's the fun part of the trip.
That aside, that Naruto is late...
If the source of the information
is Guy Sensei,
maybe he couldn't quite trust it?
That's not true!
Naruto will definitely come!
That's because Guy Sensei's
information is correct!
Whatever.
Here I am!
We're all here so...!
Is that for you to say?!
Let's go!
So...which way?
Don't be so anxious, Rokusuke,
Those guys will save our town.
It's post-meal training!
I won't lose!
How long do you intend to rest here?!
If we hurry, we can save Kanpachi
from the burial...
Give it up...
How long do you think
it's been since that happened?
It's painful but...
I remember...this sleepiness.
The shop is close by.
You say you're sleepy,
and are you walking in your sleep?!
It's okay.
I slept while on a marathon on
this road for three days straight.
You are joking, right?
It's true.
The track meet of my youth
with Guy Sensei.
My body still remembers it.
I've gotten sleepy.
Hey, Bushy Brow, are you really okay?
That's right. In this area,
there's the scent of spicy curry.
Curry? Now that you mention it...
That's right!
Over there, it's... the Curry of Life Shop!
Grandma Sansho!
Oh my... Oh goodness!
I haven't seen you for a while!
-Oh my my my!
-You're looking well!
This is the shop Lee is familiar with?
That mountain is the Katabami Gold Mine
Grandma Sansho's curry saved my life.
So you're saying it's delicious curry?
No, it really saved my life.
I'm indebted to this curry.
It was when I'd just become a Genin ...
When Guy Sensei gave me
a special training routine.
Oh my, that's right. I remember.
Do your best!
Oh my...
Hey Grandma Sansho!
Oh my, they've come again!
Those people are running in their sleep.
Karashi! Karashi!
If you had that kind of energy,
you wouldn't lose to the bullies.
Oh my, I might have said too much.
Curry of Life Shop
Oh my! It's the third day.
They've been running the whole time.
Oh my. What a problem.
I wonder if he's hungry...?
What a pickle! He's not waking up!
Maybe I didn't use enough spice?
Karashi...
I've never seen a person
who works this hard.
Oh really... so you want to help
this young man too...?
This is the curry of life.
Now! Grandma Sansho went to
the trouble of making this curry.
Let's eat!
I'm digging in!
Yum! This is yummy-yum delicious!
Delicious! The use of spices is wonderful!
And this rice
goes perfectly with the curry!
Delicious!
By the way, I don't see Karashi.
Karashi saw how hard you worked
and became a bright kid
full of energy, but...
He got too much energy and left for town.
What?
I was wrong to keep telling him
to be stronger.
"I'm going to be a man!
"I'm going to be part of
the Kurosuki family," he said.
Oh my! I'm not blaming you. Don't worry.
It's too late.
I'm responsible...
Oh my.
Neji!
Please include Karashi's rescue
into our mission!
We'll bring him back from
the road of evil!
It's fine.
We'll use this shop as a base
and take a good look into the village.
Then we'll come up with a strategy
and spring into action.
Yes!
You guys await orders here.
Because it's dangerous
if the Kurosuki family finds us.
It's a disaster!
Rokusuke! Rokusuke! He's gone!
I'm sure he went to town alone!
That's not good!
If those guys find Rokusuke...!
Now that it's come to this,
we don't have time
to come up with a strategy!
Let's get right to it!
No! We'll get right to it!
Let's hurry.
Wait for me, Kanpachi, I'm coming now...
Someone... is coming...
Aw, again... I have to put on a funeral!
Crappy news pass us by
And you become speechless
My voice is way too soft
So you don't answer
You're crying Crying alone
What can I do? I'm crying too
"Let my lonely scream ring out
through the night"
I'll thrash this confused era
with my speed
Yeah
And I'll thrash this confused night
with my speed
Yeah
I'll thrash them with my piercing guitar
and my speed
Yeah
This sinking world and its evil bastards,
I'll kick their butt
Yeah
You taught me that day.
If you cook with great care,
you can save someone's life
with just one serving of curry.
Even for a person like me,
with intense effort,
it's not an impossibility...
That's what I thought.
You were far more admirable
back then, Karashi.
But...
Next time: "A Lesson Learned!
The Iron Fist of Love!"