We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road
filled with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes and
take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose,
so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers
don't care what people think about them
follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh!
Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
We're gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
Unforgivable! A Total Lack of Respect!
W-What the heck is going on here?
Hmm...
Help me!
Excuse me there, Mister!
Wait just a moment!
What in the world is happening?
You should run away too!
There's a monster up there!
A monster...?
What could it be?
This monster thing?!
It's a g-gigantic snake!
It destroyed the castle in a flash!
How big of a snake?!
Me too, at my village before...
I was attacked by a huge snake!
We must hurry, Naruto!
That snake is probably the same one
that you saw before.
Destroy the Leaf Village...?!
And your answer is?
Lady Tsunade!
No! You must not believe
in their sweet talk...
Your brother and my uncle
wouldn't want any of that!
Their wishes...
Moreover, Tsunade, your wishes...
And dreams...
Did you forget them?!
I know it!
Even if you are like this now,
you still...
Open your eyes! Wake up, please!
Shut up, Shizune!
You don't have to answer right now.
However, I want it in a week.
Also, two human sacrifices are needed
for this Forbidden Jutsu,
so do what you need to do
to prepare them.
Lady Tsunade, let's kill them right here!
It's our chance!
With you and me, now we can...!
Lady Tsunade...
Sure, I am weak now.
However...
I also know Tsunade's weakness.
That's right, he is one of the Sannin
like Tsunade.
So he knows that...
I see it's not cured yet...
your fear of blood.
Hemophobia...?
Shall we get going, Kabuto?
Tsunade... I'll be expecting
a favorable answer from you.
Looks like we were a little too late...
Is this that snake's doing, too?!
– Let's go, Naruto!
– Huh?
Tsunade isn't here any more.
Geez, you keep telling me that...!
Welcome!
Hey, you ol' man, give me another shot!
Lady Tsunade, you're drinking too much!
Lady Tsunade...
Heck, she's nowhere to be found!
Dragging me around here and there,
but after all,
we haven't found a single trace!
Hmm?
Well, let's dine here for now.
Huh?
Isn't this a pub?
So what?
I've told you so many times!
I'm still underage!
You fool. Nobody is asking you to drink.
Kids should only be eating snacks.
– Well then...
– Welcome!
There's no need to dine here!
We can go to a ramen noodle shop
or something!
How stupid! You can gather information
in this type of place...
Huh...?
Huh?!
Tsunade!
Jiraiya?!
Why...are you here?
I've finally found you!
I'm exhausted...
That gal is Tsunade?!
She's 50 years old for real?
Now, that's a swindle.
I can't believe...
I met two of the Sannin in one day.
Here you are!
In any case...
Today is a day I see many old friends.
You mean Orochimaru...
What happened?
Nothing, really.
We exchanged a greeting.
Is it really true that this gal
is the Kunoichi
who can heal any kind of wound?
What about you?
What do you want from me?
I'll be straight with you.
Tsunade, the village has demanded
that you become the Fifth Hokage.
Hey, ol' man,
gimme the simmered meat with potatoes!
All right, in a moment.
The Fifth Hokage?!
What's this out of the blue?!
What the heck is going on?!
Do you know about the Third Hokage?
The Third Hokage?
So, he really was...
Orochimaru did it, right?
I heard about it.
directly from him.
Orochimaru did it...?
Orochimaru?!
Did he really killed the old man,
the Third Hokage?!
Who is this Orochimaru?!
Just like us, he's one of the Sannin.
Why?! The Sannin are all
from Leaf Village, right?
Then why...?!
Who's this brat?
He's Naruto Uzumaki.
This brat is...
that Nine-Tailed Fox...?
Hey, you just hold it there!
I am not done talking yet!
This Orochimaru?!
This bastard that killed Old Man Hokage.
Who the heck is he?!
He's a legendary Sannin, right?!
Then knowing that...
why would you, Pervy Sage,
leave such a guy alone?!
Besides...
What do you mean this person
is the Fifth Hokage?!
Naruto, be quiet for a moment.
But...!
Just shut up!
I'll say this again.
They are demanding that
you become the Fifth Hokage, Tsunade.
So what's your answer?
Will you accept it?
I'll resurrect the little brother
and man, both of whom you loved...
This time, I will completely destroy Leaf!
What do you say...Tsunade?
Lady Tsunade...
I really don't get it!
Impossible...
I refuse!
I remember...those words.
You said those same words
when I asked you to go out with me.
What the heck are you talking about?!
You said it yourself!
Didn't you say that
you will bring her back to the village
and have her treat Sasuke
and Kakashi Sensei?!
But what's this demand
for her to be the Hokage?!
And, on top of that, she refuses!
Lady Tsunade...
Could she be thinking of making
a deal with Orochimaru?
Calm down.
There can't be no other Fifth Hokage,
but this Tsunade.
During the dreadful Great War Era,
she contributed tremendously
to the Leaf's victory.
To this date,
there's no one who can rival
her combat and medical skills.
Still more, this Tsunade is
the granddaughter of the First Hokage.
So together with her talents,
there's no one else more suited
to becoming the Fifth Hokage.
If she becomes Hokage,
that means that
she'll come back to the village.
And then, as I'd told you,
she can treat the two.
Besides, this is what the Leaf's
top decision-making advisors settled upon.
Genin like you have no say
on this matter.
Jiraiya...
Unlike your previous apprentice,
this kid not only has a bad mouth and wit,
he's ugly to match.
What?!
It's tough on anyone to be
compared to the Fourth Hokage.
He had all the qualities to be
the greatest Ninja in all history.
Brimming with talent in Jutsu,
and he had a brilliant mind!
Popular with people and well...
he was as handsome as me.
But even that Fourth Hokage died quickly.
Risking his own life for the village...
Life is different from money...
To easily risk it and lose it,
is a fool's doing!
Did she say "fool"?!
Both my grandfather and the Second Hokage
seemed to want to subdue
the disturbances of war above all else.
But after all, they died in vain,
in the midst of their dreams
for the village.
You have changed, Tsunade...
I don't know what
you thought in your heart before,
but to say such thing out loud...
Although I look young,
I'm already in my 50s...
Years change people.
Same goes for Sarutobi Sensei...
No wonder he died showing off
at that old age!
Hokage is a bother.
No one but a fool would take it on.
Why you...?!
– Let go of me!
– Don't! We're in a pub.
I said, let go of me!
Lady Tsunade...!
Anyone who makes fun of the old man
and the Fourth Hokage...
It doesn't matter if
you are a woman!
I'll clobber you with all my might!
You're pretty gutsy...
confronting me like this.
Let's take this outside, brat!
Lady Tsunade!
Though I may not look it,
I am one of the Sannin.
Why should I even take a Genin seriously.
What did you say?!
An advance notice for a KO?
I don't mean one minute...
With one finger.
This is enough to take you down.
Lady Tsunade!
Well...
Come on, kiddo.
D-Don't make fun of me!
Darn it!
Lady Tsunade!
Forehead poking?!
Why that no good...!
She's strong...
Hey, brat!
I'll ask you one thing before you faint.
Why...get so passionate at
the mention of Hokage's name?
Unlike you...
I will be the heir to the Hokage name,
no matter what!
Because Hokage is...
Because Hokage is my dream!
That kid...
What? She's a bit off her guard...
I can't tackle her head on.
Then, I should use that Jutsu now...
Concentrate!
Oh, no!
Wha...?! This Jutsu is...!
Take this!
I believe your promise,
its a true heart give me courage
Always I feel it
the precious time with you
On your still shoulder
I feel the wind that blows
towards tomorrow
The city lights are like pieces of stars
That hold us together
"Each one of us
glows differently,"
you say laughingly
but you look most dazzling
Like a comet,
like the rainbow after the storm
You bring light into
my heart
Being lost
can be the answer
Let's promise
we won't cheat
Uh...like a shooting star,
we do go ahead.
It's been a long time since we drank
alone like this, isn't it, Tsunade?
I didn't necessarily want to see you.
Don't say that.
By the way,
you're prettier than before.
You haven't changed a bit.
Understand this.
I'm not interested in you.
Neither am I.
After all, you're actually 50 years old...
– Did you say something?
– No, nothing.
I was just remembering
the old days.
Next time: "Inheritance!
"The Necklace of Death!"