To think the Leaf's reinforcements
will be you of all people!
A man should always repay
the debt he owes a woman.
Always the bothersome guy with
the man and woman stuff!
Gaara and Kankuro are chasing after
the guys who took our village girl.
Forget about here and
head for them!
We've received information.
Gaara and Kankuro have entered
their respective battles.
I see...
The shadow won't reach, I guess...
Leaf Village's two-man cells are
just now heading there for back-up.
How well prepared.
It's a pain,
but as long as we're doing this,
we'll do it right.
We'll do it perfectly without
producing casualties!
Make sure you don't cry
in front of me this time.
Are you going to hold
that over my head forever?
Just like a woman...
I-I feel like I don't really
have my place in this.
I'll take care of all of you at once!
Here it comes!
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
The distance created between us
became too big,
because we were always together
Your honest reply, "See you..."
coming from that brash mouth
makes it sadder.
If you are in an unfamiliar town, crying
Then I want to deliver you a smile,
even if I'm not by your side
Fly into the wavy and twisted sky,
into your hands
I can feel it so close,
Our two hearts
Sealed Sand: The Counterattack!
To think you'd ask
the Leaf Village for help...
I guess the Sand has lost the edge
they used to have, huh?
Why are you here?
You know, dogs.
They're not satisfied until a favor
has been properly returned.
Especially this Akamaru!
A dog retuning a favor doesn't
have much of a ring to it!
Help is on the way to
the other two as well.
You concentrate on this fight!
You're giving me lip!
So you flies are gonna gang up
on me, huh?
But you're no match for my Dragon Eye:
Fang Release: Dark Sword.
Eat this!
If your Chakra isn't built up,
your sand is no big deal at all!
It'll only be useful for
blinding me at best!
It's futile!
I feel it.
Your Chakra is being sucked up.
What?! He was setting the sand
in the gourd aside?!
I was being cautious,
but he is much too strong.
Gaara Sensei!
Just what I'd expect from
Gaara of the Sand.
He's not called the ultimate weapon
for nothing...
The ultimate...weapon?!
However, he cannot exceed
our Ninja tools
forged in the Village of the Artisans!
Gaara!
Hey, he's totally got the edge!
Do we have a chance to
return the favor?
That's incredible wind.
What an amount of Chakra...
No, it seems that sword is
amplifying her Chakra.
So she's relying on that sword for
all of her attack and defense, huh?
Anyway, we've got to slip within
firing range for our Jutsu
and stop her movements!
Right.
Let's go at once!
Annoying!
She's attempting to maintain
her distance just from Temari.
I see.
So she just wants to pay attention
to the long range-type Temari and
blow us mid-range Jutsu users
away with wind
before we can get close, huh...?
Now then, what should we do?
Man Beast Clone!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
75.0101:07:33:1001:07:34:03Crow!
– Arms!
– Fang Over Fang!
Did you guys come to
get in my way?!
We made sure to send you
a signal, right?!
How could I tell?!
We don't click at all?
Are you guys...messing around?!
Be more serious and die!
Talking nonsense!
Although I reduced the damage
with my Infinite Kujaku Armor, still...
Just what I'd expect of Gaara,
the Sand's ultimate weapon
who hosts the Shukaku...
But you're already in our hands.
What should I do?
She's beyond the range of my Jutsu...
and I don't see anything around here
that could be used to extend my shadow.
Hey!
What're you whispering about?
What're you thinking?!
I'll explain later, for crying out loud.
Can you do it or not?
I suppose I could try, but...
What is it...?
What's he doing?
Behold the terror of Ninja tools
our village created.
What's this Chakra?
This is a water vein!
I get it!
The lines connecting the point
in the center and triangle isn't a Barrier...
It's a water vein!
Ninja Tool Barrier:
Reverse Scale Formation... Activate!
Oh no!
Gaara Sensei!
The aim of the Reverse Scale Formation
was a single point, Gaara from the start!
Our swords accurately pierce
a water vein
and summon the water dragon.
Sand has sucked up
a large amount of water
and has become as heavy as lead...
Now Gaara can no longer use sand.
Gaara!
– Gaara!
– Calm down!
Lee and Naruto are heading for Gaara!
That guy is?!
They'll save Gaara,
no matter what.
We need to concentrate on
the enemy in front of us.
To think you'd choose
a sandy area to fall on...
Just what I'd expect of Gaara
of the desert...
However!
That's as far as
your useless resistance goes!
Leaf Hurricane!
A hero's turn always comes late!
That's right!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Gaara!
Naruto...!
It seems you rushed to everyone
during the Sasuke incident...
This time we've come to return
the favor from that time.
So we'll take that guy on!
You hurry to your student straight on!
To think he'd corner you this far...
– Lee!
– Sakura!
Leave Gaara's treatment to me!
Lee, you go with Naruto!
– Sakura!
– Got it!
Then I'll be going first!
Be careful. His armor sucks up Chakra!
I'll suck up all of your Chakra!
I see. So this means we can't
release our regular power?
That doesn't matter!
Even without Chakra,
we've got fighting spirit!
Yes! We'll go with that
plus willpower!
Just as I thought.
That they haven't launched anything
during the fight thus far means
the two reinforcements don't
have long range-type Jutsu.
Then I'll maintain this distance and...
you'll die getting torn up by the wind!
While she's distracted by Shikamaru
and the others,
I'll just go for it!
Mind Destruction...!
Ino!
Foolish girl. It's useless to attempt
to exploit an opening!
You little!
You won't get close to me!
I've read your range as well!
I don't know about that...!
Ino! You stay right there!
I'm counting on you...!
Shino! Sakura!
There's one wounded
at the waterfall.
Tunneling Fang!
Now!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
Oh...!
What're you doing?!
Are you guys...mocking me?
After sucking up all of your Chakra,
I'll be returning the favor plenty!
The contusion treatment is complete.
But, the depletion of Chakra
is overwhelming.
Contact from your friends...?
– Ino's hurt?!
– Go!
Wha...?! But in your condition...
I'm okay now. Help your friend!
Okay. Don't push yourself.
Yeah...
What're you doing?!
Hurry up and go after your comrade!
I'll help my comrade.
I'll settle this in a moment.
But...
Bushy Brow!
Damn it. It's no good
just shot-gunning it!
It's just him?
A part of Black Ant...
Could it be...a signal?
Fang Over Fang once more!
Back me up with Crow!
I'm counting on you
for back up too, Choji!
Got it!
Heh! Bossing me around.
The counterattack starts now!
It's futile. Your Jutsu won't reach me!
You never know until you try, right...?!
Here we go!
Wind Style: Cyclone Scythe!
Huh?!
What're you aiming at?!
Totally misguided...
Say what?
What's the meaning of this?
I'm sure I'd read your range already...!
I'll show you!
I can create a shadow with
this thick a current
even if the water's clear.
My Jutsu's range has infinitely
improved by lifting the waterfall!
The Shadow Possession Jutsu
is a success!
Summoning...
Blade Dance!
This one's done!
Good grief...
I...couldn't do anything.
Here everyone's doing their best...
Only I...
Ino?
Gaara.
You don't have any sand
left you can use.
What's this?!
He smashed the Sand Armor.
No way! But the sand
heavy with water like that...
If I just suck up the Chakra...
This is my weapon!
You okay, Gaara?!
This is the finishing blow...
Gaara Sensei!
Hurry! Leave the rest to us!
Man Beast Clone!
Fang Over Fang!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
Annoying buzzing flies!
Dragon Eye: Fang Release: Dark Sword!
What?!
Oh, no!
Puppet Show...
Secret Black Move Iron Maiden!
The show's over!
– We did it!
– Yeah!
Matsuri.
Gaara and...!
A Shinobi carrying a child on his back.
He's heading for the valley.
The last one...
Gaara is chasing him!
What?!
You okay, Bushy Brow?
Sakura will be right back.
Thanks.
Well, I'm going after Gaara!
Got it! I'll meet up with you later!
I've got him cornered.
Matsuri.
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
Even if rains of spears were to fall,
I will run through it
Because I want to find the joy
without a shape
This big dream of mine that
cannot be translated to words,
I will make it come true,
even if it were to deepen my wounds
We stand here today because of
what we believed through,
That is why I will continue running forward,
never looking away
Even if I'm told that
there is no bright future
I'll change it right away,
lighting it with all my feeling
The wind is probably testing our hearts
In my heart, I gently grasped my hands
You are probably searching for
the answer to your tears
Your dream is always waiting near by,
with the answers in its hands
The Key to the rusted heart's door
Will always be smiling right near by
I heard you figured out the identities
of the Four Celestials?
Yes. They are the Ninja of
the Village of the Artisans
who've been harboring ill feeling
toward the Five Great Nations.
It seems they've completed
the forbidden project
passed down in the village and
intend to resurrect
their ultimate weapon.
I see. I take it the other villagers
got wind of it and evacuated.
Exactly. You head over to
where they are immediately.
Yes, ma'am.
Next time:
"The Ultimate Weapon Reborn"