C'mon!
Running like a fugitive,
Being chased by something
Inside my heart is pounding
My throat dry like it's withering
For no single one,
To none does belong,
This time is ours, right now...
Unraveling the pain,
Unraveling our hearts,
Unraveling shadows
Stifling our breath,
Reaching for beyond,
Tearing through the dark
In fighting and in love
To the distant light above,
Yes, we are on the way
I wanna rock...
Rockin' my heart
The Village Hidden in the Leaves.
This is a Hidden Village that has produced
many superb Ninjas.
-Hey Naruto! Why did you do such a thing?!
-You're really gonna get it this time!
The number one prankster of the village,
Naruto Uzumaki,
is a boy who is also
striving to become a first-rate Ninja.
I don't care!
Transform!
His strongest skill is the Sexy Jutsu.
–You fool!
-However, Naruto had a secret inside him.
-Stop making idiotic spells!
-that even he didn't know about.
At one time, the nine-tailed fox drove
the Village Hidden in the Leaves
to the brink of destruction...
That nine-tailed monster fox is
sealed within Naruto's body.
-Look at that one.
-Therefore, he's been abhorred
-I hear he's the only one who failed.
-as the Demon Fox by village grown-ups.
Serves him right.
Imagine what would happen
if he becomes a Ninja.
Okay, you may open your eyes now.
Congratulations on your graduation.
However, that Naruto,
-Iruka Sensei!
-on my sufferance,
-That hurts!
-graduates from the Ninja Academy.
Say cheese!
He starts off on his first step as a Ninja.
Ninja missions are conducted
by three-man cells.
Sasuke Uchiha.
A descendant of the Uchiha clan,
a distinguished family in
Hidden Leaf Village.
He is a boy towards whom Naruto harbors
intense feelings of rivalry.
Sakura Haruno is a Kunoichi who
Naruto has the hots for.
As a Ninja, Naruto carries out missions
with these two rookie Ninjas.
The one who observes and instructs them,
Kakashi Hatake,
also known as the Copy Ninja,
is the Leaf Village's most skilled Ninja.
One day, Naruto's group takes on
the mission to guard Tazuna,
a master bridge-builder
of the Land of Waves.
All right! We're off!
However, Tazuna is targeted by a man
named Gato
who attempts to control
the Land of the Waves.
Stop your darned grumbling...!!
-Next time I'll kill him with...
-And Gato had hired a terrifying man
-head chopper!
-for Tazuna's assassination.
Zabuza Momochi...
A Rogue Ninja of the Village Hidden
in the Mist.
He was a man who had excelled at
Silent Killing and
had successfully carried out
many assassinations.
Naruto and the gang have
a tough time of it
in the face of Zabuza's attacks...
Hey! You, with no brows...
Record in your Bingo Book about the man
who'll one day become
the Leaf Village's Hokage.
Naruto Uzumaki!!
It's not so easy!
A Shuriken in the Shuriken's shadow...!
However, the shoe is on the other foot,
thanks to Naruto and Sasuke's
close team work.
Kakashi copies
Zabuza's Jutsu with Sharingan.
-W-What's that?!
-It breaks Zabuza's composure.
7801:05:42:2401:05:44:29
Me...?
R-Ridiculous!
Is that his Genjutsu (illusion Jutsu)?
The Water Style! Giant Vortex Jutsu!!
No way!
It's over...
A Tracker Ninja boy
from A Hidden Mist Village
is the one who delivered the final blow.
I must get rid this corpse
because it contains many secrets.
Now then, please excuse me.
However, this boy, Haku...
was Zabuza's comrade.
Will you be all right the next time?
The next time...
I'll be able to see right
through the Sharingan.
Kakashi who has inferred
that Zabuza is still alive,
gives Naruto and gang...
-Ready!!
-new training in preparation...
-Here I go!
-for Zabuza's second assault.
And then, One week later...
This mist...
Sasuke! Sakura! They are coming!
This means a rival has emerged, Haku.
So it seems.
The time has come!
Secret Jutsu...
Crystal Ice Mirrors!
Now then... I'll start.
Take this!
Naruto Uzumaki...
is finally here!!
The Number One Hyperactive,
Knucklehead Ninja Joins the Fight!
Now that I've come, you're all right!
Oh...
Naruto!
The hero of a story generally appears
in this kind of situation
and takes out the enemy in no time!
Heh... That brat, eh...
He's long on talk...
Man, that idiot!
Making such a conspicuous entrance...
There's no point if you don't
catch the enemy off guard!
That boy...
What're you doing in a place
like this from morning?
Training!!
Why are you training?
I want to get stronger!
All right, here I go! Shadow Clone Jutsu...
Huh?!
Oh, no!
-Huh?
-Get out of the way, Naruto!
-Whoa!
-What?!
He's saved...
To think the enemy attacks
would cancel each other out...
That was super lucky...
Hey! What're you doing, Naruto?!
Hey! What kind of idiot would attempt
to cast a Jutsu directly
in front of an opponent?!
What?!
The essence of a Ninja is deception.
How you deceive your opponent.
Even casting one Jutsu,
you avoid the eyes of your opponents,
catch them off balance, and outsmart them...
The way you made your entrance earlier,
that's just you coming to be a target...
N-Nooo.
But I went to the trouble
of coming to the rescue.
What concerns me more than that is...
That guy...
Haku... What's the idea?
Zabuza, leave this kid to me...
Please let me fight this battle my way.
What did you say...?
So you mean no interfering...Haku?
You're naive...as usual...
I'm sorry...
Naive, eh...
True enough...
Judging from these wounds,
there's no mistaking that
I was attacked with a Senbon.
But no vital areas have
been targeted so far.
Does he mean to half-kill me...?
If so!
As for me, I'll take you out first, so...!
It's impossible. It's too much for Naruto!
I should be the one to...
Hey. Don't get any ideas...
If you move,
you know what'll happen
to that old man, right?
True...
If I move away from here and
head towards Naruto,
Zabuza will kill Tazuna.
No way can Sakura completely
protect him by herself.
How about it?
Let's just see how those young guys
fight against each other.
That mask...
You were Zabuza's comrade, after all,
weren't you!
You've got nerve to deceive us!
I'm sorry.
But, your teacher also said it, didn't he?
Things like deceiving and
catching one off guard is a Shinobi's duty.
Please don't take it personally.
You don't have that luxury, either!
Huh?
Sasuke?
I haven't...forgotten about you.
Here I thought he had disappeared...
but he was there...
I would rather you had
just gone down quietly.
But it looks like it won't work that way.
Fine. I'll put an end to it first.
H-Hey!
Naruto. I'll get to you later.
W-What's with him...?
This is it!
So the real body is over there, eh...
Okay!
I'm over here.
He moved...? How?!
-Sasuke!
What was that just now?!
Sasuke's body suddenly got battered...
How's he doing it?!
What kind of Jutsu is he using...?
It's conceivable that he has clones
hide in the mirrors and
gets them all to throw
the Senbons simultaneously...
No, they're too fast considering...
What does it mean...
not being able to see even
the trajectory of the weapons...?
Also, if it's a mere Clone Jutsu...
I don't see a reason for
these ice mirrors...
In any case, there's no way to question
that these mirrors are pivotal for his attacks.
What I can do is to launch attacks...
from both the outside and inside.
The thing to do is to figure out
the meaning of the mirror!
I'll take care of here!
All there is to do is...
for me to attack the inside and have Naruto
try attacking the mirrors from the outside.
Yo! I came to save you.
You okay, Sasuke?
Oh...
What good will it do you
to catch your ally off guard...?
Y-You idiot!
If you're a Shinobi,
you'll move more cautiously!
What's with you?!
I came to the rescue, you know!
If you also come inside the mirrors...
Dang it! I've had it, you fool!
Fool? What do you mean by fool?!
As to be expected of the
number one unpredictable Ninja.
He is making the situation worse and
worse by coming to aid.
Since it's come to this,
all that is left is to smash the mirrors!
-Fire Style!
-Hey! What're you going to do?!
These are mirrors made
with freezing water...
If so...
Fireball Jutsu!
It's not working at all!
They won't melt with that
level of firepower.
Darn it! Where'd he attack from?!
Is it the clones?
Where's the real body?!
It's useless for you to even
attempt following with your eyes.
I absolutely will not be caught.
Humph. Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Don't!
If so, I'll find out which is
the real body by hitting them all!
This is a teleportation Jutsu that uses
mirrors that can reflect only my image.
Watching you from the speed I move,
it almost seems as if
you aren't moving at all...
I knew it!
Is that Jutsu...the Kekkei Genkai?!
Kekkei...Genkai...?
It's the same type as my Sharingan...
Deep blood ties...
Lineage of paranormal individuals...
A type of Jutsu that is passed on
only through those traits...
Then...!
That's right...
It's impossible even for me
to copy that Jutsu...
And there's no way to destroy
that Jutsu, either!
Darn it...
So...what?!
I can't die here yet.
'Cause I have a dream
that I must turn into reality...
The dream to have my strength recognized
by everyone in the village...
and become the Hokage!
Dream...
Pathetic brat.
Brats like you aren't needed by anyone
and die without ever knowing
any freedom or dreams...
You have the same eyes as I do...
For me, becoming a Shinobi completely
is difficult.
If I can, I don't want to kill you guys...
And I don't want to get killed
by you guys...
But if you guys are going to come at me...
I'll kill my feelings with a sword and
completely become a Shinobi.
This bridge is the battleground
that connects each of us to our dreams.
I, for the sake of my dream.
And you, for the sake of your dreams.
Please don't hold it against me...
I want to protect the person dear to me...
I work for the sake of that person,
I fight for that person,
and I want to make that
person's dream a reality...
That's my dream.
For the sake of the dream,
I will completely become a Shinobi...
and kill you guys!
Crystal Ice Mirror defeated!
Cuz' I've finally discovered the way
to break through it!
Heh-heh. Okay, Sasuke.
Let's pull out of this place and
go assist Kakashi Sensei.
I've had this bad feeling from
a while ago.
Sensei, Sakura, please hold out somehow
until we get there.
Next episode:
"Zero Visibility: The Sharingan Shatters."
As for me, I'll kick butt once again!