We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers don't care
what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road filled
with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes
and take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose, so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers don't care
what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn) We're
gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn) We're
gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
Water Style!
– Water Shark Bomb Jutsu!
The same Jutsu as me?!
Why have you shown up too?
Well...I asked you to
take care of them earlier.
But I kinda felt uneasy, you know.
What business does a Rogue Ninja like you
have in this village now?
Kakashi Hatake...
Eye to Eye: Sharingan vs. Sharingan
What?! Why?! Why?!
Why do I have to go on a research
trip with you, Pervy Sage?
Oh no, this isn't just any research trip.
There's a woman
whose data I want to collect.
So we have to look for her first.
I really don't have time to accompany
you on your perverted research trip!
Because I have training!
Hm? Training?
I will take lessons from Kakashi Sensei
and learn a variety of things,
like Chidori!
Kakashi Sensei has been
playing favorites lately!
Well,
I think that technique is
impossible for you to learn.
More importantly...
That woman is really beautiful.
-You want to meet her, don't you?!
-Not at all.
I'm not some kid who can be
cajoled by you, Pervy Sage!
Anyway, no!
Well, it can't be helped...
Oh, well...
I know Jutsu more amazing
than Chidori, but...
It can't be helped...
Maybe I'll take Sasuke?
Of course I'll go!
I'll pack my bags right away.
Pervy Sage, don't move!
I'll be darned... He's really a cute kid.
Those eyes are exactly the same
as they used to be in the past.
That being said,
he is a true inheritor of the Sharingan...
I have to assume the worst-case scenario,
just in case.
This is a surprise... No wonder
you copied my Jutsu...
So there really is a fellow
besides Itachi who has that eye.
Your name is Kakashi,
the Copy Ninja, wasn't it?
I'm the one who was surprised.
I saw strange men in the tea house
and wondered who they were...
There they were Itachi Uchiha and...
the Mystery Man of Hidden Mist Village,
Kisame Hoshigaki.
Well, well... You know even my name.
It's an honor.
I see. You're one of
the "Seven Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist."
That huge sword is
the "Shark Skin," right?
I heard that kid Zabuza
had it out with you?
Yeah...
You are someone who's
well worth lopping off...
Stop it... Kisame.
If you were to go at it with that man,
it won't end without cost.
And if you spend too much time,
another Shinobi would come running.
However...
Don't lose sight of the goal...
You didn't come here to get injured!
Let me hear that "goal" then...?
Just came to find
something we're looking for.
Something you're looking for?
The thing you're looking for... What is it?
I'm different from Kisame,
I won't take time.
Ninja Art: Water Style. Water wall!
That's some Jutsu speed.
My eyes couldn't follow the Sign.
That Shuriken in the right
hand was a decoy...
to use a Water Style Jutsu to
launch an attack below my foot ...
That's what to expect from you, Kakashi.
Your power of analytical eye...is great.
A Shadow Clone?!
His Jutsu speed is too fast!
A water clone?!
The Copy Ninja has done well
this far with Jutsu of my village.
Nice! Kakashi!
Get down, Kurenai!
-This one is the Shadow Clone...
-Huh?
Kakashi! Kurenai!
He made the Shadow Clone body explode?!
A new Jutsu, a new Jutsu.
Sakura's going to start to like me...
Maybe!
Kakashi Sensei and
Sasuke will be surprised!
Kakashi...!
Don't lower your guard...
He's the guy who became a division chief
of Anbu Black Ops at 13 years old...
To think he's this powerful...
No, you haven't seen
this guy's strength yet.
I didn't expect that you who are
not a member of the Uchiha clan
would have mastered
the Sharingan to that extent...
But your body isn't the "Uchiha clan" body
that goes with the eye.
That's right. As a result,
my stamina doesn't last...
There's a reason why the Uchiha Clan
was deemed the strongest and feared...
I'll demonstrate the true strength
of Sharingan, the Kekkei Genkai!
I-It can't be! This is bad!
Both of you! Don't look at his eyes!
Both of you,
absolutely do not open your eyes...
It's all over now if your eyes meet.
Only people with Sharingan can
have a go with that technique.
Indeed with Sharingan,
you can resist this Mangekyo Sharingan
to a certain extent.
However...
this special Visual Jutsu of Sharingan,
Genjutsu: Tsukuyomi,
Nightmare Realm, is unbreakable.
The only person who can
bring me down is someone
using the same Kekkei Genkai,
a Sharingan user...
Sasuke...
I wonder how much you can
take without the Kekkei Genkai?
The one just now was...Genjutsu?
In the world of Tsukuyomi...
Both space and time...
and mass... I control them all.
For the next 72 hours...
I'll stab you continually with swords.
That's...
In the world of Tsukuyomi...
Both space and time...
and mass... I control them all.
Calm down...
This is Genjutsu.
It's best not to be optimistic
and think it's an illusion.
This pain is not an illusion.
This pain is absolutely
no different from reality.
How long will your spirit sustain?
There's... 71 hours 59
minutes 59 seconds left.
Wha...?! S-Since then...?!
That's all the time that has passed?!
What happened, Kakashi?!
Are you saying we should
keep our eyes closed still?!
N-Not...yet...
What happened?!
Just as that guy finished speaking,
you suddenly fell over!
Three days in that world
is less than a moment in
the actual world, huh...
But...why doesn't he kill me?
He could easily do so, if he wants to...
Whoa...To take that Jutsu without
causing his spirit to collapse.
But Itachi...
it's also dangerous for
you to overuse those eyes.
The thing you're looking for...
is it Sasuke?
No...
the legacy of the Fourth Hokage...
These guys.
What the heck are they planning...?
So, Naruto, is it...?
It's been a long time...
How many years has it been
since you returned to the village?
Kakashi...
I will keep Naruto under my care.
It was an understandable
decision of the Third Hokage
who appointed you to the role
of watching over Naruto...
But even at your level,
you may not be able to handle it properly.
What in the world are you saying?
I've been observing Orochimaru
ever since he left the village...
It was obvious that he would return
to this village sooner or later.
All told, at first I was concerned
only about him, but...
What is it?
The guy joined an organization.
An organization?
What are the details of the organization?
I don't know much of the details,
but it's a small organization known
as Akatsuki made up of nine Shinobi.
Until recently,
they weren't making any dramatic moves
except some cloak-and-dagger activities.
The biggest concern is
the members of that organization.
Almost all of them are
listed on the Bingo Book,
all S-rank deviant criminals.
That Itachi is among them.
If the nine of them get together,
their intent will not be
volunteer activities.
Since you've been told this much,
you already know what it means.
But recently,
Orochimaru pulled out of the organization.
And at that time,
other members of the organization
went in to action in different areas,
in pairs gathering Jutsu and things.
Is there proof that one of those
things is the Nine-Tailed Fox?
It's possible.
Because it's one of the spirits
who possess the strongest Chakra...
Kakashi...
Sooner or later,
that Naruto will have to
live watching his back...
That's his destiny.
For now, you should keep
your eyes on Sasuke.
It's necessary for you to teach
him how to use his Sharingan.
I'll take care of Naruto for a while.
The Nine-Tailed Fox inside
Naruto is your target?
I know that you two aren't
the only ones on the move...
The name of your organization
is Akatsuki, right?
Akatsuki?
Kisame! We'll take Kakashi.
Erase the other two.
Severe Leaf Hurricanes!
Who are you?
The Leaf's noble, blue fierce animal...
Mighty Guy!
What a sight...
Shouldn't you be called a strange beast?
Don't underestimate that man...
That man is Itachi!
You did this to Kakashi...?
Don't look at Itachi's eyes, Guy!
You'll be caught up in his Jutsu!
I know that already!
In order to fight Kakashi,
I devised ways to battle the Sharingan.
Open your eyes, both of you!
B-But...
When you battle with the Sharingan,
it's not a problem if
you don't look at those eyes!
You work around it by gaining
insight into his movements
by looking constantly at his feet.
Now that you mention it,
you're probably right, but...
You're the only one who can do that.
That's true...
There's a knack to reading all
of your opponents' movements
only by his feet.
But I can't teach it to
you in this emergency.
Just get used it right now!
What should we do?
Kurenai, get Kakashi to the medical team.
-Asuma, you are my back-up!
-Okay!
And until the reinforcements of
Anbu Black Ops I arranged for arrive,
I will hang out with you guys.
Interesting... That's some nerve...
Kisame... Pull the plug.
We didn't come to have a war.
It's too bad,
but no more of this nonsense.
We're leaving.
Too bad... I was finally feeling motivated.
It can't be helped.
All right!
Here I go!
Y-You're putting too much spirit into it.
You're not training on a mountain retreat,
you know that, right?
A cycle of hardship, right?
Inside, we were crying, right?
But the one thing we won't give up
is the dream we've chosen, right?
It's a secondary role,
a role in the shadows
But in reaching for that dream,
let us stay centered, let us stay true
Over and over,
we hung on without giving up
Over and over, we kept coming back up
Over and over,
we believed and dreamed
Over and over, we've seen fools
Over and over,
we've stood in the shadows of others
Now, it's our turn...
Let us bask in our dreams
There's a super beautiful
young lady over there!
She just winked at us!
Look, Naruto!
She must be interested in us!
She may be cuter than Sakura!
– All right, Naruto!
– Yeah!
Go back, train, then go to bed.
You always do that to me!
Next time: "Jiraiya:
Naruto's Potential Disaster!"
What are we gonna do about my training?!