We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers don't care
what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn)
Down a difficult road filled
with endless struggles
Where do you think you are going
following someone else's map?
An insightful crow comes along
to tear up the map
Now open your eyes
and take a look at the truth (Yeah!)
There's nothing to lose, so let's GO!!!
We are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
Fighting Dreamers don't care
what people think about them
Fighting Dreamers follow what they believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh! Just go my way
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn) We're
gonna do it and do our best!
Right here right now (Bang)
Hit it straight like a line drive!
Right here right now (Burn) We're
gonna do it and do our best! BANG!
Huh? Uh... Excuse me...
Return of the Morning Mist
My mother and my father...
They didn't have to die.
Because I didn't have strength,
the whole clan was destroyed.
Everyone was killed...
Darn it...
Morning training is over!
Once I've eaten breakfast
I'll get back to rigorous training!
Old man...
Konohamaru...
Yo! Konohomaru.
Naruto.
Have you already resumed
studies at the academy?
N-No, not yet.
The school buildings are damaged,
so we're all repairing them.
Is that so?
How about you, Naruto?
You're already training?
Sort of.
Wh-What?
What is it?
N-No, it's nothing...
– Hey um...!
So what is it...?
You too, Naruto, what is it?
Nothing...really...
-I don't feel lonely.
-Huh?
There's no time to be feeling lonely.
Everyone is working really hard
to rebuild the village right now.
Konohamaru...
Right now, I must work for
the village even just a little bit.
So Naruto,
you work hard at your training too.
If you don't,
I'll become Hokage before you.
Fool,
I will absolutely become Hokage.
Besides...you have to graduate
from the Academy first.
Oh, that's right...
Oh, here it is. Here, it's for you.
A free ramen ticket from Ichiraku...
Is it okay?
I already have one,
so I'm giving one to you.
Thank you, Naruto.
Oh! Konohamaru.
Good morning.
I'm going to go.
We'll work hard again today.
– Yep!
Today we're fixing the blackboards.
I brought paint.
Well! Once I've eaten ramen at Ichiraku,
I'll continue training.
This is it.
Th-This is...
A lot of time has passed since the death.
It's probably before
the Chunin Exam began.
I see, so that's it...
That Orochimaru!
After the murder of Lord Kazekage,
Orochimaru... or someone like
Kabuto played Kazekage...
How thoughtless we were...
That darn Sarutobi...
Well, it's not that easy.
The one who was your opponent
was the renowned Hokage,
deemed to be strongest
of all five great nations.
However...you've done well.
Two out of the five Kages...
Stop...
Stop giving me words of sympathy.
I will kill you!
Of course, I didn't mean to...
It's true that we didn't succeed
in bringing the village down...
On the other hand,
another objective of this plan,
Sasuke Uchiha...
Your leash is now on him.
In exchange for these
arms and all of my Jutsu...
If we could have gotten our hands on
that Itachi Uchiha from the beginning,
it wouldn't have been a problem.
However that's a dream
that can no longer come true.
He is stronger than I am.
That is why...
I pulled myself out from
that organization...
Kakashi, huh?
What does he want?
Breakfast, breakfast!
Wait for me, my ramen.
Do you already know his whereabouts?
Yes.
In that case, it will be easy...
Let's go.
Here it comes, here it comes.
Oh goodie, it's just like I thought.
Hidden Leaf Village...
has a high average score.
You're still doing such
a ridiculous thing?
Well yes, this is my research.
Old Man Homura and Koharu Sensei, huh?
I wonder what you advisers want from me.
Surely, you know...
without our telling you, don't you?
You don't have to make such scary faces.
I heard that the talks with Sand Village
have been settled without problems.
The Hidden Village in
the Sand announced that
everything was Orochimaru's handiwork.
In addition,
at the moment of their complete
surrender to us, the Leaf Village,
that wasn't a very
important issue any more.
Leaf Village has no choice but to
accept their surrender and proposition
in order to restore national power.
However,
the current strength of Leaf Village
has dropped drastically.
Under these conditions, our top priority
must be to prepare for
any unpredicted crisis.
We don't know when any
of the neighboring nations
will come out in a bold move.
Therefore, we've decided that until
the village gets its strength back,
we should assemble the top
few men from each troop,
and form an emergency executive
committee to handle this.
But first...
we need a strong, trustworthy leader.
You can find the seeds of trouble
rolling around everywhere these days.
It's not just Orochimaru.
You didn't have to go through
the trouble of informing me that.
Well... I'll continue gathering materials.
I'm going to tell you the basic plan.
We need the Fifth Hokage right away.
And yesterday at an emergency meeting
with the feudal lord of the Land of Fire,
we decided it would be you, Jiraiya.
I'm sorry, it's not my nature.
It has been decided.
Besides, if a Shinobi like you,
renowned as a Sannin, is not... then who is?
If you want a Sannin,
there is one more left...
That Tsunade.
Certainly that child probably
has that capability, but...
However, no one knows where she is.
I'll find and bring her back.
If I do that there's no problem, right?
But...
A wise one like Tsunade
is meant to be Hokage more than I,
with no motivation.
What do you want to do?
All right.
We'll give it urgent consideration.
However, we'll have three members
from Anbu Black Ops to accompany you
as the search unit for Tsunade.
Don't worry, I won't escape from this.
The guards are not necessary.
However...
There is one guy that I want
to take with me on my trip.
I've found an interesting egg...
What? That is absolutely strange.
Sorry, but if you don't have a ticket,
there's no ramen.
No, wait a minute!
I absolutely had one more.
Huh?
The one that I gave Konohamaru,
was it the last?
Welcome!
Hey, my ramen!
"Racy Violence"
Yo, you two!
You seem to be getting along well.
Fool, Anko asked me to buy rice dumplings.
That's all.
What are you doing here?
While I'm here to buy offerings,
I've made plans to meet here...
with Sasuke.
Huh, it's rare that you wait for people.
Is the offering to Obito?
Obito?
Well...that's about right.
Kakashi, it's strange
for you to be here first.
Well... once in a while.
I don't do natto (fermented
beans) and sweet things.
Oh... Is that so?
What?!
This is absolutely positively strange!
You guys aren't from the village...
Why in the world did you come?
I haven't seen you for
a while Asuma, Kurenai.
If you know about us,
are you former Leaf Shinobi?
– Huh?!
Y-You are?!
Humph, without a doubt...
Itachi...
Uchiha.
You are acquaintances of Itachi?
If so...
I'll introduce myself as well.
I'm Kisame Hoshigaki.
Hereafter, I hope to be familiar with you.
Never mind later,
I'm going to beat you now!
Itachi...
It seems you're pretty
unpopular in the village too.
I know you, too.
Kisame Hoshigake,
originally a Shinobi of
Hidden Village in the Mist.
Suspected of national covert
activities and of killing a feudal lord,
a Rogue Ninja from Land of Water,
on the wanted list in all nations.
You're a major S-rank criminal
listed in the Bingo Book.
Itachi, you have some nerve
coming back to this village
after causing that awful incident.
Asuma... Kurenai...
Don't interfere with me.
I don't intend to kill you.
That's not a line for you,
who killed your comrades.
I know there's no way you'd come here
without any clear purpose in
those suspicious appearance.
What are you after?
This guy is pretty annoying.
Should we kill him?
It doesn't look like we are able to
leave the village so smoothly...
But don't overdo it,
your techniques tend to stand out.
They're done for then.
This is...
Genjutsu.
Pressing down with the tip of
his sword... What strength.
My large sword, Shark Skin...
doesn't cut, but lops it off!
Kurenai... You're late.
With this...
it's over!
Genjutsu of that level doesn't work on me.
This is...Genjutsu Reversal?
Kurenai!
There's no time to look away.
That's what's expected from you,
Kurenai. But...
"But" this is as far as it goes...
for you.
What?!
Water Style!
– Water Shark Bomb Jutsu!
The same Jutsu as me?!
Why have you shown up too?
Well...I asked you to
take care of them earlier.
But I kinda felt uneasy, you know.
Shadow clones.
Kakashi... Hatake.
Cripes... So much fuss for nothing.
I...
I put it under my headband
in order not to drop the important
ticket during morning training.
Okay, that's fine...
Eat well and do your best.
Hmm?
You're going to do it again after this,
right? Training?
Of course! I'm full of motivation.
Good! Here you go.
Another serving for free! Go for it!
Thank you, sir!
Welcome.
Just like I heard... I had
to come and see it.
It seems that you really
are just eating ramen.
Oh, Pervy Sage!
A cycle of hardship, right?
Inside, we were crying, right?
But the one thing we won't give up
is the dream we've chosen, right?
It's a secondary role,
a role in the shadows
But in reaching for that dream,
let us stay centered, let us stay true
Over and over,
we hung on without giving up
Over and over, we kept coming back up
Over and over,
we believed and dreamed
Over and over, we've seen fools
Over and over,
we've stood in the shadows of others
Now, it's our turn...
Let us bask in our dreams
Itachi Uchiha...
who became a leader of
Anbu Black Ops at the age of thirteen
and who destroyed the Uchiha
clan single-handedly.
I don't know why he has suddenly
appeared after all this time...
But I don't think we will
allow him to leave so easily.
What is your purpose?!
Next time: "Sharingan vs. Sharingan!"